sharethrough.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy - Sharethrough

### Sharethrough Privacy Policy

This content is displayed by [Sharethrough](http://www.sharethrough.com/), the all-in-one native advertising application for publishers, app developers and advertisers, and is paid for by the advertiser or marketer displayed. You can read our Privacy Policy to learn more about how we use information to operate our application and deliver content, and to learn how to "opt out" of the targeted advertising of many companies that help deliver interest based advertising using our application or other content, websites and applications. We adhere to the standards of the DAAC online advertising program, and you may learn more about and opt out from companies that participate in that program at youradchoices.ca.

* * *

## Privacy Policy

Welcome to Sharethrough.com, a Website owned and controlled by Sharethrough, Inc., (“Sharethrough,” “we”, “us”, or “our”). We operate a platform through which websites and mobile application or “app” developers and similar platforms can display content on behalf of our advertisers (the “Promoted Content”). This content we display is labeled “Ad” or similarly identified as paid or sponsored content. You may have reached this policy by clicking on an icon adjacent to our Promoted Content.

Sharethrough helps websites, mobile apps and web services to provide engaging and relevant third party content to their users, thus often subsidizing their free content and media. To do this, we may collect and use data received from those websites and apps and their users, in anonymous form.

We provide this Privacy Policy to let you know what data we collect when you view the Promoted Content or when you visit this website, and for what purposes we use, share and protect that data. We value user privacy and transparency.

**1\. What this Policy Applies To**

This Privacy Policy applies to the website located at [www.sharethrough.com](https://sharethrough.com/) (the “Sharethrough Website”), the tools and interactive forums made available through the Sharethrough Website and the Promoted Content-advertising platform (collectively the “Services”), which includes Promoted Content offered on websites and mobile applications.

Generally, there are three categories of users of the Sharethrough Website and Services: “Publishers” who are operators or publishers of websites and apps that display the Promoted Content; “Advertisers,” who display their content across our platform, and “Users” who are individuals that use a Publisher’s website or app. By visiting the Sharethrough Website or using the Services, you are accepting the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy governs two sets of data practices:

  * Privacy Practices for Users of the Sharethrough Services and Promoted Content
  * Privacy Practices for Users of This Website (set forth in Section 5)

**2\. Sharethrough Services Content Choices and Opt-Out Choices**

We believe that delivering targeted and relevant content enhances your internet and mobile experience, and subsidizes free media and other popular content. As we describe further in this Privacy Policy, we (or a partner we work with) may collect anonymous, non-Personal Information associated with your web or mobile activities (described in Section 3). When we say “non-Personal Information,” we mean information that may be uniquely tied to a browser or device but that does not itself contain your name, address, phone number, email address, or other government identifier (like social security number). We and they use this information to provide content that is more relevant and engaging, and less likely to be annoying – for instance, to reduce your chances of seeing the same content repeatedly, or of seeing content that is irrelevant to your interests. 

If you prefer that we and/or third party platforms we work with not collect this information about your web or mobile activity for the purpose of delivering targeted advertising, you may opt out of many of the online advertising platforms that deliver targeting advertising. If you wish to opt out of (or simply learn more about) the platforms that may customize ads or content to you, and with whom we may sometimes work, you may visit the websites hosted by the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://aboutads.info/) and the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/). Please note these opt out tools are cookie-based, so if you block cookies, delete your cookies, or change or update your browser, you will need to opt out again. You may also opt out of receiving mobile-based advertising based on our collection of mobile identifiers (such as the IDFA or the Android Ad ID) through your device “settings.” 

You may also opt out of receiving mobile-based advertising based on our collection of mobile identifiers (such as the IDFA or the Android Ad ID) through your device “settings.” For example, to adjust your advertising preferences in iOS, visit Settings > Privacy > Advertising > Limit Ad Tracking. To adjust your advertising preferences in Android, visit Settings > Google > Ads > Opt out of interest-based ads.  (The precise language used may be slightly different on certain, or older, devices.) We either collect these opt-out signals ourselves or receive them from the mobile apps we work with.

**3\. Privacy Practices for End Users Who Receive and View The Content: The Data We Collect and How We Use and Share It.**

An essential part of the Service is the Sharethrough platform, which helps app developers and website owners provide more relevant third party content to their users. If you are reading this policy, you are probably familiar with the way that Sharethrough helps Advertisers display Promoted Content on websites and mobile apps. When you view or click on Promoted Content (web or mobile), we collect certain non-Personal Information automatically for use on our platform. We may enable Publishers to use all or some of this information through the Platform for analytics purposes and we also use this information (working with third party platforms) to customize Promoted Content to you, as described below.

**(a) The Information We Collect When You View Promoted Content**

When you click and view Promoted Content we or a third party platform we work with may collect certain Non-Personal Information about you. When we say “Non-Personal Information,” we mean information that generally cannot by itself be used to identify who you are on an individual, personal level (unlike, for instance, name/address, telephone number or even email address). If you view the Promoted Content through a mobile application, we may collect, retain, and use the following information:

  1. A device identifier such as an Apple IDFA or an Android Advertising ID;
  2. Your IP address (which is a number automatically assigned to your computer when you access the Internet and can be used to derive your general geographic location);
  3. The application that your device is using when interacting with Sharethrough content, and a time-stamp regarding that interaction;
  4. Information about your device and operating system;
  5. Other information that you voluntarily submit to us.

If you view the Promoted Content in a web or mobile browser, we or a third party platform we work with may collect, retain and use information including:

  1. The type of browser and operating system you have used to access the website;
  2. Your IP address (which is a number automatically assigned to your computer when you access the Internet and can be used to derive your general geographic location);
  3. Information revealed by your browser when you view or open the Promoted Content, including the website you visited before clicking and viewing the Promoted Content, time stamp and user agent string, click stream information, browser type, browser language, date and time you viewed the Promoted Content. We may collect or store this information by using cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies. You can learn more about these online technologies in Section 4 below;
  4. Other information that you voluntarily submit to us.

**(b) How We Use the Information We Collect When You View Promoted Content.**

We may use (or work with third party ad and content platforms that use) the above information for the following purposes, including through the use of cookie and device identifiers, which are explained in further detail in Section 4. Generally, we enable third party ad and content platforms to fulfill these purposes by “syncing” publisher identifiers with these platforms’ identifiers, which permits these platforms to target relevant ads to consumers (often based on other information these platforms have collected):

  1. To tailor the content we (or others, including advertisers and content providers) display to you, including building relevant data segments based on what you click and view (e.g., “enjoys sports,” “enjoys classic rock”) and when or how many times you have viewed it;
  2. To coordinate the content that we display to you across devices, including across mobile and web-based platforms, by making anonymous inferences about that device linkage;
  3. To better understand how the Service is being used and improve the Service, including to create and share with our customers (and related third parties) aggregated and analytical models regarding how, when and by whom Content is viewed – for instance, if certain ads are viewed more often at certain times, or by certain audiences;
  4. To provide insights to our customers (and related third parties) regarding website or mobile ad campaign optimization, ad placement or frequency metrics – for instance, to help advertisers understand whether and why certain ads performed well or not, and how those ads relate to other information that may be known about a user;
  5. To help us ensure that the Service is functioning properly;
  6. For other anonymous ad delivery and reporting purposes not specifically listed above;
  7. For any other purpose disclosed to you at the time your information is collected.

**(c) How we Share the Information We Collect When You View Promoted Content. We may share information collected relating to the Promoted Content, as follows:**

  1. Affiliates and Partners. We may share your non-Personal Information with our affiliates — companies that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with us — as well as select partners and service providers who help us offer our Services. We may also share this information with Publishers, Advertisers and other third party service providers (such as data management platforms and ad networks) in order to provide our Services. These entities may, for instance, use your information to make or help us make predictions about your interests, and may provide you with offers, promotional materials, and advertisements.
  2. Service Providers. We may share any information (including Personal Information you provide to us, such as through this website) with entities that provide services to us, including companies that provide payment processing, customer and web support, web analytics, data processing, data enhancement and customer insights, advertising, email distribution, and other services.
  3. Other Parties When Required by Law or as Necessary to Protect Our Services. We may disclose your information (including Personal Information) to other parties in order to: 
    * protect the legal rights or property of Sharethrough, our affiliates, and sites or services we work with;
    * protect the rights, safety and security of our users, ourselves, or any other person or entity;
    * prevent fraud (or for risk management purposes); or
    * comply with or respond to the law or legal process or a request for cooperation by a government entity, whether or not legally required. For example, where appropriate, we may be required to disclose your information to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
  4. Other Parties in Connection With a Transfer of Assets. If we make a sale or transfer of assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger or transfer (or due diligence related to such a transaction), or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, we may transfer your information as part of that transaction.
  5. We (or third party platforms we work with) may aggregate your Non-Personal Information with the Non-Personal Information of others and share that aggregated information without restriction, including with Publishers and Advertisers, such as for analytics purposes or to help them learn more about their customers and users and better tailor and measure ads, content and offers sent to actual and potential customers.

**4\. Cookies, Web Beacons, and Similar Technologies**

We, and third party ad and content platforms we work with, may use cookies and similar technologies on the Sharethrough website and when you engage with our services, such as when you view or click on Promoted Content. This section provides more information about some of those technologies and how they work.

(a) Cookies. Cookies are small text files that websites and other online services use to store information about users on the users’ own computers. For instance, when you are on certain websites, cookies can be used to store sign-in credentials so that you don’t have to enter them each time you return to a website, or to store other information to make web viewing more customized or efficient upon future visits. Cookies also may store a unique identifier tied to your computer so that web services and content and advertising networks can recognize you across visits to different websites. You can configure your internet browser to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse all or certain cookies completely, but if you do so, it will likely affect your ability to fully engage with certain websites.

(b) Sharethrough (and third party platforms we work with) may use or support cookies as follows:

  1. To collect information about your browsing activities in order to deliver the Services; 
  2. To relate the information collected by cookies to information we obtain from you directly (such as through this Website) or from commercially available sources;
  3. To work with third parties that help us serve Promoted Content (through our Services or across the internet) or provide other services to us, such as providing users the ability to view or comment on content or tracking site usage statistics;

We also may use cookies (and web beacons, described below) for all of the purposes we’ve set forth in the above Section titled “How We Use the Information We Collect When You View Promoted Content.” We (or third party platforms we work with) may also use mobile identifiers, like Apple IDFAs and Android Advertising IDs, for those same purposes.

(c) Web beacons. We (or third party platforms we work with) may use technologies called “Web beacons” that communicate information from your Internet browser to a web server. Web beacons can be embedded in web pages, videos, or emails, and can allow a web server to read certain types of information from your browser, check whether you have viewed a particular web page or email message, and determine, among other things, the time and date on which you viewed the Web beacon, the IP address of your computer, and the URL of the web page from which the Web beacon was viewed. We, or our partners, may use web beacons for a variety of purposes, including to analyze the use of the Services and in conjunction with cookies to provide content that is more relevant to you.

**5\. Privacy Practices for Users of this Website**

**(a) The Information We Gather on the Website and How We Use it:**

The Sharethrough Website itself is primarily directed to Publishers and Advertisers, but we welcome Users who want to know more about our Services. When you access the Website or Services, we may collect the following information:

  1. Personal Information. When you set up an account with us (for instance, to sign up as a Publisher), we may request and you may provide certain “Personal Information” to us – that is, is information that may be used to directly identify a person based on their individual, personal identity. This may include your name, postal address, e-mail address, or phone number, and other information associated with this Personal Information. We collect Personal Information from you when you knowingly provide it, such as when you register as an Advertiser or Publisher on the Website, communicate with us and/or or request information. We may use your Personal Information to administer your account and provide you services, to send communications and administrative emails, learn more about our Users and customers, to respond to your inquiries, and to send marketing and product update messages. 
  2. Non-Personal Information. Whether or not you sign up for an account or provide us with Personal Information, we may collect other Non-Personal Information when you visit our Website. This may include:
    1. The type of browser and operating system you have used to access the website;
    2. Your IP address (which is a number automatically assigned to your computer when you access the Internet and can be used to derive your general geographic location);
    3. What part of our Website you visit, click and view, and how long you view them;
    4. Other information that you submit to us.

We may collect or store the above information by using cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies, and may target or retarget ads to you using those cookies, device identifiers, or similar technologies, when you browse the Internet or use your mobile device. 

**(b) Accessing and Controlling Our Use of Your Information:**

We acknowledge the right of individuals to access their personal data. If you provide Personal Information when registering for our Website, you may access and modify that information at any time by visiting your account settings. While we would be sorry to see you go, you can delete your account at any time by contacting support@Sharethrough.com. Keep in mind, however, that even if you delete your account, we may retain your information to comply with laws, prevent fraud, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law, and account deletion does not result in deletion of information collected in connection with our Services. Following any deletion, there may be residual information that remains within our databases, access logs, and other records. In addition, we are not responsible for updating or removing your information already disclosed to third parties who have been provided information as permitted by this Policy. In addition, You can opt out of receiving certain email communications from the Website by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each email. Please note that even if you unsubscribe or opt-out, we may still send you communications related to your use of the Service. Please refer to the “International Users” section below for additional options. 

**6\. MISCELLANEOUS TERMS**

**(a) Information Security, Retention, and Data Integrity**

We take security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. However, no security safeguard is 100 percent foolproof, and, like other web and mobile applications and platforms, we are unable to guarantee that the security measures we take will not be penetrated or compromised or that your information will remain secure under all circumstances.

**(b) Children**

We do not intentionally collect or maintain Personal Information from individuals who are under 13 years of age, and no portion of our Website or Services is designed to attract people under the age of 13. Protecting the privacy of children is important to us: if we learn that a user is under the age of 13, we will take reasonable steps to remove that user’s Personal Information from our databases.

**(c) Links to Other Websites**

While we may link to another website or service through this Website, or allow others to share content on them, that is not an endorsement, authorization or representation that we are affiliated with that third party, nor is it an endorsement or acknowledgement of their privacy practices. Other websites and services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

**(d) International Users**

The Website and Services are hosted in the United States and elsewhere. Through your access to the Website or Services, you consent to the transfer of your information to the United States and other countries. The laws in the United States and the other countries regarding processing the information may be less stringent than in your country.

Sharethrough complies with the principles of the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and the United Kingdom. Sharethrough has certified that it adheres to the Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/list.

Sharethrough may be liable for the appropriate transfer of EU or U.K. individual’s personal data to third parties.

To file a complaint, residents of any country, including countries participating in the Privacy Shield, may contact us as described at the end of this Policy. Sharethrough has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles to BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from Sharethrough, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Sharethrough, please visit www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/ for more information and to file a complaint. Finally and as a last resort, EU or U.K. individuals whose privacy complaint has not been resolved may appeal to the Privacy Shield Panel, a binding arbitration mechanism.

Sharethrough is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission.

Individuals in some countries outside the United States (including all individuals whose information we collect under the Privacy Shield) have certain legal rights to access certain information we hold about them and to obtain its correction, amendment or deletion (in addition to the options described in the “Accessing and Controlling Our Use of Your Information” section above). To exercise those rights, they may contact us as described below.

**(e) Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, which may occur through our posting of new terms, made effective after a reasonable period of time.

**7\. THE EU GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR)**

As of May 25, 2018, a new data privacy law known as the EU General Data Protection Regulation (or the “GDPR”) will be in effect through the EEA countries and Switzerland. The GDPR requires Sharethrough and those using our services to provide users with certain information about the processing of their “Personal Data.” “Personal Data” is a term used in Europe that means, generally, data that identifies or can identify a particular unique user or device – for instance, names, addresses, cookie identifiers, mobile device, precise location data and biometric data.

To comply with the GDPR, we provide the below representations and information, which are specific to persons located in EEA countries or Switzerland (so don’t rely on the below, if you’re not).

**a. Legal grounds for processing your Personal Data**

The GDPR requires us to tell you about the legal basis we’re relying on to process any Personal Data about you.  The legal basis for us processing your Personal Data for the purposes set out in Sections 3 and 4 above (and Section 5 as to our corporate customer data) will typically be because:

  * _You provided your consent._ In order to store and gain access to information stored on your device, we rely on your consent. For this so-called “cookie consent” (which applies not only to “cookies” but also to mobile ad identifiers), we rely on our own compliance steps and our web and mobile partners’ compliance steps, designed to ensure that consent is collected and passed on to partners, and to ensure that we only facilitate the collection of legally obtained data. We do this to fulfill our obligations under the ePrivacy Directive. We may choose to obtain consent in other cases as well, in which case we will adhere to applicable laws relating to such consent and its withdrawal.
  * _The processing is in our legitimate interest._ In some cases, we use legitimate interest as a legal basis for processing Personal Data, in order to provide our and/or other data controllers’ services. Such processing goes beyond the original collection of a mobile ad identifiers. A legitimate interest we rely on, for instance, is the tailoring of promotional communications to users of web and mobile properties, which is beneficial to users and is an integral part of the ecosystem by which freely available content is funded through advertising revenue. This also sometimes includes providing analysis of and reporting about ad campaigns, as well.
  * We also rely on legitimate interest when we use Personal Data to maintain the security of our Services, such as to detect fraud or to ensure that bugs are detected and fixed.
  * _Contractual Relationships._ Sometimes, we process certain data as necessary under a contractual relationship we have (such as our customer records and contact information);
  * _Legal Obligations._ Finally, some processing of data may be necessary for us to comply with our legal or regulatory obligations.

**b. Transfers of Personal Data**

As Sharethrough works with global companies and technologies, we may need to transfer your Personal Data outside of the country from which it was originally provided. For instance, we may transfer your data to third parties that we work with who may be located in jurisdictions outside the EEA or Switzerland, and which have no data protection laws or laws that are less strict compared with those in Europe.

When we transfer Personal Data outside of the EEA or Switzerland, we take steps to make sure that appropriate safeguards are in place to protect your Personal Data. For example, as described in Section 6(d) Sharethrough is Privacy Shield certified, and thus self-certifies to protect Personal Data from the EEA and Switzerland in accordance with established data privacy principles. You can learn more about this in Section 11. Feel free to contact us at the contact information below, for more information about the safeguards we have put in place to protect your Personal Data and privacy rights in these circumstances.

**c. Personal Data Retention**

As a general matter, we retain your Personal Data for as long as necessary to provide our Services, or for other important purposes such as complying with legal obligations, resolving disputes, and enforcing our agreements. We generally render our own identifiers (e.g., those we use to “sync” our customers data to online users) inactive after **[13 months]** , provided that we may retain them if we have a legal or significant operational need to do so, such as for auditing, corporate record-keeping, compliance accounting or security and bug-prevention purposes.

**d. Your Rights as a Data Subject**

The GDPR provides you with certain rights in respect of Personal Data that data controllers hold about you, including certain rights to access Personal Data, to request correction of the Personal Data, to request to restrict or delete Personal Data, and to object to our processing of your Personal Data (including profiling for online ad targeting).

  * _Right To Access:_ If you wish to exercise your right to access Personal Data we process as a data controller, you may do so by requesting access through the e-mail address [support@sharethrough.com](mailto:support@sharethrough.com). When we receive your request, we will provide you with current, step-by-step instructions to follow in order to obtain access. As we are required to verify a requestor’s identity prior to providing Personal Data, we will assess requests to exercise certain data access rights on a case-by-case basis: in doing so, we consider (a) the difficulty of verifying whether data that we hold and data we have linked to it truly and solely belongs to the data subject making the request, along with (b) the potential adverse affects on disclosure of personal data to the wrong individual. Because such improper disclosure would likely adversely affect the privacy rights and freedoms of the data subject, we may limit the Personal Data we make available.
  * Please note that we will only grant requests submitted via email for Personal Data for which we are a data controller, as explained further, below. Where we act as a processor for one of our customers, we will refer your request to that customer. Please identify the customer your request refers to (if possible), to simplify this process.

_Right to Correct:_ If you wish to exercise your right to correct Personal Data, you may do so by contacting us at the contact information below.

_Right to Object to Processing or to Withdraw Consent:_ By using the browser-based cookie “opt out” and device-based “opt-out” signals described in Section 2 of this Privacy Policy, you may withdraw consent for processing on which we rely on consent. If you do so, we will cease processing your Personal Data for purposes of our services within 30 days or less.

We either collect these opt-out signals ourselves or receive them from the mobile apps we work with.

  * _Right to Erasure._

You also have the right to obtain the erasure of Personal Data concerning you that we hold as a controller. The above opt-out process satisfies this right. When a user opts-out through our partners (or through mobile device settings), and we receive this signal, we no longer use Personal Data to provide our advertising services. We will also manually delete your Personal Data if prefer that we do so; please contact us at support@sharethrough.com for further instructions if you wish to exercise this right manually. Please note, however, that we may retain copies of certain Personal Data on inactive or back-up files, for our own internal and necessary purposes, such as auditing, accounting and billing, legal or bug-detection. We will in most cases delete such data within 36 months, absent a compelling reason to retain it. 

  * _Right to Lodge Complaints._ You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority. However, we hope that you will first consult with us, so that we may work with you to resolve any complaint or concern you might have.

**e. Sharethrough as a data controller and a data processor**

EU data protection law makes a distinction between organisations that process Personal Data for their own purposes (known as “data controllers”) and organisations that process Personal Data on behalf of other organisations (known as “data processors”). As noted above, we are not always a data controller of the data in our possession, but are sometimes a data processor for other companies such as our customers. In such cases, we may direct your inquiry to the relevant data controller, since data controllers are the ones with primary responsibility for your Personal Data.

**8.Enforcement, Questions, and Complaints**

If you have any inquiries or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, or to exercise your rights, please contact us by emailing us at [privacy@sharethrough.com](mailto:privacy@sharethrough.com) or writing to us at: 

Sharethrough, Inc.  
Attention: Privacy Inquiries   
170 Columbus Ave, Suite 280  
San Francisco, CA 94133 

Last Updated: May 2018

**Politique de confidentialité de Sharethrough**

Ce contenu vous est proposé par [Sharethrough](http://sharethrough.com/), le logiciel de publicités natives tout-en-un destiné aux éditeurs, aux développeurs d'applications et aux annonceurs, et pris directement en charge par l'annonceur ou le distributeur. Sharethrough utilise la méthode de ciblage dite « par centres d'intérêt » pour aider les professionnels du marketing et les éditeurs avec lesquels nous travaillons à proposer à leurs utilisateurs des publicités et un contenu plus pertinents. Consultez notre politique de confidentialité pour découvrir comment nous utilisons ces informations aux fins de la livraison de contenu et comment se désinscrire du ciblage Sharethrough sur ce navigateur ou cet appareil, ou ce [site web mis au point par le secteur](http://www.aboutads.info/) permettant de renoncer aux services de nombreuses autres sociétés qui proposent des publicités selon les centres d'intérêt. Nous adhérons aux normes du programme de publicité en ligne de la DAAC, et vous pouvez en apprendre davantage sur les entreprises qui participent à ce programme sur le site youradchoices.ca et vous en retirer.

* * *

## Politique de confidentialité

Bienvenue sur Sharethrough.com, un site web qui est détenu et contrôlé par Sharethrough, Inc., (« Sharethrough », « nous », « notre » ou « nos »). Nous gérons une plateforme permettant aux sites web, aux développeurs d'applications mobiles ou « applis » et à d'autres plateformes similaires de diffuser du contenu au nom de nos annonceurs (le « Contenu sponsorisé »). Ce contenu est identifié à l'aide du terme « publicité » ou comme contenu sponsorisé ou ayant fait l'objet d'une transaction financière. Il est d'ailleurs possible que vous consultiez actuellement la présente politique après avoir cliqué sur une icône apparaissant à côté de notre Contenu sponsorisé.

Sharethrough aide les sites web, les applications mobiles et les services en ligne à proposer un contenu tiers intéressant et pertinent à leurs utilisateurs. C'est pourquoi, les médias et le contenu gratuits que nous proposons sont souvent subventionnés. À cet effet, nous sommes susceptibles de recueillir et d'utiliser les données reçues de ces sites web et applications ainsi que de leurs utilisateurs de manière anonyme.

Nous avons élaboré la présente Politique de confidentialité pour que vous sachiez quelles données nous recueillons lorsque vous consultez un Contenu sponsorisé ou naviguez sur ce site web et à quelles fins nous utilisons, partageons et protégeons ces données. Nous accordons une très grande importance à la confidentialité de nos utilisateurs et à la transparence.

**1\. Champ d'application de la présente Politique**

La présente Politique de confidentialité s'applique au site web accessible à partir de l'adresse [www.sharethrough.com](https://sharethrough.com/) (le « Site Sharethrough »), aux outils et forums interactifs mis à disposition via le Site Sharethrough et à la plateforme publicitaire de contenu sponsorisé (collectivement les « Services ») comprenant le Contenu sponsorisé proposé sur les sites web et les applications mobiles.

Globalement, il existe trois catégories d'utilisateurs du Site Sharethrough et de ses Services : Les « Éditeurs », c'est-à-dire les opérateurs ou éditeurs des sites web et applications où est diffusé le Contenu sponsorisé ; les « Annonceurs » qui diffusent leur contenu à travers notre plateforme ; et les « Utilisateurs » qui sont les personnes utilisant le site web ou l'application d'un Éditeur. En naviguant sur le Site Sharethrough ou en utilisant les Services, vous acceptez les principes et procédures décrites dans la présente Politique de confidentialité.

La présente Politique de confidentialité régit deux ensembles de procédures en matière de données :

  * les Procédures de confidentialité pour les Utilisateurs des Services Sharethrough et du Contenu sponsorisé ; et
  * les Procédures de confidentialité pour les Utilisateurs du Site Sharethrough (telles qu'elles sont décrites à la Section 5)

**2\. Choix du contenu des Services Sharethrough et options de désinscription**

Nous estimons que la livraison d'un contenu ciblé et pertinent améliore votre expérience de navigation en ligne et mobile et permet de financer les médias et contenus qui vous sont proposés gratuitement. Comme nous l'indiquons plus loin dans la présente Politique de confidentialité, nous (ou l'un de nos partenaires) pouvons recueillir de manière anonyme des Informations à caractère non personnel en connexion avec vos activités sur un navigateur web ou un appareil mobile (cf. Section 3). « Informations non personnelles » fait référence aux informations pouvant faire l'objet de la création d'un lien unique avec un navigateur ou un appareil, mais où ne figurent pas vos nom, numéro de téléphone ou adresse e-mail ni toute autre donnée d'identification officielle (comme votre numéro de sécurité sociale). Nos partenaires et nous-mêmes utilisons ces informations pour vous proposer un contenu plus pertinent et intéressant et moins susceptible d'être perçu comme une nuisance. Vous avez ainsi moins de chances de voir le même contenu à plusieurs reprises ou un contenu qui ne correspond pas à vos goûts et centres d'intérêt.

Si vous ne souhaitez pas que nous, et/ou les plateformes tierces avec lesquelles nous travaillons, recueillions ces informations à propos de vos activités sur votre navigateur web ou mobile aux fins de la fourniture de publicités ciblées, vous pouvez choisir de ne pas vous inscrire sur les plateformes publicitaires en ligne proposant des publicités ciblées. Si vous souhaitez vous désinscrire des plateformes tierces pouvant proposer un contenu personnalisé ou des publicités ciblées avec lesquelles nous sommes susceptibles de travailler de temps en temps (ou simplement pour en savoir plus à ce propos), rendez-vous sur les sites web hébergés par la [Digital Advertising Alliance](https://www.aboutads.info/) et la [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/). Sachez que ces outils de désinscription utilisent des cookies et que si vous choisissez de bloquer leurs cookies, de les supprimer ou de modifier ou mettre à jour votre navigateur, vous devrez vous désinscrire à nouveau. Vous pouvez également exprimer votre refus de tout contenu publicitaire mobile à l'aide de nos identifiants d'abonné mobile (comme votre identifiant publicitaire Android ou votre IDFA) en configurant les paramètres de votre appareil. 

**3\. Procédures de confidentialité pour les Utilisateurs finaux recevant et consultant le Contenu  : quelles sont les données recueillies et comment nous les utilisons et les partageons**

La plateforme Sharethrough fait partie intégrante des Services proposés ; elle aide les développeurs d'applications et les propriétaires de sites web à fournir un contenu tiers plus pertinent à leurs utilisateurs. Si vous lisez la présente politique, vous savez probablement comment Sharethrough aide les Annonceurs à diffuser un Contenu sponsorisé sur les sites web et les applications mobiles. Lorsque vous consultez ou cliquez sur un Contenu sponsorisé (web ou mobile), nous recueillons automatiquement certaines Informations à caractère non personnel aux fins de leur utilisation sur notre plateforme. Nous pouvons autoriser les Éditeurs à utiliser la totalité ou une partie de ces informations via la Plateforme à des fins analytiques et nous utilisons également ces informations (en collaboration avec d'autres plateformes tierces) afin de vous proposer un Contenu sponsorisé personnalisé, tel que décrit ci-dessous.

**(a) Informations recueillies lorsque vous consultez un Contenu sponsorisé**

Lorsque vous cliquez sur un Contenu sponsorisé et le consultez, nous ou l'une des plateformes tierces avec lesquelles nous travaillons, pouvons recueillir des Informations non personnelles à votre égard. Les « Informations non personnelles » sont des informations qui, utilisées seules, ne permettent généralement pas l'identification d'une personne physique (contrairement, par exemple, au nom, à l'adresse, au numéro de téléphone ou à l'adresse e-mail). Si vous consultez le Contenu sponsorisé via une application mobile, nous pouvons recueillir, conserver et utiliser les informations suivantes : 

  1. Un identificateur d'appareil, tel un identifiant publicitaire Android ou l'IDFA d'Apple ;
  2. Votre adresse IP (qui est un numéro automatiquement attribué à votre ordinateur lorsque vous accédez à Internet et peut servir à déterminer votre emplacement géographique général) ;
  3. L'application utilisée par votre appareil lors de vos interactions avec le contenu Sharethrough, et l'horodatage concernant cette interaction ;
  4. Des données de géolocalisation, y compris des données de géolocalisation précises, comme lorsque vous consultez le Contenu sponsorisé via une application mobile ;
  5. Toute autre information que vous nous soumettez de votre plein gré.

Si vous consultez le Contenu sponsorisé sur un navigateur web ou mobile, nous-mêmes, ou une plateforme tierce avec laquelle nous travaillons, pourrons recueillir, conserver et utiliser les informations suivantes :

  1. Le type de navigateur et le système d'exploitation utilisés pour accéder au site web ;
  2. Votre adresse IP (qui est un numéro automatiquement attribué à votre ordinateur lorsque vous accédez à Internet et peut servir à déterminer votre emplacement géographique général) ;
  3. Les informations transmises par votre navigateur lorsque vous consultez ou ouvrez le Contenu sponsorisé, y compris le site web visité avant de cliquer et de consulter le Contenu sponsorisé, les données d'horodatage et de la chaîne d'agent utilisateur, les données sur le flux de clics, le type de navigateur, la langue du navigateur et la date et l'heure à laquelle vous avez consulté le Contenu sponsorisé. Nous pourrons recueillir et stocker ces informations à l'aide de cookies, de balises web et d'autres technologies similaires. Pour en apprendre davantage sur ces technologies en ligne, veuillez vous référer à la Section 4 ci-dessous ;
  4. Toute autre information que vous nous soumettez de votre plein gré.

**(b) Comment nous utilisons les informations recueillies lorsque vous consultez un Contenu sponsorisé**

Nous sommes susceptibles d'utiliser (ou de travailler avec des plateformes publicitaires et de contenu tierces qui utilisent) les informations ci-dessus aux fins suivantes, y compris de par l'utilisation d'identifiants de cookies ou d'appareils, qui font l'objet d'explications plus détaillées à la section 4. Généralement, nous autorisons les plateformes publicitaires et de contenu tierces à remplir ces objectifs en « synchronisant » les identifiants des éditeurs avec les identifiants de ces plateformes, ce qui permet aux plateformes de proposer des publicités pertinentes au consommateur (souvent sur la base d'informations complémentaires recueillies au préalable par ces plateformes :

  1. Pour personnaliser le contenu que nous vous proposons (ou que d'autres vous proposent, y compris les publicitaires et fournisseurs de contenu), notamment en développant des segments de données pertinents en fonction de vos clics, de ce que vous consultez (par ex. « aime le sport », « aime le rock classique ») et du moment ou de la fréquence de consultation ;
  2. Pour coordonner le contenu que nous ou d'autres vous proposons sur vos différents appareils, y compris à travers diverses plateformes mobiles et web, en réalisant des inférences anonymes à propos des liens entre appareils ;
  3. Pour mieux comprendre la manière dont le Service est utilisé et y apporter des améliorations, y compris pour créer et partager avec nos clients (et autres tierces parties connexes) des modèles cumulés et analytiques concernant la manière et le moment de l'accès au Contenu ainsi que la personne qui le consulte (par ex. si certaines publicités sont populaires à une heure donnée ou auprès d'un public particulier) ;
  4. Pour fournir des informations pertinentes à nos clients (et aux parties tierces connexes) concernant l'optimisation d'une campagne publicitaire en ligne ou mobile, le placement d'annonces ou les paramètres de fréquence (par ex. pour aider les publicitaires à comprendre si certaines publicités ont bien marché ou non et pourquoi, et le lien entre ces publicités et toute autre information connue à propos d'un utilisateur) ;
  5. Pour nous aider à assurer le bon fonctionnement du Service ;
  6. À d'autres fins de fourniture de publicités et de création de rapports anonymes n'apparaissant pas dans la liste ci-dessus ;
  7. À toute autre fin dont vous êtes informé(e) au moment de la collecte de vos informations..

**(c) Comment nous partageons les informations recueillies lorsque vous consultez le Contenu sponsorisé. Nous pourrons partager les informations recueillies en relation au Contenu sponsorisé comme suit :**

  1. Sociétés affiliées et partenaires. Nous pourrons partager vos Informations non personnelles avec nos sociétés affiliées – des sociétés qui nous contrôlent, sont contrôlées par nous ou sont placées sous le contrôle de la même personne que nous – ainsi que certains partenaires et prestataires de services nous aidant à proposer nos Services. Nous pourrons également partager ces informations avec des Éditeurs, des Annonceurs et d'autres prestataires de services tiers (tels que les plateformes de gestion des données et les réseaux publicitaires) aux fins de la prestation de nos Services. Ces entités peuvent, par exemple, utiliser vos informations pour faire, ou nous aider à faire, des prévisions quant à vos centres d'intérêt, et peuvent vous faire des offres et vous proposer un matériel promotionnel et des publicités.
  2. Prestataires de services. Nous pourrons partager tout type d'information (y compris les Informations personnelles que vous nous fournirez par l'intermédiaire de ce site, par exemple) avec les entités qui nous fournissent leurs services, y compris, sans limitation, des sociétés proposant des services de traitement des paiements, de support client et web, d'analyse web, de traitement des données, d'enrichissement des données et d'informations clients, de publicité et de diffusion par courrier électronique.
  3. Autres parties lorsque la loi l'exige ou dès que nécessaire pour veiller à la protection de nos Services. Nous pourrons partager vos informations (y compris vos Informations personnelles) avec d'autres parties aux fins suivantes :
    * pour protéger les droits légaux ou la propriété de Sharethrough, de nos sociétés affiliées et des sites ou services avec lesquels nous travaillons ;
    * pour protéger les droits, la sûreté et la sécurité de nos utilisateurs, de nous-mêmes ou de toute personne ou entité tierce ;
    * pour empêcher la fraude (ou à des fins de gestion des risques) ; ou
    * pour respecter la loi ou donner suite à un acte de procédure ou à une demande de coopération par une entité gouvernementale, que la loi nous y oblige ou non. Par exemple, lorsque cela est pertinent, il peut nous être demandé de communiquer vos informations à des tiers à des fins de respect des exigences de sécurité nationale ou de maintien de l'ordre.
  4. Autres parties en relation avec une cession d'actifs. Si nous vendons ou cédons nos actifs ou si nous prenons part à une fusion ou à une cession (ou dans le cadre de toute procédure de diligence raisonnable en lien avec une telle transaction), ou dans l'éventualité peu probable d'une faillite, nous pourrons transférer vos informations dans le cadre de cette transaction.
  5. Nous (ou toute plateforme tierce avec laquelle nous travaillons) pourrons associer vos Informations non personnelles aux Informations non personnelles d'autres personnes et partager ces informations agrégées sans restriction, y compris avec des Éditeurs et des Annonceurs, à des fins d'analyse, par exemple, ou pour les aider à en apprendre davantage sur leurs clients et utilisateurs et à mieux personnaliser et analyser les publicités, le contenu et les offres qu'ils envoient à leurs clients actuels et potentiels.

**4\. Cookies, balises web et autres technologies similaires**

Nous, ainsi que toute plateforme tierce de publicités ou de contenu avec laquelle nous travaillons, utilisons des cookies et autres technologies similaires sur le Site Sharethrough et lorsque vous interagissez avec nos services, notamment lorsque vous consultez ou cliquez sur un Contenu sponsorisé. Cette section contient de plus amples informations à propos de certaines de ces technologies et de leur fonctionnement.

Les cookies. Les cookies sont de petits fichiers texte utilisés par les sites et services en ligne pour stocker des informations à propos des utilisateurs sur les ordinateurs de ceux-ci. Par exemple, lorsque vous naviguez sur certains sites, les cookies peuvent être utilisés pour enregistrer vos coordonnées de connexion de sorte que vous n'ayez pas à les saisir à chaque nouvelle visite, ou pour stocker d'autres informations servant à personnaliser votre expérience de navigation en ligne ou à l'optimiser en vue de votre prochaine connexion. Les cookies peuvent également stocker un identifiant unique en relation avec votre ordinateur pour que les services et le contenu en ligne et les réseaux publicitaires puissent vous reconnaître lorsque vous naviguez sur différents sites. Vous pouvez configurer votre navigateur internet pour qu'il vous prévienne de l'enregistrement de chaque nouveau cookie ou de sorte qu'il refuse l'enregistrement de tous les cookies ou de certains types de cookies uniquement, mais cela nuira à la qualité de vos interactions avec certains sites web.

(b) Sharethrough (et toute plateforme tierce avec laquelle nous travaillons) peut utiliser ou prendre en charge les cookies aux fins suivantes :

  1. Pour recueillir des informations à propos de vos activités de navigation afin de vous fournir nos Services ;
  2. Pour établir un lien entre les informations recueillies grâce aux cookies et les informations que vous nous fournissez directement (par l'intermédiaire de ce site, par exemple) ou qui nous sont fournies par différentes sources commerciales ;
  3. Pour travailler avec des tiers qui nous aident à proposer un Contenu sponsorisé (à travers nos Services ou via Internet) ou nous fournissent d'autres services, comme la possibilité pour les utilisateurs de consulter ou de commenter un contenu ou de suivre les statistiques d'utilisation d'un site ;

Nous pouvons également utiliser les cookies (et les balises web, comme indiqué ci-dessous) à toutes les fins décrites dans la section ci-dessus intitulée « Comment nous utilisons les informations recueillies lorsque vous consultez un Contenu sponsorisé ». Nous (ou toute plateforme tierce avec laquelle nous travaillons) sommes également susceptibles d'utiliser les identifiants mobiles, comme les identifiants publicitaires Android ou les IDFA d'Apple, aux mêmes fins.

(c) Les balises web. Nous (ou toute plateforme tierce avec laquelle nous travaillons) sommes susceptibles d'utiliser des technologies appelées « balises web » transmettant des informations depuis votre navigateur Internet vers un serveur web. Les balises web peuvent être intégrées aux pages web, aux vidéos ou aux e-mails, et peuvent permettre à un serveur web de lire certains types d'informations depuis votre navigateur, de savoir si vous avez consulté une page web ou un e-mail spécifique et de déterminer, entre autres, l'heure et la date auxquelles vous avez vu la balise web, l'adresse IP de votre ordinateur et l'URL de la page web à partir de laquelle la balise web a été vue. Nous, ou nos partenaires, pourrons utiliser des balises web à diverses fins, y compris pour analyser l'utilisation des Services et, conjointement avec des cookies, pour vous fournir un contenu plus pertinent.

**5\. Procédures de confidentialité pour les Utilisateurs de ce site web**

**(a) Informations recueillies sur le site et leur utilisation :**

Le Site Sharethrough lui-même vise principalement les Éditeurs et les Annonceurs, mais nous accueillons tout Utilisateur souhaitant en savoir plus à propos de nos Services. Lorsque vous accédez à notre site ou à nos Services, nous sommes susceptibles de recueillir les informations suivantes :

  1. Informations personnelles. Lorsque vous créez un compte auprès de notre société (par exemple, pour vous inscrire en tant qu'Éditeur), nous pourrons vous demander et vous pourrez nous fournir certaines « Informations personnelles », c'est-à-dire des informations pouvant servir à identifier un individu spécifique sur la base de son identité personnelle. Ces informations peuvent comprendre votre nom, adresse postale, adresse e-mail ou numéro de téléphone et toute autre information considérée comme une Information personnelle. Nous recueillons vos Informations personnelles lorsque vous nous les communiquez sciemment – par exemple, lorsque vous vous inscrivez en tant qu'Éditeur ou Annonceur sur le Site Sharethrough, entrez en communication avec nous et/ou nous demandez des informations. Nous pouvons utiliser vos Informations personnelles pour gérer votre compte et vous fournir des services, vous envoyer des messages ainsi que des e-mails de nature administrative, en apprendre davantage à propos de nos utilisateurs et clients, répondre à vos demandes, vous envoyer des messages marketing et vous faire part de mises à jour concernant nos produits.
  2. Informations non personnelles. Que vous ouvriez un compte ou non ou que vous nous fournissiez des Informations personnelles ou non, nous pouvons recueillir d'autres Informations non personnelles lorsque vous naviguez sur notre site. Celles-ci peuvent comprendre les informations suivantes :
    1. Le type de navigateur et le système d'exploitation utilisés pour accéder au site web ;
    2. Votre adresse IP (qui est un numéro automatiquement attribué à votre ordinateur lorsque vous accédez à Internet et peut servir à déterminer votre emplacement géographique général) ;
    3. Les pages de notre site que vous avez consultées et sur lesquelles vous avez navigué et cliqué, et pendant combien de temps vous les avez consultées ; et
    4. Toute autre information que vous nous soumettez.

Nous pouvons recueillir et stocker les informations susmentionnées à l'aide de cookies, de balises web et d'autres technologies similaires, et pouvons cibler ou redéfinir le ciblage de ces publicités à l'aide de ces cookies, d'identificateurs d'appareil ou d'autres technologies similaires, lorsque vous naviguez sur Internet ou utilisez votre appareil mobile.

**(b) Accès et contrôle de l'utilisation que nous faisons de vos Informations :**

Nous respectons le droit d'accès de chacun à ses données personnelles. Si vous nous fournissez des Informations personnelles lors de votre inscription sur notre site, sachez que vous pouvez modifier ces informations à tout moment en accédant aux paramètres de votre compte. Même si nous serions déçus que vous nous quittiez, vous pouvez supprimer votre compte à tout moment en écrivant à support@Sharethrough.com. Toutefois, n'oubliez pas que, si vous supprimez votre compte, nous pourrons conserver vos informations à des fins de respect des exigences légales en vigueur, de prévention de la fraude, de résolution de litiges et problèmes, de fourniture d'assistance dans le cas d'une enquête et d'application de nos conditions d'utilisation. Nous pourrons prendre toute autre mesure permise par la loi, et la suppression d'un compte ne signifie pas que les informations recueillies en relation avec nos Services ont été supprimées. Après qu'un compte est supprimé, il est possible que certaines informations résiduelles restent dans nos bases de données, registres d'accès et autres archives. En outre, nous ne sommes pas responsables de la mise à jour ni de la suppression de vos informations déjà communiquées à des tiers en accord avec la présente Politique. De surcroît, vous pouvez refuser de recevoir certaines communications électroniques en cliquant sur le lien de « désinscription » qui se trouve en bas de chaque e-mail. Sachez que si vous vous désinscrivez ou retirez votre nom de notre liste de diffusion, nous pourrons toutefois continuer à vous envoyer des messages en relation avec votre utilisation du Service. Pour de plus amples informations sur les options qui s'offrent à vous, veuillez consulter la section « Utilisateurs internationaux » ci-dessous. 

**6\. AUTRES CONDITIONS**

**(a) Sécurité, conservation et intégrité des données**

Nous prenons des mesures de sécurité pour protéger vos données contre un accès, une modification, une diffusion ou une destruction non autorisée. Toutefois, aucun dispositif de sécurité n'est infaillible et nous ne pouvons pas vous certifier que les mesures de sécurité que nous prenons ne seront pas corrompues ou compromises ni que vos données demeureront en sécurité en toutes circonstances.

**(b) Les enfants**

Nous ne recueillons ni ne conservons intentionnellement aucune Information personnelle provenant d'enfants âgés de moins de 13 ans, et aucune partie de notre site ou de nos Services n'est conçue pour attirer les enfants âgés de moins de 13 ans. Nous avons à cœur de protéger la vie privée des enfants, et si nous venons à apprendre que l'un de nos utilisateurs est âgé de moins de 13 ans, nous prendrons les mesures raisonnables nécessaires pour supprimer de nos bases de données les Informations personnelles de cet utilisateur.

**(c) Liens vers d'autres sites web**

Bien que nous puissions publier un lien vers un autre site web ou service à travers ce site, ou autoriser d'autres personnes à y partager un contenu, ceci ne garantit pas, ni n'autorise, ni n'affirme notre affiliation à cette tierce partie, ni ne signifie que nous approuvons ou reconnaissons les procédures de confidentialité de celle-ci. D'autres sites web et services respectent des règles différentes en matière d'utilisation ou de communication des Informations personnelles. Nous vous conseillons vivement de lire les politiques et déclarations de confidentialité des autres sites web que vous visitez.

**(d) Utilisateurs internationaux**

Le Site web et nos Services sont hébergés aux États-Unis et ailleurs dans le monde. En accédant au Site web ou à nos Services, vous consentez au transfert de vos informations vers les États-Unis et d'autres pays. Les lois en matière de traitement des informations des États-Unis ou d'autres pays peuvent être moins strictes que celles en place dans votre pays.

Sharethrough respecte les principes du Bouclier de protection des données UE-États-Unis établis par le ministère du Commerce en ce qui concerne la collecte, l'utilisation et le stockage des informations personnelles en provenance des pays membres de l'Union européenne et du Royaume-Uni. Sharethrough certifie respecter les principes de notification, de choix, de responsabilité en cas de transfert ultérieur, de sécurité, d'intégrité des données, de limitation des finalités, d'accès, de voies de recours, d'application et de responsabilité. En cas de conflit entre les politiques énoncées dans la présente politique de confidentialité et les principes du bouclier de protection des données, les principes du bouclier de protection des données prévaudront. Pour en savoir plus à propos du bouclier de protection des données et pour consulter notre page de certification, rendez-vous sur https://www.privacyshield.gov/list. 

Sharethrough peut être tenu responsable du bon transfert des données personnelles des individus de l'UE ou du Royaume-Uni auprès de tierces parties.

S'ils veulent porter plainte, les résidents de tout pays, y compris les pays ayant accepté de se conformer aux principes du bouclier de protection des données, peuvent nous contacter de la manière indiquée à la fin de la présente Politique. Sharethrough s'engage en outre à référer les plaintes de confidentialité non résolues en vertu des principes du bouclier de protection des données au BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, un fournisseur à but non lucratif de services axés sur le mode alternatif de résolution des conflits situé aux États-Unis et régi par le Council of Better Business Bureaus. Si vous ne recevez pas d'accusé de réception en temps opportun de la part de Sharethrough, ou si votre plainte n'est pas résolue de façon satisfaisante par Sharethrough, consultez www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/ pour de plus amples informations et pour déposer plainte. Enfin, et en dernier recours, les résidents de l'UE ou du Royaume-Uni dont la plainte en matière de confidentialité n'a pas été résolue peuvent faire appel auprès du panel du bouclier de protection des données (« Privacy Shield Panel »), un mécanisme de règlement des litiges pouvant prendre des décisions contraignantes.

Sharethrough est soumis aux pouvoirs d'enquête et d'exécution de la Federal Trade Commission.

Les résidents de certains pays hors des États-Unis (y compris tous les individus dont les informations sont recueillies par nous-mêmes en vertu du bouclier de protection des données) disposent de droits juridiques d'accès à certaines informations que nous détenons à leur propos et peuvent demander leur rectification, modification ou suppression (en sus des options décrites dans la section ci-dessus intitulée « Accès et contrôle de l'utilisation que nous faisons de vos Informations »). Pour exercer ces droits, ils peuvent nous contacter selon les modalités décrites ci-dessous.

**(e) Modifications de la présente Politique de confidentialité**

La présente politique est susceptible d'être modifiée à tout moment, auquel cas nous publierons de nouvelles conditions qui entreront en vigueur après un délai raisonnable.

**7\. LE RÈGLEMENT GÉNÉRAL SUR LA PROTECTION DES DONNÉES (RGPD) DE L'UE**

Le 25 mai 2018, une nouvelle loi sur la confidentialité des données, le Règlement général sur la protection des données (RGPD) de l'Union européenne, prendra effet dans les pays de l'EEE et en Suisse. En vertu du RGDP, Sharethrough et ceux qui utilisent nos services doivent fournir aux utilisateurs certaines informations concernant le traitement de leurs données personnelles. En Europe, l'expression « données personnelles » fait référence aux données qui permettent d'identifier ou sont susceptibles de permettre d'identifier un utilisateur ou un appareil unique spécifique. Il peut s'agir d'un nom, d'une adresse, de témoins de connexion ou cookies, d'un appareil mobile, de données de localisation précises ou de données biométriques.

Afin de respecter le RGPD, nous mettons à disposition des utilisateurs les déclarations et informations ci-après. Celles-ci sont spécifiques aux résidents de l'EEE ou de la Suisse. Si vous ne résidez pas dans l'un de ces pays, ces informations ne vous concernent pas.

**a. Base juridique du traitement de vos données personnelles**

Le RGPD nous contraint à vous informer de la base juridique en vertu de laquelle nous traitons vos données personnelles.  La base juridique du traitement de vos données personnelles aux fins visées dans les Sections 3 et 4 ci-dessus (et la Section 5 eu égard aux données de nos sociétés clientes) repose sur les principes suivants :

  * _Vous avez donné votre consentement._ Pour stocker des informations sur votre appareil et/ou accéder aux informations qui s'y trouvent, votre consentement est nécessaire. Aux fins de ce « consentement par cookie » (qui s'applique non seulement aux cookies, mais également aux identifiants publicitaires mobiles), nos partenaires de connexion web et mobile et nous-mêmes avons mis en place des mesures de mise en conformité afin de nous assurer que votre consentement est recueilli et communiqué aux partenaires et que nous ne facilitons que la collecte de données obtenues en conformité avec la loi. Nous procédons ainsi afin de nous acquitter de nos obligations en vertu de la directive relative à la vie privée et aux communications électroniques. Nous pouvons également décider d'obtenir votre consentement dans d'autres situations, auquel cas nous respecterons les lois applicables en relation à ce consentement et à son retrait.
  * _Le traitement sert nos intérêts légitimes._ Dans certains cas, un intérêt légitime constitue la base juridique du traitement des données personnelles aux fins de la prestation de services auprès de nos contrôleurs de données et/ou d'autres contrôleurs de données. Un tel traitement va au-delà de la collecte originelle des identifiants publicitaires mobiles. Par exemple, la personnalisation des communications promotionnelles soumises aux utilisateurs de services web et en ligne constitue l'un des intérêts légitimes sur lesquels nous nous appuyons. Un tel service est utile aux utilisateurs et constitue également une partie intégrante de l'écosystème qui permet le financement de contenu disponible gratuitement grâce aux revenus tirés de la publicité. Ce service inclut parfois l'analyse et l'élaboration de rapports sur les campagnes publicitaires.
  * Nous nous appuyons également sur un intérêt légitime lorsque nous utilisons les données personnelles pour veiller à la sécurité de nos services, comme la détection de tentatives de fraude ou de bogues afin de les solutionner.
  * _Relations contractuelles._ Il nous arrive de traiter certaines données en vertu de relations contractuelles (comme les dossiers et les coordonnées de nos clients).
  * _Obligations juridiques._ Enfin, nous pouvons être contraints de traiter certaines données pour respecter nos obligations juridiques ou réglementaires.

**b. Transfert de données personnelles**

Sharethrough travaillant avec des sociétés et des technologies à portée mondiale, nous pouvons avoir besoin de transférer vos données personnelles en dehors du pays où vous les avez soumises. Par exemple, nous pouvons transférer vos données à des collaborateurs tiers qui peuvent être basés dans une juridiction en dehors de l'EEE ou de la Suisse et qui ne bénéficient d'aucune loi de protection des données ou dont les lois sont moins sévères que les lois européennes.

Lorsque nous transférons des données personnelles hors de l'EEE ou de la Suisse, nous nous assurons que nous disposons des mécanismes de protection appropriés pour protéger vos données personnelles. Par exemple, tel que décrit à la Section 6(d), Sharethrough ayant reçu une certification de conformité aux principes du bouclier de protection des données, nous nous engageons à protéger les données personnelles en provenance de l'EEE et de la Suisse conformément aux principes de confidentialité des données en vigueur. Pour plus d'informations à ce sujet, veuillez vous référer à la Section 11.  N'hésitez pas à nous contacter aux coordonnées précisées ci-dessous si vous souhaitez obtenir davantage d'informations sur les mécanismes de protection que nous avons mis en place pour protéger vos données personnelles et vos droits relatifs à la confidentialité dans de telles circonstances.

**c. Conservation des données personnelles**

De façon générale, nous conservons vos données personnelles aussi longtemps que nécessaire à des fins de prestation de nos services ou à toute autre fin utile, notamment de conformité à la loi, de résolution des litiges et d'exécution de nos accords. Généralement, nous désactivons nos propres identifiants (p. ex. ceux que nous utilisons pour « synchroniser » nos données clients avec les clients en ligne) après **[13 mois]** , à condition que nous puissions les conserver s'il existe un besoin juridique ou opérationnel impérieux de le faire, notamment d'audit, de tenue de registre d'entreprise, de conformité, de sécurité et de prévention des bogues.

**d. Vos droits en tant que personne concernée**

Le RGPD vous accorde certains droits quant aux données personnelles que les contrôleurs de données détiennent à votre propos, y compris certains droits d'accès aux données personnelles. Vous pouvez notamment demander la modification, la restriction ou la suppression de vos données personnelles, et vous pouvez vous opposer au traitement de vos données personnelles par nos soins (y compris le profilage à des fins de ciblage publicitaire en ligne).

  * _Droit d'accès._ Si vous souhaitez faire valoir votre droit d'accès aux données personnelles que nous traitons en notre qualité de contrôleur des données, vous pouvez le faire en écrivant à l'adresse suivante : [support@sharethrough.com](mailto:support@sharethrough.com).. Après réception de votre demande, nous vous enverrons des instructions précises qui vous permettront d'accéder à vos données personnelles. Étant donné que nous sommes dans l'obligation de vérifier l'identité des personnes qui nous soumettent une demande avant de leur communiquer des données personnelles, nous évaluerons chaque demande d'accès aux données de façon indépendante. À cette fin, nous tiendrons compte de (a) la difficulté de vérifier si les données que nous détenons et les données y afférentes appartiennent véritablement et uniquement à la personne concernée qui est l'auteur de la demande, ainsi que du (b) possible impact négatif de la divulgation de données personnelles à la mauvaise personne. Comme la divulgation indue de données personnelles aurait probablement une incidence défavorable sur le droit à la confidentialité et les libertés de la personne concernée, nous nous réservons le droit de limiter les données personnelles que nous acceptons de communiquer.
  * Nous ne répondrons qu'aux seules demandes soumises par e-mail et pour lesquelles nous sommes un contrôleur des données, comme précisé ci-après. Lorsque nous agissons en tant que contrôleur des données pour l'un de nos clients, nous soumettrons votre demande à ce client. Afin de faciliter le traitement de votre demande, veuillez identifier le client à laquelle votre demande fait référence (dans la mesure du possible).

_Droit de modification._ Si vous souhaitez faire valoir votre droit de modification aux données personnelles, vous pouvez le faire en nous contactant aux coordonnées ci-après.

_Droit d'opposition au traitement des données personnelles ou droit de retrait de consentement._ En utilisant un cookie de désinscription via votre navigateur et en choisissant de vous désinscrire du ciblage Sharethrough comme indiqué à la Section 2 de la présente Politique de confidentialité, vous retirez le consentement de traitement de vos données personnelles sur lequel nous nous appuyons. Dans ce cas, nous cesserons de traiter vos données personnelles aux fins de nos services sous 30 jours.

Nous recueillons nous-mêmes vos choix ou nos applications mobiles partenaires nous les font parvenir.

  * Droit de suppression. Vous avez aussi le droit d'exiger la suppression des données personnelles que nous détenons à votre sujet en notre qualité de contrôleur des données. Le processus susmentionné permet de satisfaire à ce droit. Quand un utilisateur se désabonne par l'intermédiaire de nos partenaires (ou via les paramètres d'un appareil mobile), et que nous recevons ce signal, nous n'utilisons plus vos données personnelles pour vous fournir des services publicitaires. Si vous en faites la demande, nous pouvons également supprimer manuellement vos données personnelles ; à cette fin, veuillez nous contacter à support@sharethrough.com. Toutefois, sachez que nous sommes susceptibles de conserver des copies de certaines données personnelles sur des fichiers inactifs ou de sauvegarde, afin de satisfaire à des processus internes et nécessaires, notamment d'audit, de tenue des comptes et de facturation, de conformité à la loi et de détection des bogues. Dans la plupart des cas, nous supprimerons ces données sous 36 mois, sauf s'il existe un motif impérieux à leur conservation.
  * _Droit de porter plainte._ Vous avez le droit de déposer une plainte auprès d'une autorité de surveillance. Toutefois, nous espérons que vous vous adresserez d'abord à nous afin de nous donner la possibilité de résoudre votre plainte ou de répondre à vos attentes.

**e. Sharethrough en tant que contrôleur des données et responsable du traitement des données**

La loi européenne de protection des données opère une distinction entre les organisations qui traitent les données personnelles à des fins personnelles (les « contrôleurs des données ») et les organisations qui traitent les données personnelles au nom d'autres organisations (les « responsables du traitement des données »). Comme nous l'avons déjà indiqué, nous n'agissons pas toujours en qualité de contrôleur des données qui sont en notre possession, mais nous agissons parfois en tant que responsable du traitement des données pour d'autres sociétés, notamment nos clients. Dans de tels cas, nous pouvons rediriger votre demande vers le contrôleur des données pertinent, étant donné que les contrôleurs des données sont généralement responsables des données personnelles.

**8\. Application, questions et plaintes**

Si vous avez des questions ou inquiétudes à propos de la présente Politique de confidentialité ou de nos procédures de confidentialité, ou si vous souhaitez exercer vos droits, écrivez-nous à [privacy@sharethrough.com](mailto:privacy@sharethrough.com)ou à l'adresse ci-dessous :

Sharethrough, Inc.  
À l'attention de : Privacy Inquiries   
170 Columbus Ave, Suite 280  
San Francisco, CA 94133, États-Unis

Dernière mise à jour : mai 2018

**Datenschutzrichtlinie von Sharethrough**

Diese Inhalte werden Ihnen präsentiert von [Sharethrough](http://sharethrough.com/), der All-in-One-Native-Advertising-Anwendung für Herausgeber, App-Entwickler und Werbetreibende, und wurden vom angezeigten Werbetreibenden oder Vermarkter bezahlt. Lesen Sie unsere Datenschutzrichtlinie, um mehr darüber zu erfahren, wie wir Daten nutzen, um unsere Anwendung zu betreiben und Inhalte bereitzustellen, und wie Sie zielgerichtete Werbung vieler Unternehmen, die mithilfe unserer Anwendung interessenbasierte Werbung bereitstellen, oder andere Inhalte, Websites und Anwendungen deaktivieren können.

* * *

## Datenschutzrichtlinie

Willkommen bei Sharethrough.com, einer Website von Sharethrough, Inc. („Sharethrough“, „wir“, „uns“ oder „unser“). Wir betreiben eine Plattform, über die Websites, Entwickler mobiler Anwendungen oder „Apps“ und ähnliche Plattformen im Namen unserer Werbepartner Inhalte (die „Werbeinhalte“) anzeigen können. Diese von uns angezeigten Inhalte tragen den Hinweis „Werbung“ oder eine ähnliche Bezeichnung, die sie als bezahlte oder gesponserte Inhalte kennzeichnen. Möglicherweise sind Sie über ein Symbol neben unseren beworbenen Inhalten auf die Seite dieser Richtlinie gelangt.

Sharethrough unterstützt Websites, mobile Apps und Web-Services bei der Bereitstellung ansprechender, relevanter Inhalten von Drittanbietern für ihre Nutzer und unterstützt demnach häufig deren kostenlose Inhalte und Medien. Hierfür behalten wir uns vor, die anonymisierten Daten solcher Websites und Apps sowie die anonymisierten Daten der Nutzer dieser Websites und Apps zu erfassen und zu nutzen.

Mit dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie informieren wir Sie darüber, welche Daten wir erfassen, wenn Sie sich die Werbeinhalte ansehen oder diese Website besuchen, und zu welchen Zwecken wir diese Daten nutzen, weitergeben und schützen. Wir legen Wert auf die Privatsphäre der Nutzer und auf Transparenz.

**1\. Geltungsbereich**

Diese Datenschutzrichtlinie gilt für die Website [www.sharethrough.com](http://sharethrough.com/) (nachfolgend „Sharethrough-Website“), die Tools und interaktiven Foren, die durch die Sharethrough-Website und die Plattform zur Auslieferung von Werbeinhalten (nachfolgend „Dienste“) zur Verfügung gestellt werden. Hierunter fallen auch die auf Websites und mobilen Anwendungen angebotenen Werbeinhalte.

Im Allgemeinen lassen sich die Nutzer der Sharethrough-Website und -Dienste in drei Kategorien unterteilen: „Herausgeber“, die Betreiber oder Herausgeber von Websites oder Apps sind, auf denen die Werbeinhalte angezeigt werden; „Werbetreibende“, die ihre Inhalte auf unserer Plattform anzeigen; und „Nutzer“, also Privatpersonen, die Websites oder Apps von Herausgebern nutzen. Durch den Besuch der Sharethrough-Website oder die Nutzung der Dienstleistungen akzeptieren Sie die in dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie beschriebenen Richtlinien und Praktiken.

Diese Datenschutzrichtlinie regelt zwei verschiedene Datenschutzpraktiken:

  * Datenschutzpraktiken für Nutzer der Dienste und Werbehinhalte von Sharethrough
  * Datenschutzpraktiken für Nutzer dieser Website (siehe Abschnitt 5)

**2\. Wahlmöglichkeiten und Opt-out-Tools für Inhalte der Sharethrough-Dienste**

Wir sind davon überzeugt, dass die Bereitstellung gezielter, relevanter Inhalte Ihre Erfahrung bei der Nutzung des Internets und mobiler Geräte verbessert und freie Medien sowie andere beliebte Inhalte fördert. Wie in dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie des Weiteren beschrieben, erfassen wir (oder unsere Partner) anonymisierte, nicht-personenbezogene Daten zu Ihren Aktivitäten im Internet oder auf mobilen Geräten (wie in Abschnitt 3 beschrieben). Unter „nicht-personenbezogenen Daten“ verstehen wir Informationen, die nur an einen Browser oder ein Gerät gekoppelt sind, ohne dass darin Name, Adresse, Telefonnummer, E-Mail-Adresse oder andere, öffentliche Identifikatoren (z. B. die Sozialversicherungsnummer) des Nutzers enthalten sind. Anhand dieser Informationen stellen wir und diese Browser bzw. Gräte relevantere, ansprechendere und weniger störende Inhalte bereit – um zum Beispiel zu verhindern, dass dieselben Inhalte wiederholt angezeigt werden oder diese für Sie überhaupt nicht relevant sind. 

Falls Sie nicht wünschen, dass wir oder Drittplattformen diese Informationen über Ihre Aktivitäten im Internet oder auf mobilen Geräten erfassen, um Ihnen gezielte Werbeinhalte anzuzeigen, können Sie die Dienste von vielen Online-Plattformen, die gezielte Werbeinhalte bereitstellen, deaktivieren. Um Plattformen, die möglicherweise Werbung oder Inhalte auf Sie abstimmen und mit denen wir gelegentlich zusammenarbeiten, zu deaktivieren oder mehr über sie zu erfahren, besuchen Sie bitte die von der [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) und der [ >Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/) Bitte beachten Sie, dass diese Opt-out-Tools Cookies verwenden. Sollten Sie Cookies blockieren, löschen, ändern oder eine neuere Version Ihres Browsers installieren, müssen Sie die betreffenden Dienste erneut deaktivieren. In Ihren Geräteeinstellungen können Sie außerdem den Empfang von Werbung auf mobilen Geräten auf Grundlage der Erfassung mobiler Kennungen (wie z. B. IDFA oder Android-Ad-ID) ablehnen.

In Ihren Geräteeinstellungen können Sie außerdem den Empfang von Werbung auf mobilen Geräten auf Grundlage der Erfassung mobiler Kennungen (wie z. B. IDFA oder Android-Ad-ID) ablehnen. Um beispielsweise Ihre bevorzugten Anzeigeneinstellungen in iOS einzurichten, gehen Sie auf Einstellungen > Datenschutz > Werbung > Kein Ad-Tracking. Um Ihre bevorzugten Anzeigeneinstellungen in Android einzurichten gehen Sie auf Einstellungen > Google > Anzeigen > Personalisierte Werbung deaktivieren.  (Die exakte Formulierung kann auf bestimmten oder älteren Geräten abweichen.) Wir erfassen diese Opt-out-Signale entweder selbst oder erhalten diese über die Apps für Mobilgeräte, mit denen wir arbeiten.

**3\. Datenschutzpraktiken für Endnutzer, die Inhalte erhalten und sehen: Die von uns erfassten Daten und wie wir sie nutzen und weitergeben.**

Ein wesentlicher Bestandteil des Dienstes ist die Sharethrough-Plattform, die App-Entwickler und Website-Betreiber dabei unterstützt, ihren Nutzern relevantere Inhalte Dritter bereitzustellen. Da Sie diese Richtlinie lesen, sind Sie vermutlich mit der Art und Weise vertraut, wie Sharethrough Werbetreibende dabei unterstützt, Werbeinhalte auf Websites und mobilen Apps anzuzeigen. Wenn Sie (im Internet oder auf mobilen Geräten) Werbeinhalte ansehen oder anklicken, erfassen wir automatisch bestimmte nicht-personenbezogene Daten, die wir auf unserer Plattform nutzen. Wir behalten uns vor, Herausgebern die Nutzung aller oder einiger dieser Daten durch die Plattform zu Analysezwecken zu gestatten. Außerdem nutzen wir die Daten (in Zusammenarbeit mit Drittplattformen), um Werbeinhalte wie unten beschrieben auf Sie abzustimmen.

**(a) Die Daten, die wir erfassen, wenn Sie sich Werbeinhalte ansehen**

Wenn Sie auf Werbeinhalte klicken und sich diese ansehen, werden bestimmte, nicht-personenbezogene Daten über Sie durch uns oder eine Drittplattform, mit der wir zusammenarbeiten, erfasst. Unter „nicht-personenbezogenen Daten“ verstehen wir Daten, anhand derer Sie grundsätzlich nicht persönlich identifiziert werden können (im Gegensatz zu Daten wie Name/Adresse, Telefonnummer oder sogar die E-Mail-Adresse). Wenn Sie sich die Werbeinhalte mit einem mobilen Gerät ansehen, können die folgenden Daten von uns erfasst, aufbewahrt und genutzt: 

  1. Eine Gerätekennung, wie z. B. eine Apple IDFA oder eine Android Advertising ID;
  2. Ihre IP-Adresse (hierbei handelt es sich um eine Nummer, die Ihrem Computer automatisch zugewiesen wird, wenn Sie auf das Internet zugreifen, und mit der Ihr allgemeiner geografischer Standort ermittelt werden kann);
  3. Die Anwendung, mit der Ihr Gerät mit Sharethrough-Inhalten interagiert und einen Zeitstempel zu Ihrer Interaktion;
  4. Daten zu Ihrem Gerät und Betriebssystem;
  5. Weitere Informationen, die Sie freiwillig an uns übermitteln.

Wenn Sie sich die Werbeinhalte mit einem Webbrowser oder mobilen Browser ansehen, können wir oder die Plattform eines Dritten, mit dem wir zusammenarbeiten, unter Umständen die folgenden Daten erfassen, aufbewahren und nutzen:

  1. Den Typ des Browsers und des Betriebssystems, mit denen Sie auf die Website zugegriffen haben;
  2. Ihre IP-Adresse (hierbei handelt es sich um eine Nummer, die Ihrem Computer automatisch zugewiesen wird, wenn Sie auf das Internet zugreifen, und mit der Ihr allgemeiner Standort ermittelt werden kann);
  3. Daten, die Ihr Browser preisgibt, wenn Sie die Werbeinhalte anzeigen oder öffnen, einschließlich der Website, die Sie vor dem Anklicken und Anzeigen der Werbeinhalte besucht haben, sowie Systemzeit, User Agent String, Click-Stream-Daten, Browsertyp, Browsersprache, Datum und Uhrzeit bei Anzeigen der Werbeinhalte. Wir können diese Informationen mithilfe von Cookies, Webbeacons oder ähnlichen Technologien erfassen bzw. speichern. Mehr über diese Online-Technologien erfahren Sie weiter unten in Abschnitt 4;
  4. Weitere Informationen, die Sie freiwillig an uns übermitteln.

**(b) So nutzen wir die Daten, die wir erfassen, wenn Sie sich Werbeinhalte ansehen.**

Wir behalten uns die Nutzung der aufgeführten Daten (oder die Zusammenarbeit mit Werbe- und Content-Plattformen Dritter, die diese Daten nutzen) zu den nachfolgend genannten Zwecken vor, unter anderem durch die Verwendung von Cookies und Gerätekennungen (nähere Informationen hierzu finden Sie in Abschnitt 4).Im Allgemeinen ermöglichen wir Werbe- und Content-Plattformen Dritter diese Zwecke zu erfüllen, indem sie die Kennungen der Herausgeber mit den Kennungen der Plattformen „abgleichen“. Dadurch können diese Plattformen gezielt relevante Anzeigen an Verbraucher senden (oftmals auf Grundlage anderer Informationen, die diese Plattformen erfasst haben:

  1. Für die Zusammenstellung maßgeschneiderter Inhalte, die wir (oder Dritte, darunter Werbetreibende und Inhaltsanbieter) Ihnen anzeigen, einschließlich der Erstellung relevanter Datensegmente auf der Grundlage der von Ihnen besuchten Websites (z. B. „mag Sport“, „mag Classic Rock“) sowie der Zugriffszeit und -häufigkeit;
  2. Zur Koordination der Inhalte, die wir oder Andere Ihnen auf Ihren Geräten anzeigen, einschließlich auf mobilen und webbasierten Plattformen; dies geschieht mittels anonymer Rückschlüsse auf die Geräteverlinkung.
  3. Zum besseren Verständnis der Nutzung sowie zur Verbesserung des Dienstes, einschließlich der Erzeugung aggregierter und analytischer Modelle und deren Austausch mit unseren Kunden (und relevanten Dritten) in Bezug auf die Fragen, wie, wann und von wem die Inhalte angesehen werden – zum Beispiel, ob bestimmte Werbung öfter zu bestimmen Zeiten und von einer bestimmten Zielgruppe angesehen wird;
  4. Um unseren Kunden (und relevanten Dritten) Einblicke in Bezug auf die Optimierung von Werbekampagnen für Websites und mobile Geräte sowie die Platzierung von Werbung und Kennzahlen zur Häufigkeit bereitzustellen – damit Werbetreibende beispielsweise verstehen, ob und warum bestimmte Werbeanzeigen erfolgreich waren und warum nicht und inwiefern diese Werbeanzeigen mit anderen, über einen Nutzer bekannten Daten im Zusammenhang stehen;
  5. Um dafür zu sorgen, dass der Dienst richtig funktioniert;
  6. Zu weiteren Zwecken der anonymen Bereitstellung von und Berichterstattung über Werbung, die oben nicht spezifisch aufgeführt wurden;
  7. Zu allen weiteren Zwecken, die Ihnen zum Zeitpunkt der Datenerfassung mitgeteilt wurden.

**(c) Wie wir die Daten weitergeben, die wir erfassen, wenn Sie sich Werbeinhalte ansehen. Wir geben die im Zusammenhang der Werbeinhalte erfassten Daten wie folgt weiter:**

  1. Tochterunternehmen und Partner. Wir geben Ihre nicht-personenbezogenen Daten an unsere Tochterunternehmen – Unternehmen, die uns kontrollieren oder von uns kontrolliert werden oder mit uns unter gemeinsamer Kontrolle stehen – sowie an ausgewählte Partner und Dienstleister weiter, die uns dabei helfen, unsere Dienste anzubieten. Wir geben diese Daten im Rahmen der Bereitstellung unserer Dienste auch an Herausgeber, Werbetreibende und andere Drittanbieter (wie z. B. Datenmanagementplattformen und Werbenetzwerke) weiter. Diese nutzen Ihre Informationen zum Beispiel zum Erstellen von Prognosen Ihrer Interessen und können Ihnen Angebote und Werbematerial zukommen lassen.
  2. Dienstleister. Wir tauschen beliebige Daten (einschließlich personenbezogener Daten, die Sie uns z. B. über diese Website bereitgestellt haben) eventuell mit Körperschaften aus, die uns Dienstleistungen bereitstellen, einschließlich Unternehmen, die Zahlungsabwicklung, Kunden- und Websupport, Web-Analytik, Datenverarbeitung, Datenaufbereitung/Kundeneinblicke, Werbung, E-Mail-Versand und sonstige Dienstleistungen bereitstellen.
  3. Sonstige Parteien, falls dies gesetzlich vorgeschrieben oder für den Schutz unserer Dienstleistungen erforderlich ist. Wir können Ihre Daten (einschließlich personenbezogene Daten) aus folgenden Gründen gegenüber sonstigen Parteien offenlegen:
    * Zum Schutz der Rechtsansprüche oder des Eigentums von Sharethrough, unserer Tochterunternehmen sowie der Websites oder Dienste, mit denen wir zusammenarbeiten;
    * Zum Schutz der Rechte und Sicherheit unserer Nutzer, von uns selbst oder anderen Personen oder Körperschaften;
    * Zum Verhindern von Betrug (oder zu Zwecken des Risikomanagements) oder
    * Zur Einhaltung der geltenden Gesetze oder als Reaktion auf rechtliche Verfahren oder Anträge auf Zusammenarbeit seitens einer Regierungsbehörde, unabhängig davon, ob dies gesetzlich erforderlich ist oder nicht. Zum Beispiel kann es sein, dass wir gegebenenfalls dazu verpflichtet sind, aus Gründen der nationalen Sicherheit oder der Strafverfolgung Ihre Daten preiszugeben.
  4. Sonstige Parteien im Zusammenhang mit Vermögensübertragungen. Falls es zu einer Veräußerung oder Übertragung von Vermögenswerten kommt oder Sharethrough anderweitig an Fusionen oder Übertragungen (oder an einer mit einer solchen Transaktion im Zusammenhang stehenden Unternehmensprüfung) beteiligt ist oder im unwahrscheinlichen Falle einer Zahlungsunfähigkeit kann es sein, dass wir Ihre Daten ebenfalls übertragen.
  5. Ihre nicht-personenbezogenen Daten können von uns (oder einer Drittplattform, mit der wir zusammenarbeiten) mit den nicht-personenbezogenen Daten Anderer zusammengefasst und ohne Einschränkung z. B. an Herausgeber und Werbetreibende weitergegeben werden, wie z. B. zu Analysezwecken, oder um ihnen zu ermöglichen, genauere Informationen über ihre Kunden und Nutzer bereitzustellen und Werbung, Inhalte und Angebote für bestehende und potenzielle Kunden relevanter und die Werbewirkung besser messbar zu machen.

**4\. Cookies, Webbeacons und ähnliche Technologien**

Auf der Sharethrough-Website sowie bei der Nutzung unserer Dienste, wenn Sie also z. B. auf Werbeinhalte klicken, können Cookies und ähnliche Technologien zum Einsatz kommen, die von uns oder von Werbe- und Content-Plattformen, mit denen wir zusammenarbeiten, verwendet werden. Dieser Abschnitt enthält weitere Informationen über einige dieser Technologien und ihrer Funktionsweisen.

(a) Cookies. Cookies sind kleine Textdateien, mit denen Websites und andere Online-Dienste Informationen über Nutzer auf den Computern der Nutzer speichern. Falls Sie zum Beispiel bestimmte Websites nutzen, können mithilfe von Cookies Anmeldedaten gespeichert werden, damit Sie sie nicht jedes Mal wieder eingeben müssen, wenn Sie zu diesen Websites zurückkehren. Außerdem können andere Informationen gespeichert werden, um die angezeigten Inhalte auf Sie abzustimmen oder bei zukünftigen Besuchen effizienter zu gestalten. In Cookies können außerdem Kennungen gespeichert werden, die mit Ihrem Computer verbunden sind, sodass Sie bei Besuchen auf unterschiedlichen Websites von Webdiensten, Inhalten und Werbenetzen erkannt werden können. Sie können Ihren Internet-Browser so konfigurieren, dass Sie gewarnt werden, sobald ein Cookie versendet wird, oder dass alle oder bestimmte Cookies von vornherein abgelehnt werden. Die hat wahrscheinlich zur Folge, dass Sie manche Websites nicht in vollem Umfang nutzen können.

(b) Cookies können von Sharethrough (und Drittplattformen, mit denen wir zusammenarbeiten) wie folgt genutzt werden:

  1. Zur Erfassung von Daten über Ihre Browser-Aktivitäten, um seine Dienste bereitzustellen;
  2. Zum Verknüpfen der durch Cookies erfassten Daten mit Daten, die wir von Ihnen direkt (wie z. B. über diese Website) oder über kommerziell verfügbare Quellen erhalten haben;
  3. Zur Zusammenarbeit mit Dritten, die uns dabei unterstützen, Werbeinhalte (durch unsere Dienste oder über das Internet) zu liefern, oder uns andere Dienste bereitstellen, wie z. B. das Ermöglichen des Anzeigens oder Kommentierens von Inhalten durch Nutzer oder das Erstellen von Statistiken der Website-Nutzung;

Darüber hinaus können wir Cookies (und Webbeacons, siehe unten) zu allen im obigen Abschnitt[ „So nutzen wir die Daten, die wir erfassen, wenn Sie sich Werbeinhalte ansehen“](https://platform-cdn.sharethrough.com/privacy-policy#how-we-use-information-en) beschriebenen Zwecken nutzen. Auch mobile Kennungen, wie z. B. Apple-IDFAs und Android-Advertising-IDs, können von uns (oder Drittplattformen, mit denen wir zusammenarbeiten) zu ebendiesen Zwecken genutzt werden.

(c) Webbeacons. Wir (oder Drittplattformen, mit denen wir zusammenarbeiten) behalten uns vor, sogenannte „Webbeacons“ zu nutzen, die Daten von Ihrem Internet-Browser an einen Webserver übertragen. Webbeacons können in Webseiten, Videos und E-Mails eingebettet sein und es einem Webserver ermöglichen, bestimmte Arten von Browser-Informationen zu lesen. Des Weiteren lässt sich damit prüfen, ob Sie sich eine bestimmte Webseite oder E-Mail-Nachricht angesehen haben, sowie u. a. die Uhrzeit und das Datum Ihres Zugriffs auf den Webbeacon, die IP-Adresse Ihres Computers und die URL der Webseite, von der das Webbeacon aus angesehen wurde, bestimmen. Wir oder unsere Partner nutzen Webbeacons zu verschiedenen Zwecken, wie z. B. zur Analyse der Nutzung der Dienste und im Zusammenhang mit Cookies zur Bereitstellung von Inhalten, die für Sie relevanter sind.

**5\. Datenschutzpraktiken für Nutzer dieser Website**

**(a) Die Informationen, die wir auf der Website erfassen, und deren Nutzung:**

Die Sharethrough-Website an sich richtet sich vorwiegend an Herausgeber und Werbetreibende, doch wir begrüßen auch Nutzer, die mehr über unsere Dienste erfahren möchten. Beim Zugriff auf die Website oder die Dienste erfassen wir u. U. die folgenden Informationen:

  1. Personenbezogene Daten. Wenn Sie ein Konto bei uns einrichten (z. B. um sich als Herausgeber anzumelden), werden Sie dazu aufgefordert, bestimmte „personenbezogene Daten“ an uns zu übermitteln. Hierbei handelt es sich um Daten, die wir nutzen, um Personen anhand ihrer individuellen, persönlichen Identität direkt zu identifizieren. Beispiele für solche Daten sind Name, Anschrift, E-Mail-Adresse oder Telefonnummer sowie weitere Daten, die mit diesen personenbezogenen Daten zusammenhängen. Wir erfassen Ihre personenbezogene Daten, wenn Sie diese wissentlich bereitstellen, wie z. B. bei der Anmeldung als Werbetreibender oder Herausgeber auf der Website, wenn Sie mit uns kommunizieren und/oder wenn Sie Informationen anfordern. Ihre personenbezogenen Daten können von uns genutzt werden, um Ihr Konto zu verwalten, um Ihnen unsere Dienste bereitzustellen, um per E-Mail neuste Informationen und Mitteilungen zu Ihrem Konto zur Verfügung zu stellen, um unsere Nutzer und Kunden besser kennenzulernen, um auf Ihre Anfragen zu reagieren und um Sie zu Marketingaktivitäten und Produktneuheiten auf dem Laufenden zu halten.
  2. Nicht-personenbezogene Daten. Unabhängig davon, ob Sie ein Konto einrichten oder uns Ihre personenbezogenen Daten zukommen lassen, erfassen wir bei Ihrem Besuch auf unserer Website eventuell nicht-personenbezogene Daten. Hierbei kann es sich um folgende Daten handeln:
    1. Den Typ des Browsers und des Betriebssystems, mit denen Sie auf die Website zugegriffen haben;
    2. Ihre IP-Adresse (hierbei handelt es sich um eine Nummer, die Ihrem Computer automatisch zugewiesen wird, wenn Sie auf das Internet zugreifen, und mit der Ihr allgemeiner Standort ermittelt werden kann);
    3. Die Bereiche unserer Website, die Sie besuchen, anklicken und sich ansehen sowie die Dauer dieser Aktivitäten;
    4. Weitere Informationen, die Sie freiwillig an uns übermitteln.

Wir können diese Informationen mithilfe von Cookies, Webbeacons oder ähnlichen Technologien erfassen bzw. speichern und mithilfe dieser Cookies, Gerätekennungen und ähnlicher Technologien Werbung gezielt auf Sie abstimmen, wenn Sie im Internet browsen oder Ihre mobilen Geräte verwenden.

**(b) Zugriff auf Ihre personenbezogenen Daten und Regelung unserer Nutzung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten:**

Wir erkennen das Grundrecht auf Zugang zu personenbezogenen Daten an. Falls Sie uns bei Ihrer Anmeldung auf unserer Website personenbezogene Daten bereitgestellt haben, können Sie jederzeit in den Kontoeinstellungen auf diese Daten zugreifen und diese ändern. Falls Sie dies wünschen, können Sie Ihr Konto auch jederzeit löschen. Wenden Sie sich hierfür an support@sharethrough.com. Vergessen Sie jedoch nicht, dass wir selbst dann, wenn Sie Ihr Konto löschen, Ihre personenbezogenen Daten möglicherweise aufbewahren, um gesetzliche Vorschriften einzuhalten, Betrug zu vermeiden, Streitigkeiten beizulegen, Probleme zu beheben, Ermittlungen zu unterstützen, unsere Nutzungsbedingungen durchzusetzen und weitere gesetzlich zulässige Maßnahmen zu ergreifen. Das Löschen des Kontos führt nicht zur Löschung der im Zusammenhang mit unseren Diensten erfassten Daten. Nach einer Löschung können Reste personenbezogener Daten in unseren Datenbanken, Zugangsprotokollen und sonstigen Aufzeichnungen zurückbleiben. Des Weiteren sind wir nicht für die Aktualisierung oder Löschung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten verantwortlich, die bereits im Rahmen dieser Richtlinie an Dritte weitergegeben wurden. Darüber hinaus können Sie die Zustellung bestimmter E-Mails von der Website deaktivieren, indem Sie am unteren Rand von einer E-Mail auf „Abmelden“ klicken. Beachten Sie bitte, dass Sie im Falle eines Widerspruchs nach wie vor E-Mails erhalten können, die sich auf Ihre Nutzung des Dienstes beziehen. Der Abschnitt „Internationale Nutzer“ enthält Informationen zu weiteren Optionen.

**6\. SONSTIGE BEDINGUNGEN**

**(a) Informationssicherheit, Aufbewahrung und Datenintegrität**

Wir ergreifen Sicherheitsmaßnahmen zum Schutz vor einem unbefugten Zugriff auf die Daten oder vor einer unbefugten Änderung, Offenlegung oder Löschung von Daten. Es gibt jedoch keine hundertprozentigen Sicherheitsmechanismen. Daher können wir nicht garantieren, dass die von uns ergriffenen Sicherheitsmaßnahmen nicht doch überwunden oder beeinträchtigt werden oder dass Ihre Daten unter allen Umständen sicher sind.

**(b) Kinder**

Zu keinem Zeitpunkt erfassen oder speichern wir vorsätzlich die personenbezogenen Daten von Personen unter 13 Jahren. Unsere Website bzw. unsere Dienste sind nicht darauf ausgelegt, Personen unter 13 Jahren anzusprechen. Der Schutz der Daten von Kindern liegt uns sehr am Herzen: Sollten wir erfahren, dass ein Nutzer jünger als 13 Jahre ist, werden wir angemessene Maßnahmen ergreifen, um die personenbezogenen Daten dieses Nutzers aus unserer Datenbank zu löschen.

**(c) Links zu anderen Websites**

Auch wenn wir auf dieser Website Links zu anderen Websites oder Diensten bereitstellen oder es anderen ermöglichen, Inhalte auf diesen zu teilen, handelt es sich dabei nicht um Empfehlungen, Genehmigungen oder Partnerschaften mit den jeweiligen Dritten. Ferner handelt es sich dabei auch nicht um eine Befürwortung oder Anerkennung deren Datenschutzpraktiken. Andere Websites und Dienste befolgen andere Regeln, was die Nutzung oder Offenlegung personenbezogener Daten betrifft. Wir fordern Sie dazu auf, sich die Datenschutzrichtlinien oder -erklärungen der anderen von Ihnen besuchten Websites durchzulesen.

**(d) Internationale Nutzer**

Die Website und die Dienste werden von den USA sowie von anderen Ländern aus betrieben. Durch Ihre Nutzung der Website und der Dienste stimmen Sie der Übermittlung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten an die USA und die anderen Länder zu. Die in den USA und den anderen Ländern geltenden Gesetze zur Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten können weniger streng sein als in Ihrem Heimatland.

Sharethrough hält sich an die vom US-Handelsministerium herausgegebenen Bestimmungen des EU-US-Datenschutzschildes bezüglich der Erfassung, Nutzung und Speicherung personenbezogener Daten aus Mitgliedstaaten der Europäischen Union. Sharethrough versichert, dass es die Grundsätze von Informationspflicht, Wahlmöglichkeit, Weitergabe, Sicherheit, Datenintegrität, Zweckbindung, Zugriff sowie Beschwerde, Durchsetzung und Haftung einhält. Bei einem Konflikt zwischen den Bestimmungen dieser Richtlinie und denen des Datenschutzschildes kommen die Bestimmungen des Datenschutzschildes zur Anwendung. Näheres zum Datenschutzschild-Programm erfahren Sie auf https://www.privacyshield.gov/list. Dort können Sie sich auch unsere Zertifizierungsseite ansehen.

Es kann sein, dass Sharethrough für die angemessene Übermittlung der personenbezogenen Daten von EU-Bürgern an Dritte haftet.

Beschwerden richten Bürger aller Länder, einschließlich derer, die am Datenschutzschirm teilnehmen, bitte an die am Ende dieser Richtlinie angegebenen Kontaktdaten. Sharethrough hat sich außerdem dazu verpflichtet, offene Datenschutzbeschwerden gemäß den Bestimmungen des EU-US-Datenschutzschildes an BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD weiterzuleiten. Hierbei handelt es sich um einen gemeinnützigen, alternativen Streitbeilegungsanbieter mit Sitz in den Vereinigten Staaten, der vom Council of Better Business Bureaus betrieben wird. Falls Sie von Sharethrough keine zeitnahe Eingangsbestätigung Ihrer Beschwerde erhalten oder falls Ihre Beschwerde von Sharethrough nicht zufriedenstellend bearbeitet wurde, können Sie unter www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/ weitere Informationen erhalten und eine Beschwerde einreichen. Zu guter Letzt und als letztes Mittel haben EU-Bürger, deren Datenschutzbeschwerden nicht beigelegt werden konnten, die Möglichkeit, das Privacy Shield Panel, ein verbindliches Schiedsgericht, anzurufen.

Sharethrough unterliegt den Ermittlungs- und Vollstreckungsbefugnissen der US-Behörde Federal Trade Commission.

Bürger mancher Länder außerhalb der USA (einschließlich aller Bürger, deren Daten wir im Rahmen des Datenschutzschildes erfassen) haben bestimmte Rechte auf Zugriff auf bestimmte personenbezogene Daten, die wir gespeichert haben, sowie auf deren Berichtigung, Änderung oder Löschung (neben den oben im Abschnitt „Zugriff auf Ihre personenbezogenen Daten und Regelung unserer Nutzung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten“ beschrieben Optionen). Um von diesen Rechten Gebrauch zu machen, sind wir über die unten angegebenen Daten erreichbar.

**(e) Änderungen dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie**

Diese Datenschutzrichtlinie kann von Zeit zu Zeit geändert werden. Dies kann durch die Veröffentlichung der neuen Bedingungen geschehen, die nach einem angemessenen Zeitraum in Kraft treten.

**7\. DIE DATENSCHUTZ-GRUNDVERORDUNG DER EU (DSGVO)**

Am 25. Mai 2018 tritt in den Ländern des EWR und in der Schweiz ein neues Datenschutzgesetz in Kraft, die Datenschutz-Grundverordnung der EU (oder „DSGVO“). Im Rahmen der DSGVO sind Sharethrough und alle Nutzer unserer Dienstleistungen dazu verpflichtet, Nutzern bestimmte Informationen über die Verarbeitung ihrer „personenbezogenen Daten“ bereitzustellen. „Personenbezogene Daten“ sind alle Informationen, die sich auf eine identifizierte oder identifizierbare natürliche Person oder ein Gerät beziehen – beispielsweise Namen, Adressen, Cookie-Kennungen, Mobilgeräte, genaue Standortdaten und biometrische Daten.

Um der DSGVO nachzukommen, führen wir im Folgenden die Erläuterungen und Informationen auf, die speziell für Personen im EWR oder in der Schweiz gelten. (Stützen Sie sich also nicht darauf, falls Sie nicht zu dieser Personengruppe gehören.)

**a. Rechtmäßige Gründe für die Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten**

Nach der DSGVO müssen wir Sie über die Rechtsgrundlagen informieren, auf denen die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten erfolgt.  Die Rechtsgrundlagen für unsere Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten für die in Abschnitten 3 und 4 oben aufgeführten Zwecke (sowie Abschnitt 5 bezüglich der Daten unserer Unternehmenskunden) basiert normalerweise auf folgenden Grundlagen:

  * _Sie haben Ihre Einwilligung gegeben._ Für die Speicherung und den Zugriff auf Informationen, die auf Ihrem Gerät gespeichert sind, benötigen wir Ihre Einwilligung. Diese sogenannte „Cookie-Einwilligung“ (die nicht nur für „Cookies“, sondern auch für die Kennung von mobilen Anzeigen gilt) basiert auf unseren eigenen Compliance-Maßnahmen und den Compliance-Maßnahmen unserer Partner für webbasierte und mobile Anwendungen, durch die wir sicherstellen, dass die Einwilligung der Betroffenen erfasst und an unsere Partner weitergeleitet wird, und um zu gewährleisten, dass wir nur die Erfassung von rechtmäßig erhobenen Daten ermöglichen. Damit erfüllen wir unsere Verpflichtungen im Rahmen der Datenschutzrichtlinie für elektronische Kommunikation. Wir werden in anderen Fällen ebenfalls eine Einwilligung einholen. In diesem Fall werden wir den geltenden Gesetzen in Bezug auf solche Einwilligungen und ihren Widerruf entsprechen.
  * _Die Verarbeitung liegt in unserem berechtigten Interesse._ In einigen Fällen ziehen wir berechtigtes Interesse als rechtliche Grundlage für die Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten heran, um unsere Dienstleistungen und/oder die Dienstleistungen anderer Verantwortlicher bereitzustellen. Diese Verarbeitung geht über die ursprüngliche Erfassung der Anzeigen-Kennung bei Mobilgeräten hinaus. Ein berechtigtes Interesse ist beispielsweise die gezielte Abstimmung von Werbung auf den Nutzer von webbasierten und mobilen Plattformen, von denen Nutzer profitieren und die integraler Bestandteil des Ökosystems sind, in dem frei verfügbarer Content durch Werbeeinnahmen finanziert wird. Dies umfasst gelegentlich die Auswertung von Werbekampagnen und die Erstellung entsprechender Berichte.
  * Wir berufen uns zudem auf ein berechtigtes Interesse, wenn wir personenbezogene Daten nutzen, um die Sicherheit unserer Dienstleistungen zu bewahren, beispielsweise in Bezug auf Betrugserkennung oder die Erkennung und Behebung von Softwarefehlern.
  * _Vertragliche Beziehungen._ Gelegentlich verarbeiten wir bei Bedarf Daten im Rahmen einer vertraglichen Beziehung, die wir haben (beispielsweise unsere Kundendaten oder Kontaktinformationen).
  * _Rechtliche Verpflichtungen._ Schließlich kann die Verarbeitung von Daten erforderlich sein, um rechtlichen oder regulatorischen Verpflichtungen zu entsprechen.

**b. Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten**

Da Sharethrough mit globalen Unternehmen und Technologien arbeitet, kann die Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten in ein anderes Land erforderlich sein, als das, in dem die Daten ursprünglich bereitgestellt wurden. Beispielsweise übermitteln wir Ihre Daten womöglich an Dritte, mit denen wir zusammenarbeiten und die sich in Gebieten außerhalb der rechtlichen Zuständigkeit des EWR oder der Schweiz befinden, in denen keine Datenschutzgesetze gelten oder die Datenschutzgesetze im Vergleich zu Europa weniger streng sind.

Falls wir Daten in Länder außerhalb des EWR oder der Schweiz übermitteln, ergreifen wir die erforderlichen Schritte, um angemessene Garantien sicherzustellen, dass Ihre personenbezogenen Daten geschützt sind. So ist Sharethrough beispielsweise wie in Abschnitt 6 (d) dargestellt im Rahmen des US-EU-Datenschutzschildes zertifiziert und gibt eine Eigenerklärung zum Schutz personenbezogener Daten aus dem EWR und der Schweiz ab, um den etablierten Datenschutzprinzipien zu entsprechen. Mehr hierzu erfahren Sie in Abschnitt 11. Wenn Sie weitere Informationen über die Garantien erfahren möchten, mit denen wir in diesen Fällen Ihre personenbezogenen Daten und Ihre Datenschutzrechte schützen, nehmen Sie Kontakt mit uns auf.

**c. Aufbewahrung personenbezogener Daten**

Im Allgemeinen bewahren wir personenbezogene Daten so lange auf, wie es die Bereitstellung unserer Dienstleistungen erfordert, oder so lange es für andere wichtige Zwecke erforderlich ist, beispielsweise für die Einhaltung rechtlicher Verpflichtungen, die Beilegung von Streitigkeiten oder die Durchsetzung unserer Vereinbarungen. Im Allgemeinen deaktivieren wir unsere eigenen Kennungen (d. h. die Kennungen, mit deren Hilfe wir die Daten unserer Kunden mit den Online-Nutzern „abgleichen“ nach **[13 Monaten]** , vorausgesetzt wir können sie aufbewahren, wenn dies aus rechtlichen oder wichtigen betrieblichen Gründen notwendig ist, wie für Auditierung, Datenhaltung in Unternehmen, für die Buchführung oder Einhaltung der Sicherheitsvorgaben und zum Schutz vor Softwarefehlern.

**d. Ihre Rechte als betroffene Person**

Die DSGVO stattet Sie mit bestimmten Rechten in Bezug auf Ihre personenbezogenen Daten aus, die Verantwortliche über Sie halten, einschließlich dem Recht auf Auskunft hinsichtlich Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten, dem Recht auf Berichtigung der personenbezogenen Daten, dem Recht auf Einschränkung oder Löschung personenbezogener Daten und dem Recht, unserer Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten (einschließlich Profiling für gezielte Online-Werbung) zu widersprechen.

  * _Auskunftsrecht:_ Falls Sie Ihr Recht auf Auskunft hinsichtlich der personenbezogenen Daten ausüben möchten, die wir als Verantwortlicher verarbeiten, können Sie Ihre Anfrage über folgende E-Mail-Adresse stellen support@sharethrough.com. Nach Erhalt Ihrer Anfrage senden wir Ihnen die aktuellen Schritt-für-Schritt-Anleitungen, wie Sie Auskunft zu Ihren Daten erhalten. Wir sind dazu verpflichtet, die Identität der um Auskunft ersuchenden Person zu verifizieren, bevor wir Auskunft über personenbezogene Daten geben. Daher werden wir bestimmte Anfragen in Bezug auf das Auskunftsrecht fallweise beurteilen. Dabei werden wir berücksichtigen, (a) wie schwierig die Feststellung ist, ob die von uns gehaltenen Daten und die Daten, die wir verknüpft haben, wirklich und eindeutig der betroffenen Person zugeordnet werden können, die das Auskunftsrecht geltend macht, und (b) welche möglichen negativen Effekte eine Offenlegung personenbezogener Daten der falschen Person gegenüber beinhaltet. Da eine solche vorschriftswidrige Offenlegung mit großer Wahrscheinlichkeit einen negativen Effekt auf die Datenschutzrechte und die Grundfreiheiten der betroffenen Person haben würde, schränken wir die personenbezogenen Daten ein, die wir zur Verfügung stellen.
  * Beachten Sie bitte, dass wir nur Auskunftsersuchen in Bezug auf personenbezogene Daten per E-Mail bearbeiten können, für die wir der Verantwortlicher sind (siehe unten). Wo wir der Auftragsverarbeiter für einen unserer Kunden sind, werden wir Ihre Anfrage an diesen Kunden weiterleiten. Um diesen Prozess zu vereinfachen, bitten wir Sie (falls möglich) den Kunden anzugeben, auf den sich Ihre Anfrage bezieht.

_Recht auf Berichtigung:_ Falls Sie Ihr Recht auf Berichtigung hinsichtlich der Daten ausüben möchten, die wir als Verantwortlicher verarbeiten, können Sie uns über die untenstehenden Informationen kontaktieren.

_Widerspruchsrecht gegen die Verarbeitung oder Widerruf der Einwilligung:_ Durch die Deaktivierung von Cookies in Ihrem Browser und die gerätebasierten Opt-out-Signale (siehe Abschnitt 2 dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie), können Sie Ihre Einwilligung zur Verarbeitung der personenbezogenen Daten wiederrufen, die auf Ihrer Einwilligung basiert. Wenn Sie Ihre Einwilligung widerrufen, stellen wir die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zum Zwecke unserer Dienstleistungen innerhalb von maximal 30 Tagen ein.

Wir erfassen diese Opt-out-Signale entweder selbst oder erhalten diese über die Apps für Mobilgeräte, mit denen wir arbeiten.

  * _Recht auf Löschung._ Sie haben das Recht auf Löschung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten, die wir als Verantwortlicher für die Verarbeitung halten. Der oben beschriebene Opt-out-Prozess erfüllt dieses Recht. Wenn ein Nutzer das Opt-out über unsere Partner wählt (oder über die Einstellungen seines Mobilgeräts) und wir dieses Signal erhalten, stellen wir die Nutzung der personenbezogenen Daten für unsere Werbedienstleistungen ein. Wir werden Ihre personenbezogenen Daten auch manuell löschen, wenn Sie dies bevorzugen. Kontaktieren Sie uns über [support@sharethrough.com](mailto:support@sharethrough.com), um weitere Anweisungen zu erhalten, falls Sie das Recht auf manuelle Löschung geltend machen möchten. Beachten Sie aber, dass wir Kopien bestimmter personenbezogener Daten in deaktivierten Dateien oder Sicherungskopien für unsere eigenen internen und notwendigen Zwecke aufbewahren können, wie für Auditierung, Buchführung und Fakturierung, für rechtliche Zwecke oder zur Erkennung von Softwarefehlern. In den meisten Fällen werden wir solche Daten innerhalb von 36 Monaten löschen, es sei denn, es liegt ein zwingender Grund für die Aufbewahrung vor.
  * _Recht auf Einreichung einer Beschwerde._ Sie haben das Recht bei der Aufsichtsbehörde eine Beschwerde einzureichen. Wir hoffen jedoch, dass Sie zunächst Kontakt zu uns aufnehmen, sodass wir mit Ihnen gemeinsam die Beschwerde beilegen oder Ihre etwaigen Bedenken zerstreuen können.

**e. Sharethrough als Verantwortlicher und Auftragsverarbeiter**

Das Datenschutzgesetz der EU unterscheidet zwischen Organisationen, die personenbezogene Daten für ihre eigenen Zwecke verarbeiten (bezeichnet als „Verantwortliche“) und Organisationen, die personenbezogene Daten im Auftrag anderer Organisationen verarbeiten (bezeichnet als „Auftragsverarbeiter“). Wie oben aufgeführt, sind wir nicht immer der Verantwortliche für die Daten in unserem Besitz, sondern gelegentlich auch ein Auftragsverarbeiter für andere Unternehmen, beispielsweise für unsere Kunden. In diesen Fällen können wir Ihre Anfrage an den entsprechenden Verantwortlichen weiterleiten, da es die Verantwortlichen sind, die die Hauptverantwortung für Ihre personenbezogenen Daten haben.

**8\. Durchsetzung, Fragen und Beschwerden**

Falls Sie hinsichtlich dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie oder unserer Datenschutzpraktiken Fragen haben oder Bedenken dazu äußern möchten, oder von Ihren Rechten Gebrauch machen möchten, schreiben Sie bitte eine E-Mail an [privacy@sharethrough.com](mailto:privacy@sharethrough.com) oder schreiben Sie uns per Post an:

Sharethrough, Inc.   
Attention: Privacy Inquiries   
170 Columbus Ave, Suite 280  
San Francisco, CA 94133

Stand: Mai 2018

**Informativa sulla privacy di Sharethrough**

Questo contenuto è reso visibile da Sharethrough, l’applicazione di native advertising all-in-one per editori, sviluppatori di app e inserzionisti, ed è pagato dall’inserzionista o addetto al marketing indicato. La nostra Informativa sulla privacy spiega come utilizziamo informazioni per il funzionamento della nostra applicazione e per erogare contenuti e come disattivare la pubblicità mirata da parte di molte aziende che si occupano dell’erogazione di pubblicità basata sugli interessi tramite la nostra applicazione o altri contenuti, siti internet e applicazioni.

* * *

## Informativa sulla privacy

Benvenuti su Sharethrough.com, un sito appartenente a e controllato da Sharethrough, Inc. (di seguito “Sharethrough”, “noi”, “ci” o “nostro”). Gestiamo una piattaforma che consente ai siti internet e agli sviluppatori di applicazioni mobili (“app”) e a piattaforme simili di dare visibilità ai contenuti forniti dai nostri inserzionisti (i “Contenuti promozionali”). Il contenuto che vi mostriamo viene identificato come “Annuncio” o con diciture simili, a indicare che si tratta di un contenuto a pagamento o sponsorizzato. Potreste essere stati indirizzati alla presente informativa proprio cliccando su un’icona a fianco di un nostro Contenuto promozionale.

Sharethrough aiuta i siti internet, le app per dispositivi mobili e i servizi web a fornire ai propri utenti contenuti di terze parti accattivanti e pertinenti; spesso questa pratica finanzia la loro offerta di contenuti e media gratuiti. A tal fine, possiamo raccogliere e utilizzare in forma anonima i dati ricevuti da tali siti e applicazioni e dai loro utenti.

Con la presente Informativa sulla privacy intendiamo illustrarvi la natura dei dati che raccogliamo quando visualizzate il Contenuto promozionale o visitate il presente sito internet e per quali scopi utilizziamo, condividiamo e tuteliamo tali dati. La privacy dell’utente e la trasparenza sono importanti per noi.

**1\. Ambito di applicazione della presente Informativa**

La presente Informativa sulla privacy si applica al sito internet con indirizzo [www.sharethrough.com](http://sharethrough.com/) (di seguito, il “Sito di Sharethrough”), agli strumenti e ai forum interattivi disponibili attraverso il Sito di Sharethrough e alla piattaforma pubblicitaria per i Contenuti promozionali (denominati nel complesso i “Servizi”), compresi quelli offerti su siti internet e applicazioni mobili.

Generalmente si distinguono tre categorie di utenti del Sito di Sharethrough e dei Servizi: “Editori”, ovvero coloro che gestiscono o pubblicano i siti e le app dove compare il Contenuto promozionale; “Inserzionisti”, che rendono visibile il loro contenuto attraverso la nostra piattaforma e “Utenti”, ovvero i soggetti che utilizzano il sito o la app di un Editore. Visitando il Sito di Sharethrough o utilizzando i Servizi si accettano le norme e prassi descritte nella presente Informativa sulla privacy.

La presente Informativa sulla privacy regola due distinti ambiti concernenti i dati:

  * Le prassi sulla privacy per gli utenti dei Servizi offerti da Sharethrough e dei Contenuti promozionali 
  * Le prassi sulla privacy per gli utenti del presente Sito internet (di cui alla Sezione 5)

**2\. Scelte e Negazione del consenso circa i contenuti dei Servizi offerti da Sharethrough**

Riteniamo che proporre contenuti mirati e pertinenti migliori la vostra fruizione di internet e dei dispositivi mobili; tale pratica sovvenziona i media gratuiti e altri contenuti di ampia diffusione. Come descritto nel seguito della presente Informativa sulla privacy, noi (o un partner con cui collaboriamo) potremmo raccogliere dati non personali in forma anonima associati alle vostre attività sul web o su dispositivi mobili (cfr. sezione 3). Per “dati non personali” intendiamo informazioni associate in modo univoco a un browser o dispositivo, ma che non contengono il vostro nome, indirizzo, numero di telefono, indirizzo e-mail o altri strumenti di identificazione delle persone fisiche rilasciati dallo Stato (come il codice fiscale). Sia noi, sia loro utilizziamo tali informazioni per fornirvi contenuti più pertinenti e accattivanti, nonché solitamente meno fastidiosi: ad esempio, per ridurre le possibilità che vi siano riproposti più volte gli stessi contenuti o ne visualizziate di non affini ai vostri interessi.

Se preferite che noi e/o piattaforme di terze parti con cui collaboriamo non raccogliamo tali informazioni circa le vostre attività sul web o su dispositivo mobile con lo scopo di proporre pubblicità mirata, potete negare il consenso a molte delle piattaforme pubblicitarie online che la distribuiscono. Se desiderate negare il consenso o semplicemente ricevere maggiori informazioni sulle piattaforme che possono proporre inserzioni o contenuti mirati all’utente e con cui potremmo talora collaborare, potete visitare i siti di [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) e [Network Advertising Initiative.](https://www.networkadvertising.org/)Segnaliamo che questi strumenti per la negazione del consenso sono basati sui cookie, quindi se questi vengono bloccati o eliminati, o se viene cambiato o aggiornato il browser, occorrerà negare di nuovo il consenso. Potete anche disattivare la ricezione di pubblicità su dispositivo mobile basata sugli identificativi da noi utilizzati (come l’IDFA o l’ID Pubblicità su Android) modificando le “impostazioni” del dispositivo.

Potete anche disattivare la ricezione di pubblicità su dispositivo mobile basata sugli identificativi da noi utilizzati (come l’IDFA o l’ID Pubblicità su Android) modificando le “impostazioni” del dispositivo. Ad esempio, per modificare le preferenze relative ai messaggi pubblicitari su iOS, selezionate Impostazioni > Privacy > Pubblicità > Limita raccolta dati pubblicitari. Per modificare le preferenze annunci su Android, selezionate Impostazioni > Google > Annunci > Disattiva annunci basati sugli interessi. (Su alcuni dispositivi, soprattutto se modelli precedenti, le istruzioni potrebbero essere formulate diversamente). Ci occupiamo direttamente della raccolta di queste segnalazioni per la negazione del consenso oppure le riceviamo dalle app per dispositivi mobili con le quali collaboriamo.

**3\. Prassi sulla privacy per gli utenti finali che ricevono e visualizzano i contenuti: quali dati raccogliamo, come li usiamo e condividiamo**

Una componente essenziale del Servizio è la piattaforma Sharethrough, che aiuta gli sviluppatori di app e i titolari di siti web a fornire contenuti di terze parti più pertinenti per i loro utenti. Se state leggendo la presente informativa, probabilmente siete a conoscenza della modalità con cui Sharethrough aiuta gli Inserzionisti a far comparire Contenuti promozionali su siti web e app mobili. Quando visualizzate o cliccate su un Contenuto promozionale (sia su web, sia su dispositivo mobile), raccogliamo automaticamente taluni dati non personali da utilizzare sulla nostra piattaforma. Potremmo consentire agli Editori di utilizzare tutte queste informazioni o parte di esse attraverso la Piattaforma con finalità analitiche. Ci avvaliamo di tali informazioni (in collaborazione con piattaforme di terze parti) anche per proporvi Contenuti promozionali personalizzati, come spiegato di seguito.

**(a) Le informazioni che raccogliamo quando visualizzate Contenuti promozionali**

Quando cliccate su un Contenuto promozionale e lo visualizzate, noi o una piattaforma di terze parti con cui collaboriamo potremmo raccogliere alcuni dati non personali su di voi. Per “Dati non personali” intendiamo informazioni che generalmente da sole non consentono di risalire all’identità del singolo utente (a differenza di dati come nome, indirizzo, numero di telefono o persino indirizzo e-mail). Visualizzando il Contenuto promozionale con un’applicazione mobile, potremmo raccogliere, conservare e utilizzare le seguenti informazioni: 

  1. Gli identificativi del dispositivo, quali l’IDFA di Apple o l’ID Pubblicità su Android;
  2. L’indirizzo IP (una stringa numerica attribuita automaticamente al computer quando si accede a internet, che può essere utilizzata per risalire alla posizione geografica approssimativa dell’utente);
  3. L’applicazione utilizzata dal dispositivo durante l’interazione con il contenuto di Sharethrough e una marca temporale associata a tale interazione;
  4. Informazioni sul dispositivo e sul sistema operativo utilizzato;
  5. Altre informazioni che ci fornite volontariamente.

Visualizzando il Contenuto promozionale con un browser su web o su dispositivo mobile, noi o una piattaforma di terze parti con cui collaboriamo potremmo raccogliere, conservare e utilizzare informazioni quali:

  1. Il tipo di browser e sistema operativo utilizzato per accedere al sito;
  2. L’indirizzo IP (una stringa numerica attribuita automaticamente al computer quando si accede a internet, che può essere utilizzata per risalire alla posizione geografica approssimativa dell’utente);
  3. Informazioni fornite dal browser quando l’utente visualizza o apre il Contenuto promozionale, compreso il sito internet visitato prima di cliccare sul Contenuto promozionale e visualizzarlo, il time stamp e la stringa agente utente, le analisi di percorso interno (clickstream), il tipo di browser e il suo linguaggio, la data e l’orario in cui è stato visualizzato il Contenuto promozionale. Potremmo raccogliere o conservare queste informazioni utilizzando cookie, web beacon e tecnologie simili. La Sezione 4, riportata di seguito, contiene ulteriori informazioni su tali tecnologie online.
  4. Altre informazioni che l’utente ci fornisce volontariamente.

**(b) Come utilizziamo le informazioni che raccogliamo quando visualizzate i Contenuti promozionali**

Potremmo utilizzare le suddette informazioni per gli scopi seguenti, anche attraverso l’utilizzo di cookie e codici identificativi del dispositivo, come spiegato più dettagliatamente nella Sezione 4. Potremmo altresì collaborare con piattaforme per la distribuzione di contenuti e pubblicitarie di terze parti che usano tali informazioni con le stesse finalità. Generalmente consentiamo alle piattaforme per la distribuzione di contenuti e pubblicitarie di terze parti di raggiungere tali scopi tramite la “sincronizzazione” degli identificatori degli editori con quelli di suddette piattaforme, con lo scopo di permettere a tali piattaforme di proporre pubblicità mirate ai consumatori (spesso sulla base di altre informazioni raccolte dalle stesse):

  1. Per adattare i contenuti che vi mostriamo (o che vi mostrano altri, compresi gli inserzionisti e i fornitori di contenuti), anche tramite la costruzione di data segment appositi basati sui vostri clic e sui contenuti visualizzati (per es. “ama lo sport”, “ama il rock classico”), nonché sul momento e sulla frequenza di tali visualizzazioni;
  2. Per coordinare i contenuti mostrati da noi o da altri su vari dispositivi, compresi quelli mobili e le piattaforme web attraverso inferenze anonime sui collegamenti tra i dispositivi;
  3. Per comprendere meglio le modalità di utilizzo del Servizio e migliorarlo, per esempio creando e condividendo con i nostri clienti (e terze parti interessate) modelli aggregati e analitici con informazioni su come, quando e da chi viene visualizzato il Contenuto (per es. se alcune inserzioni sono visualizzate più spesso in determinati orari o da alcune fasce di pubblico);
  4. Per fornire ai nostri clienti (e a terze parti interessate) informazioni approfondite sull’ottimizzazione delle campagne promozionali su siti internet o su dispositivi mobili, sul posizionamento dell’annuncio o metriche sulla frequenza (per es. per aiutare gli inserzionisti a capire se determinate inserzioni abbiano avuto o meno buone performance e perché, e la relazione tra tali annunci e altre informazioni che potrebbero essere note sull’utente);
  5. Per aiutarci ad accertarci che il Servizio funzioni correttamente;
  6. Per altri scopi legati alla pubblicazione degli annunci e alla reportistica in forma anonima, diversi da quelli elencati in precedenza;
  7. Per qualsiasi altro scopo dichiarato all’utente al momento della raccolta delle informazioni su di lui.

**(c) Come condividiamo le informazioni che raccogliamo quando visualizzate i Contenuti promozionali. Potremmo condividere le informazioni raccolte in relazione al Contenuto promozionale come segue:**

  1. Affiliati e Partner. Potremmo condividere i vostri dati non personali con i nostri affiliati (entità che controllano la nostra azienda, ne sono controllate o sono sottoposte a comune controllo), nonché con partner selezionati e fornitori che ci aiutano a erogare i nostri Servizi. Potremmo condividere tali dati anche con Editori, Inserzionisti e altri fornitori terzi (come le piattaforme di gestione dei dati e gli ad network) per erogare i nostri Servizi. Questi soggetti potrebbero, per esempio, utilizzare le informazioni su di voi per fare previsioni sui vostri interessi o per aiutarci a formularne e potrebbero proporvi offerte, materiali promozionali e pubblicità.
  2. Fornitori di servizi. Potremmo condividere qualsiasi informazione (compresi i Dati personali che ci comunicate, per esempio tramite il presente sito) con soggetti prestatori di servizi, comprese aziende che gestiscono l’elaborazione dei pagamenti, l’assistenza clienti e il supporto web, i servizi analitici, l’elaborazione dei dati, l’arricchimento e il miglioramento dei dati, il customer insight, la pubblicità, la distribuzione delle e-mail e altri servizi.
  3. Altri soggetti ove previsto dalla legge o qualora sia necessario per tutelare i nostri Servizi. Potremmo divulgare informazioni su di voi (compresi i Dati personali) ad altri soggetti al fine di:
    * proteggere i diritti previsti dalla legge o i beni di Sharethrough, dei nostri affiliati e dei siti o dei servizi con cui collaboriamo;
    * tutelare i diritti, l’incolumità e la sicurezza dei nostri utenti, di noi stessi o di altre persone o soggetti;
    * prevenire le frodi (o con finalità legate alla gestione dei rischi); ovvero
    * ottemperare alle disposizioni di legge, anche nell’ambito di un’iniziativa legale, o dare seguito a una richiesta di collaborazione da parte di un ente governativo, a prescindere che rappresenti o meno un obbligo di legge. Per esempio potremmo essere tenuti, se del caso, a divulgare informazioni su di voi per motivi di sicurezza nazionale o su richiesta delle forze dell’ordine.
  4. Altri soggetti in relazione a un trasferimento di attività. In caso di una nostra vendita o trasferimento di attività, fusione o cessione di altro tipo (o nell’ambito della due diligence connessa a tale transazione), o nell'improbabile eventualità di fallimento, potremmo cedere le vostre informazioni nell’ambito di tale operazione.
  5. Noi (o piattaforme di terze parti con cui collaboriamo) potremmo combinare i vostri dati non personali con quelli di altri utenti e condividere tali informazioni in forma aggregata senza limitazione, anche con Editori e Inserzionisti, per esempio con finalità analitiche o per aiutarli a saperne di più sui loro clienti e utenti e a proporre annunci, contenuti e offerte mirati a clienti esistenti o potenziali.

**4\. Cookie, web beacon e tecnologie simili**

Noi e le piattaforme per la distribuzione di contenuti e pubblicità di terze parti con cui collaboriamo possiamo utilizzare cookie e tecnologie simili sul sito di Sharethrough e quando usufruite dei nostri servizi, per esempio quando visualizzate o cliccate sui Contenuti promozionali. La presente sezione fornisce maggiori informazioni su alcune di queste tecnologie e sul loro funzionamento.

(a) Cookie. I cookie sono piccoli file di testo utilizzati da siti web e altri servizi online per conservare informazioni sugli utenti sui loro stessi computer. Per esempio, su taluni siti i cookie possono essere utilizzati per memorizzare le credenziali di accesso, in modo da non doverle inserire ogni volta che si visita nuovamente quel sito. Possono essere conservate anche altre informazioni per personalizzare la navigazione e renderla più efficiente durante visite successive. I cookie possono anche memorizzare un identificativo univoco associato al vostro computer, per consentire ai servizi web e ai network che distribuiscono contenuti e pubblicità di riconoscervi quando visitate siti diversi. Potete configurare il vostro browser web in modo che vi avvisi ogni volta che viene inviato un cookie o che blocchi completamente tutti i tipi di cookie o alcuni di essi, ma in tal caso con ogni probabilità non sarete più in grado di fruire pienamente di tutte le funzioni di alcuni siti.

(b) Sharethrough (e piattaforme di terze parti con cui collaboriamo) potrebbe utilizzare o supportare i cookie per gli scopi seguenti:

  1. Per raccogliere informazioni sulle vostre attività di navigazione in rete al fine di erogare i Servizi;
  2. Per associare le informazioni raccolte dai cookie a quelle che otteniamo direttamente da voi (per esempio attraverso questo sito internet) o da fonti disponibili sul mercato;
  3. Per collaborare con terze parti che ci aiutano a distribuire i Contenuti promozionali (tramite i nostri Servizi o su internet) o che ci forniscono altri servizi, per esempio dando agli utenti la possibilità di visualizzare o commentare i contenuti o di monitorare le statistiche sull’utilizzo del sito;

Potremmo anche utilizzare i cookie (e i web beacon descritti di seguito) per tutte le finalità elencate nella sezione [“Come utilizziamo le informazioni che raccogliamo quando visualizzate i Contenuti promozionali”](https://platform-cdn.sharethrough.com/privacy-policy#how-we-use-information-en)riportata sopra. Noi (o piattaforme di terze parti con cui collaboriamo) potremmo anche avvalerci di identificativi per dispositivi mobili, come IDFA su Apple e ID Pubblicità su Android, con finalità analoghe.

(c) Web beacon. Noi (o piattaforme di terze parti con cui collaboriamo) potremmo impiegare tecnologie denominate “web beacon”, che trasmettono informazioni dal vostro browser a un server web. I web beacon possono essere integrati nelle pagine web, in video o e-mail per consentire a un server web di leggere alcune informazioni sul vostro browser, verificare se avete visualizzato una determinata pagina internet o messaggio e-mail e stabilire data e orario della visualizzazione del web beacon, indirizzo IP del computer, URL della pagina web da cui è stato visualizzato il web beacon e altro. Noi (o i nostri partner) potremmo ricorrere ai web beacon con diverse finalità, tra cui l’analisi dell’uso dei Servizi e, in abbinamento ai cookie, per fornire contenuti più rilevanti per l’utente.

**5\. Le prassi sulla privacy per gli utenti del presente sito internet**

(a) Le informazioni che raccogliamo sul sito internet e come le utilizziamo:

Il Sito di Sharethrough si rivolge principalmente a Editori e Inserzionisti, ma sono i benvenuti anche gli Utenti che desiderano maggiori informazioni sui nostri Servizi. Quando accedete al Sito o utilizzate i Servizi, potremmo raccogliere le informazioni seguenti:

  1. Dati personali. Quando create un account sul nostro sito (per esempio, per registrarvi come Editori), potremmo richiedere e voi potreste fornirci alcuni “Dati personali”, ovvero informazioni che consentono di risalire direttamente a una persona sulla base della sua identità. Tali dati possono comprendere nome, indirizzo postale ed e-mail, numero di telefono e altre informazioni pertinenti. Raccogliamo i vostri Dati personali quando li fornite deliberatamente, per esempio quando vi registrate come Inserzionisti o Editori sul Sito, comunicate con noi e/o richiedete informazioni. Potremmo avvalerci dei vostri Dati personali per gestire il vostro account ed erogarvi servizi, per inviare comunicazioni ed e-mail di carattere amministrativo, per raccogliere informazioni sui nostri Utenti e clienti, per rispondere alle vostre domande e per mandare messaggi di marketing o aggiornamenti sui prodotti.
  2. Dati non personali. A prescindere che venga creato un account e che ci forniate i vostri Dati personali o meno, potremmo raccogliere altri Dati non personali quando visitate il nostro Sito. Si tratta di informazioni come:
    1. Il tipo di browser e sistema operativo utilizzato per accedere al sito;
    2. L’indirizzo IP (una stringa numerica attribuita automaticamente al computer quando si accede a internet, che può essere utilizzata per risalire alla posizione geografica approssimativa dell’utente);
    3. Quale parte del nostro Sito web visitate, su quali collegamenti cliccate, quali contenuti visualizzate e per quanto tempo;
    4. Altre informazioni da voi stessi fornite.

Potremmo raccogliere o conservare le informazioni suddette grazie a cookie, web beacon e tecnologie simili. Quando navigate in rete o utilizzate il vostro dispositivo mobile, potremmo avvalerci di tali cookie, identificativi dell’apparecchio o tecnologie simili per il targeting o retargeting di annunci pubblicitari mirati.

(b) Accesso ai vostri Dati e controllo del loro uso da parte nostra:

Riconosciamo il diritto degli individui ad accedere ai loro dati personali. Se ci fornite Dati personali durante la registrazione sul nostro Sito, potete accedere a tali dati e modificarli in qualsiasi momento tramite le impostazioni dell’account. Ci dispiacerebbe se doveste decidere di cancellare il vostro account, ma potete farlo in qualsiasi momento contattando support@Sharethrough.com. Vi ricordiamo, tuttavia, che anche cancellando il vostro account potremmo conservare i vostri dati per adempiere la legge, prevenire frodi, dirimere controversie, risolvere problemi, collaborare a eventuali indagini, garantire il rispetto delle nostre Condizioni di utilizzo e per altri usi consentiti dalla legge. La cancellazione di un account non comporta la cancellazione dei dati raccolti in relazione ai nostri Servizi. Dopo una cancellazione, potrebbero permanere dei dati residui nei nostri database, nei log di accesso e in documenti di altro tipo. Inoltre, non è nostra responsabilità aggiornare o cancellare i vostri dati già trasmessi a terze parti che li abbiano ricevuti con le modalità consentite dalla presente Informativa. Potete altresì interrompere la ricezione di certe e-mail inviate dal Sito cliccando sul link “Annulla l’iscrizione” presente in fondo a ogni messaggio. Segnaliamo che anche annullando l’iscrizione o negando il consenso, potremmo comunque inviarvi comunicazioni relative all’uso del Servizio da parte vostra. Vi invitiamo a consultare la sezione “Utenti internazionali” qui di seguito per opzioni aggiuntive.

**6\. VARIE**

**(a) Sicurezza delle informazioni, conservazione e integrità dei dati**

Adottiamo misure di sicurezza volte a proteggere da accessi non autorizzati ai dati o dalla loro alterazione, divulgazione o distruzione non autorizzata. Tuttavia, nessuna precauzione è assolutamente infallibile e, al pari di altre applicazioni e piattaforme per il web e dispositivi mobili, non siamo in grado di garantire che le misure di sicurezza adottate non siano soggette a penetrazione o compromissione o che i vostri dati resteranno al sicuro in tutte le circostanze.

**(b) Bambini**

Non raccogliamo né conserviamo intenzionalmente Dati personali di minori di 13 anni e nessuna parte del nostro Sito o dei nostri Servizi è costruita per attirare persone al di sotto dei 13 anni di età. Proteggere la privacy dei bambini per noi è importante. Se apprendiamo che un utente ha meno di 13 anni, prenderemo tutte le misure ragionevoli per rimuovere i Dati personali di tale utente dai nostri database.

**(c) Collegamenti ad altri siti**

Il presente Sito web potrebbe reindirizzare a un altro sito o servizio, o consentire a terzi di condividere contenuti su di essi; tuttavia, ciò non implica in alcun modo da parte nostra approvazione, autorizzazione o dichiarazione di affiliazione a tale terza parte, né comporta approvazione o riconoscimento delle loro prassi in materia di riservatezza. Altri siti internet e servizi seguono regole diverse in relazione all’uso o alla divulgazione di dati personali. Vi invitiamo a leggere le informative o politiche sulla privacy degli altri siti web che visitate.

**(d) Utenti internazionali**

Il Sito web e i Servizi sono ospitati su server ubicati negli Stati Uniti e in altri Paesi. Accedendo al Sito web o ai Servizi, acconsentite al trasferimento dei vostri dati negli Stati Uniti e in altri Paesi. Le norme sul trattamento di tali dati vigenti negli Stati Uniti e negli altri Paesi possono essere meno rigide di quelle in vigore nel vostro Paese.

Sharethrough aderisce ai principi dell’accordo “Privacy Shield” tra Unione Europea e Stati Uniti come previsto dal Dipartimento del commercio degli Stati Uniti in merito a raccolta, uso e conservazione dei dati personali provenienti dagli Stati membri dell’UE e del Regno Unito. Sharethrough ha certificato la propria adesione ai principi di Notifica, Scelta, Responsabilità per il trasferimento successivo, Sicurezza, Integrità dei dati e Limitazione delle finalità, Accesso e Ricorso, Garanzie di applicazione e Responsabilità. In caso di conflitto tra i contenuti della presente informativa sulla privacy e i principi dell’accordo “Privacy Shield”, questi ultimi prevarranno. Maggiori informazioni sul programma “Privacy Shield” sono disponibili all’indirizzo https://www.privacyshield.gov/list, dove è possibile anche visualizzare la pagina con la nostra certificazione.

Sharethrough può essere responsabile dell’opportuno trasferimento dei dati personali di soggetti residenti nell’UE e nel Regno Unito a terze parti.

Per presentare un reclamo, i residenti di qualsiasi Paese, compresi quelli aderenti al “Privacy Shield”, ci possono contattare con le modalità indicate in calce alla presente Informativa. Sharethrough si impegna altresì a inoltrare reclami irrisolti sulla privacy ai sensi dell’accordo “Privacy Shield” tra UE e Stati Uniti a BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, organismo alternativo non-profit di risoluzione dei contenziosi, con sede negli Stati Uniti e gestito dal Council of Better Business Bureaus. Se non avete ricevuto tempestivamente riscontro al vostro reclamo da parte di Sharethrough, o se Sharethrough non vi ha dato adeguato seguito, visitate www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/ per maggiori informazioni o per presentare un reclamo. Infine e solo in ultima istanza, i cittadini dell’UE o del Regno Unito, i cui reclami in materia di privacy non siano stati risolti, possono fare appello al Privacy Shield Panel, un meccanismo di arbitrato le cui decisioni sono vincolanti.

Sharethrough è soggetta ai poteri investigativi ed esecutivi della Federal Trade Commission.

I residenti in alcuni Paesi diversi dagli Stati Uniti (compresi tutti i soggetti i cui dati vengono da noi raccolti ai sensi dell’accordo “Privacy Shield”) godono per legge di alcuni diritti che sanciscono la possibilità di accedere a taluni dati su di loro di cui siamo in possesso e di richiederne la correzione, modifica o cancellazione (in aggiunta alle opzioni descritte nella sezione “Accesso ai vostri Dati e controllo del loro uso da parte nostra” riportata sopra). Per esercitare tali diritti, possono contattarci con le modalità indicate di seguito.

**(e) Modifiche alla presente Informativa sulla privacy**

La presente Informativa sulla privacy è soggetta a modifiche periodiche, anche tramite la pubblicazione da parte nostra di nuovi termini, validi dopo un periodo di tempo ragionevole.

**7\. IL REGOLAMENTO GENERALE UE SULLA PROTEZIONE DEI DATI (GDPR)**

Il 25 maggio 2018, nei Paesi dello Spazio Economico Europeo (SEE) e in Svizzera entrerà in vigore una nuova legge sulla tutela dei dati personali denominata Regolamento generale UE sulla protezione dei dati (o il “GDPR”). Col GDPR Sharethrough e chi utilizza i nostri servizi saranno tenuti a fornire agli utenti determinate informazioni in merito all’elaborazione dei loro “Dati personali”. “Dati personali” è una dicitura utilizzata in Europa che indica, in senso lato, dati che identificano o possono identificare un utente o un dispositivo specifico, ad esempio nomi, indirizzi, identificatori cookie, dispositivi mobili, dati precisi relativi alla posizione e dati biometrici.

Per ottemperare al GDPR, di seguito riportiamo dichiarazioni e informazioni specifiche per coloro che si trovano in Paesi SEE o in Svizzera (in caso contrario, quanto segue non si applica).

**a. Fondamenti legali per l’elaborazione dei Dati personali**

Col GDPR siamo tenuti a mettervi al corrente della base giuridica utilizzata per l’elaborazione di eventuali Dati personali che vi riguardano.  Solitamente la base giuridica per l’elaborazione di Dati personali che vi riguardano per gli scopi delineati nelle sezioni 3 e 4 sopracitate (nonché sezione 5 per i dati sulla nostra clientela aziendale) è rappresentata dal fatto che:

  * _Ci avete fornito il vostro consenso._ Ci serve il vostro consenso per conservare e accedere alle informazioni memorizzate sul vostro dispositivo. Per ottenere questo cosiddetto “consenso dei cookie” (che non si applica soltanto ai “cookie” ma anche agli identificativi di pubblicità per dispositivi mobili) ci basiamo sulle nostre procedure di conformità e su quelle dei nostri partner mobili e sul web; sono state ideate per garantire che il consenso sia raccolto e trasmesso ai partner, nonché per assicurarsi che agevoliamo soltanto la raccolta di dati ottenuti lecitamente. Così facendo adempiamo ai nostri obblighi ai sensi della direttiva e-privacy. Potremmo decidere di ottenere il consenso anche in altri casi, e in tal caso rispetteremo le leggi applicabili relative a tale consenso e alla sua revoca.
  * _L’elaborazione è un nostro interesse legittimo._ In alcuni casi l’interesse legittimo diventa la base giuridica per l’elaborazione di Dati personali al fine di fornire i nostri servizi e/o quelli di altri titolari del trattamento. Tale elaborazione non si limita alla semplice raccolta originaria di identificativi di pubblicità per dispositivi mobili. Ad esempio, un interesse legittimo di cui ci avvaliamo è l’adattamento di comunicazioni promozionali agli utenti di properties web e mobile, un procedimento vantaggioso per gli utenti e parte integrante dell’ecosistema nel quale i contenuti liberamente consultabili sono finanziati con ricavi pubblicitari. Inoltre ciò presuppone anche la fornitura di analisi e reportistica sulle campagne promozionali.
  * Ci avvaliamo poi dell’interesse legittimo quando utilizziamo i Dati personali per garantire la sicurezza dei nostri Servizi, ad esempio per rilevare frodi o per assicurarci che eventuali bug siano individuati e risolti.
  * _Relazioni contrattuali._ A volte, se del caso, elaboriamo alcuni dati nell’ambito di accordi contrattuali in essere (ad esempio i dati e i recapiti dei clienti).
  * _Obblighi legali._ Infine, potrebbe essere necessario elaborare alcuni dati per adempiere ai nostri obblighi legali o normativi.

**b. Trasferimenti di Dati personali**

Poiché Sharethrough opera con aziende e tecnologie globali, potrebbe essere necessario trasferire i Dati personali che vi riguardano all’esterno del Paese dove sono stati inizialmente forniti. Ad esempio, potremmo trasferire i vostri dati a terze parti con cui collaboriamo che operano da giurisdizioni esterne al SEE o alla Svizzera, prive di leggi sulla tutela dei dati personali o con leggi meno rigorose di quelle europee.

Quando trasferiamo i Dati personali all’esterno del SEE o della Svizzera, adottiamo misure atte a garantire la tutela dei Dati personali che vi riguardano. Ad esempio, come descritto nella sezione 6(d), Sharethrough è certificata ai sensi di “Privacy Shield” e, di conseguenza, autocertifica la protezione dei Dati personali provenienti dal SEE e dalla Svizzera nel totale rispetto dei principi stabiliti in materia di tutela dei dati personali. La sezione 11 contiene ulteriori informazioni a riguardo.  Contattateci senza indugio ai recapiti indicati di seguito per ulteriori informazioni circa le misure adottate per proteggere i Dati personali che vi riguardano e i diritti di riservatezza in tali eventualità.

**c. Conservazione dei Dati personali**

In linea generale, conserviamo i Dati personali che vi riguardano per il tempo necessario a fornirvi i Servizi o per altri scopi importanti, quali adempiere agli obblighi di legge, risolvere controversie e far rispettare i nostri accordi. Solitamente rendiamo i nostri identificativi (ad es. quelli utilizzati per “sincronizzare” i dati sui nostri clienti con gli utenti online) inattivi allo scadere di **[13 mesi]** , a patto che sia possibile conservarli qualora si manifestino notevoli esigenze operative o legali, ad esempio a scopo di verifica, tenuta dei registri aziendali, conformità delle rappresentazioni contabili o sicurezza e prevenzione di bug.

**d. I vostri diritti in quanto interessati**

Il GDPR garantisce diritti specifici sui Dati personali che vi riguardano in possesso dei titolari del trattamento, ivi inclusi taluni diritti necessari per accedere ai Dati personali, richiedere la correzione degli stessi, richiedere che i Dati personali siano limitati o cancellati, nonché per opporsi all’elaborazione, da parte nostra, dei Dati personali che vi riguardano (tra cui la profilazione per proporre pubblicità mirata online).

  * _Diritto di accesso:_ per esercitare il diritto di accesso ai Dati personali da noi elaborati in qualità di titolari del trattamento, contattateci via e-mail all’indirizzo [support@sharethrough.com](mailto:support@sharethrough.com). Una volta pervenutaci la richiesta, provvederemo a fornirvi istruzioni aggiornate e dettagliate per ottenere l’accesso. Poiché siamo tenuti a verificare l’identità dei richiedenti prima di fornire Dati personali, valuteremo caso per caso le richieste di esercizio di determinati diritti di accesso ai dati: in tal modo considereremo (a) la difficoltà di appurare se i dati in nostro possesso e i dati ad essi collegati appartengano esclusivamente e realmente all’interessato che presenta richiesta, nonché (b) quali potenziali effetti nocivi potrebbe comportare la divulgazione dei Dati personali alla persona errata. Potremmo limitare i Dati personali messi a disposizione poiché tale divulgazione irregolare potrebbe sortire effetti negativi sui diritti di riservatezza e le libertà dell’interessato.
  * Segnaliamo che daremo corso soltanto alle richieste pervenuteci tramite e-mail e relative a Dati personali per i quali siamo titolari del trattamento, come illustrato di seguito. Se siamo responsabili del trattamento per uno dei nostri clienti, provvederemo a inoltrare la richiesta allo stesso. Per semplificare il processo, identificate il cliente a cui fa riferimento la richiesta, ove possibile.

_Diritto di correzione:_ Per esercitare il diritto di correzione dei Dati personali contattateci ai recapiti indicati di seguito.

_Diritto di opporsi all’elaborazione o di revocare il consenso:_ È possibile revocare il consenso all’elaborazione di dati per i quali esso è necessario tramite i cookie di opt-out su browser e segnalazioni per la negazione del consenso su dispositivo descritti nella sezione 2 della presente Informativa sulla privacy. In tale caso, interromperemo l’elaborazione dei Dati personali che vi riguardano per gli scopi dei nostri servizi entro massimo 30 giorni.

Ci occupiamo direttamente della raccolta di queste segnalazioni per la negazione del consenso oppure le riceviamo dalle app per dispositivi mobili con le quali collaboriamo.

  * _Diritto di cancellazione._ Disponete inoltre del diritto di ottenere la cancellazione dei Dati personali che vi riguardano in nostro possesso in qualità di titolari del trattamento. Il procedimento di negazione del consenso sopra delineato soddisfa tale diritto. Quando un utente nega il consenso tramite i nostri partner (o le impostazioni dei dispositivi mobili) e ci arriva tale segnalazione, interromperemo l’utilizzo dei Dati personali per la fornitura dei nostri servizi promozionali. Se preferite, provvederemo inoltre all’eliminazione manuale dei Dati personali che vi riguardano; se desiderate esercitare questo diritto potete contattarci via e-mail all’indirizzo [support@sharethrough.com](mailto:support@sharethrough.com) per ottenere ulteriori informazioni. Segnaliamo tuttavia che potremmo conservare copie di taluni Dati personali su file inattivi o di backup per scopi interni e necessari, quali verifiche, contabilità e fatturazione, conformità legale o rilevazione di bug. Nella maggior parte dei casi provvederemo all’eliminazione di tali dati entro 36 mesi, salvo qualora sussista un valido motivo per la loro conservazione.
  * _Diritto di presentare reclami._ Avete il diritto di presentare reclami all’autorità di controllo. Ci auguriamo tuttavia che prima vi rivolgiate direttamente a noi così da cercare di risolvere insieme eventuali reclami o dubbi.

**e. Sharethrough in qualità di titolare e responsabile del trattamento**

La legislazione UE sulla protezione dei dati opera una distinzione tra le organizzazioni che elaborano i Dati personali per i loro scopi (definite “titolari del trattamento”) e quelle che li elaborano a nome di altre organizzazioni (definite “responsabili del trattamento”). Come sopra indicato, non siamo sempre titolari del trattamento dei dati in nostro possesso, ma a volte siamo responsabili del trattamento per altre aziende, quali i nostri clienti. In tali eventualità provvederemo a inoltrare eventuali richieste al titolare del trattamento pertinente poiché i titolari del trattamento sono i primi responsabili dei Dati personali che vi riguardano.

**8\. Applicazione, domande e reclami**

Per eventuali domande o dubbi circa la presente Informativa sulla privacy o le nostre prassi in materia di riservatezza o per esercitare i vostri diritti potete contattarci via e-mail all’indirizzo[privacy@sharethrough.com](mailto:privacy@sharethrough.com) o inviare una lettera a:

Sharethrough, Inc.   
Attention: Privacy Inquiries   
170 Columbus Ave, Suite 280  
San Francisco, CA 94133, USA

Ultimo aggiornamento: maggio 2018

**Política de privacidad de Sharethrough**

## Política de privacidad

Bienvenido a Sharethrough.com, un sitio web propiedad de Sharethrough, Inc., («Sharethrough», «nosotros», «nos» o «nuestro/s») y controlado por dicha sociedad. A través de nuestra plataforma, los sitios web, las aplicaciones móviles y los desarrolladores de aplicaciones, así como otras plataformas similares, pueden mostrar contenido en representación de nuestros anunciantes (el «Contenido Promocionado»). A este contenido que mostramos se le coloca la etiqueta «Anuncio» o se identifica de manera similar como contenido de pago o patrocinado. Puede haber llegado usted a la presente política haciendo clic en un icono situado junto al Contenido Promocionado.

Sharethrough ayuda a los sitios web, las aplicaciones móviles y los servicios web a proporcionar contenido de terceros pertinente e interesante para los usuarios, por lo que su contenido multimedia y gratuito suele estar subvencionado. Para ello, podemos recabar y utilizar datos recibidos de dichos sitios web y aplicaciones, así como de sus usuarios, de forma anónima.

Le presentamos la presente Política de privacidad para informarle sobre los datos que recopilamos cuando ve usted el Contenido Promocionado o cuando visita este sitio web, y con qué fines los usamos, compartimos y protegemos. Valoramos la transparencia y el derecho a la intimidad de los usuarios.

**1\. Aplicación de la presente política**

La presente Política de privacidad se aplica al sitio web ubicado en [www.sharethrough.com](https://sharethrough.com/) (el «Sitio Web de Sharethrough»), las herramientas y los foros interactivos disponibles a través del Sitio web de Sharethrough y la plataforma publicitaria de Contenido Promocionado (colectivamente, los «Servicios»), que incluyen Contenido Promocionado ofrecido en sitios web y aplicaciones móviles.

En términos generales, existen tres categorías de usuarios de los Servicios y del Sitio web de Sharethrough: Los «Editores», que son los encargados de administrar y publicar sitios web y aplicaciones en los que se muestra Contenido Promocionado, los «Anunciantes», que muestran su contenido en nuestra plataforma, y los «Usuarios», que son las personas que utilizan una aplicación o sitio web de un Editor. Al visitar el Sitio web de Sharethrough o utilizar los Servicios, acepta las políticas y las prácticas que se describen en la presente Política de privacidad.

La presente Política de privacidad rige dos grupos de prácticas en cuanto a datos:

  * Las prácticas en materia de privacidad respecto de los usuarios de los Servicios y del Contenido Promocionado de Sharethrough.
  * Prácticas en materia de privacidad para usuarios de este sitio web (definidas en el apartado 5)

**2\. Opciones de contenido de los Servicios de Sharethrough y cancelación**

En nuestra opinión, facilitar contenido pertinente y personalizado mejora la experiencia de uso del móvil y de Internet y sirve para subvencionar contenido multimedia gratuito y otro contenido popular. Tal como describimos de manera más extensa en la presente Política de privacidad, nosotros (o un socio con el que colaboremos) podemos recopilar Información No Personal anónima asociada a las actividades que lleve a cabo en la web o con el móvil (descritas en el apartado 3). Al hablar de «Información No Personal», nos referimos a información que puede estar vinculada exclusivamente a un navegador o dispositivo, pero que no contiene su nombre, dirección, número de teléfono, dirección de correo electrónico u otra identificación gubernamental (como el número de la Seguridad Social). Estos medios y nosotros utilizamos esta información para facilitar contenido que resulte más pertinente e interesante y con menos probabilidades de molestarle (por ejemplo, para reducir las probabilidades de que vea el mismo contenido reiteradamente o de que se le muestre contenido que no le interesa).

Si prefiere que nosotros o las plataformas externas con las que trabajamos no recopilemos esta información sobre su actividad móvil o en la web con el fin de presentarle publicidad personalizada, puede cancelar muchas de las plataformas publicitarias online que proporcionan publicidad personalizada. Si desea cancelar las plataformas que pueden personalizar anuncios o contenido para el usuario (o simplemente obtener más información acerca de ellas), y con las que podemos colaborar en ocasiones, puede visitar los sitios web alojados por la [Digital Advertising Alliance](https://www.aboutads.com/) (Alianza de Publicidad Digital) y por la [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/) (Iniciativa de Publicidad en Red). Estas herramientas de cancelación se basan en cookies; por consiguiente, si bloquea o borra las cookies o si cambia o actualiza el navegador, tendrá que volver a realizar la cancelación. A través de los «ajustes» de su dispositivo también puede cancelar la recepción de publicidad en el móvil basándose en la recopilación de identificadores móviles (por ejemplo el IDFA o el ID de publicidad de Android). 

A través de los «ajustes» de su dispositivo también puede cancelar la recepción de publicidad en el móvil basándose en la recopilación de identificadores móviles (por ejemplo el IDFA o el ID de publicidad de Android). Por ejemplo, para ajustar sus preferencias de publicidad en iOS, vaya a Ajustes > Privacidad > Publicidad > Limitar seguimiento. Para ajustar sus preferencias de publicidad en Android, vaya a Ajustes > Google > Anuncios > Inhabilitar Personalización de Anuncios.  (Estas preferencias pueden venir expresadas de forma ligeramente diferente en algunos dispositivos o en algunos modelos más antiguos). Recopilamos estas señales de cancelación nosotros mismos o las recibimos de las aplicaciones móviles con las que trabajamos.

**3\. Prácticas en materia de privacidad respecto de usuarios finales que reciben y ven el Contenido: Datos que recabamos y cómo los utilizamos y compartimos.**

Una parte esencial del Servicio es la plataforma Sharethrough, que ayuda a los desarrolladores de aplicaciones y a los propietarios de sitios web a facilitar contenido de terceros más pertinente para sus usuarios. Si está leyendo esta política, es probable que sepa cómo ayuda Sharethrough a los Anunciantes a mostrar Contenido Promocionado en los sitios web y las aplicaciones móviles. Al ver o hacer clic en el Contenido Promocionado (web o móvil), recopilamos automáticamente determinada Información No Personal para utilizarla en nuestra plataforma. Podemos permitir a los Editores que empleen la totalidad o parte de esta información a través de la Plataforma para fines analíticos, y también empleamos esta información (en colaboración con plataformas externas) para personalizar el Contenido Promocionado según el usuario, como se describe a continuación.

**(a) Información que recabamos cuando ve usted Contenido Promocionado**

Cuando hace clic en Contenido Promocionado y lo ve, nosotros o una plataforma externa con la que colaboramos podemos recopilar determinada Información No Personal sobre usted. Al hablar de «Información No Personal», nos referimos a información que, por lo general, no puede utilizarse por sí sola para identificarle de manera individual o personal (a diferencia, por ejemplo, del nombre/la dirección, el número de teléfono o incluso la dirección de correo electrónico). Si ve el Contenido Promocionado a través de una aplicación móvil, podemos recabar, mantener y usar la siguiente información: 

  1. Un identificador de dispositivo, como un IDFA de Apple o un ID de publicidad de Android.
  2. Su dirección IP (que es un número asignado automáticamente a su ordenador cuando accede a Internet y que puede utilizarse para conocer su ubicación geográfica general).
  3. La aplicación que emplea su dispositivo al interactuar con contenido de Sharethrough y un sello temporal correspondiente a dicha interacción.
  4. Información acerca de su dispositivo y el sistema operativo.
  5. Otra información que usted nos envíe voluntariamente.

Si ve el Contenido Promocionado en un navegador móvil o web, nosotros o la plataforma externa con la que trabajemos podemos recabar, mantener y usar información como, por ejemplo, la siguiente:

  1. El tipo de navegador y sistema operativo que ha utilizado para acceder al sitio web.
  2. Su dirección IP (que es un número asignado automáticamente a su ordenador cuando accede a Internet y que puede utilizarse para conocer su ubicación geográfica general).
  3. Información revelada por su navegador cuando ve o abre usted el Contenido Promocionado, lo que incluye el sitio web que ha visitado antes de hacer clic y ver dicho Contenido, el sello de tiempo y la cadena del agente de usuario, información sobre el flujo de clics, el tipo de navegador, el idioma del navegador, la fecha y la hora en las que ha visto el Contenido Promocionado. Podemos recabar y almacenar esta información usando cookies, balizas web y tecnologías similares. Puede obtener más información sobre estas tecnologías en línea en el apartado 4 siguiente.
  4. Otra información que usted nos envíe voluntariamente.

**(b) Cómo utilizamos la información recabada cuando ve usted Contenido Promocionado.**

Podemos utilizar la información anterior (o colaborar con plataformas de publicidad y contenido externas que utilicen) con los fines siguientes, incluido el uso de cookies e identificadores de dispositivos, que se explican más detalladamente en el apartado 4. Por lo general, permitimos que plataformas de publicidad y contenido externas cumplan estos objetivos «sincronizando» los identificadores de editores con los identificadores de estas plataformas, lo que permite que dichas plataformas dirijan anuncios relevantes a los consumidores (por lo general, a raíz de la información que estas plataformas recopilen):

  1. Para adaptar el contenido que nosotros (u otros, incluidos anunciantes y proveedores de servicios) le mostramos, lo que incluye generar segmentos de datos pertinentes en función de dónde haga clic y de lo que vea (por ejemplo, «le gustan los deportes», «le gusta el rock clásico») y cuándo o cuántas veces lo ha visto.
  2. Para coordinar el contenido que nosotros u otros le mostramos en diferentes dispositivos, como las plataformas web y móviles, por medio de deducciones anónimas acerca de la vinculación de dicho dispositivo.
  3. Para saber cómo se utiliza el Servicio y para mejorarlo, por ejemplo, para crear y compartir con nuestros clientes (y terceros relacionados) modelos analíticos y agregados con respecto a cómo, cuándo y quién ve el Contenido (por ejemplo, si un determinado público ve determinados anuncios con mayor frecuencia o a ciertas horas.
  4. Para facilitar información a nuestros clientes (y terceros relacionados) sobre la optimización de campañas publicitarias móviles o web, la colocación de anuncios o métricas de frecuencia —por ejemplo, para ayudar a los anunciantes a saber si determinados anuncios han funcionado bien o no y por qué, además de la manera en la que se relacionan dichos anuncios con otra información conocida sobre un usuario.
  5. Para ayudarnos a garantizar que el Servicio funciona correctamente.
  6. Para otros fines de generación de informes y entrega de anuncios de forma anónima, no incluidos de forma específica en la lista anterior.
  7. Para cualquier otro fin que se le comunique en el momento en que se recabe su información.

**(c) Cómo compartimos la información que recabamos cuando ve usted Contenido Promocionado. Podemos compartir información recabada en relación con el Contenido Promocionado, como sigue:**

  1. Filiales y socios. Podemos compartir su Información No Personal con nuestras filiales (sociedades que nos controlan, que son controladas por nosotros o que se encuentran controladas por la misma entidad que nosotros), así como con determinados socios y proveedores de servicios que nos ayudan a prestar nuestros Servicios. También podemos compartir esta información con Editores, Anunciantes y otros terceros proveedores de servicios (como las plataformas de gestión de datos y las redes de anuncios) para prestar nuestros Servicios. Estas entidades pueden utilizar, por ejemplo, su información para realizar o ayudarnos a realizar predicciones sobre lo que le interesa y poder presentarle ofertas, materiales promocionales y anuncios.
  2. Proveedores de servicios. Podemos compartir cualquier información (incluida Información Personal que nos facilite, por ejemplo, a través de este sitio web) con entidades que nos presten servicios, lo que incluye sociedades que ofrezcan procesamiento de pagos, servicio de asistencia web y al cliente, analíticas web, tratamiento de datos, información específica sobre clientes y ampliación de los datos, publicidad, distribución de correo electrónico y otros servicios.
  3. Otras partes cuando la legislación lo exija o como sea necesario para proteger nuestros Servicios. Podemos revelar su información (incluida Información Personal) a otras partes, con el fin de:
    1. Proteger los derechos legales o la propiedad de Sharethrough, nuestras filiales y los sitios o servicios con los que cooperemos.
    2. Proteger nuestros derechos y nuestra seguridad, los de nuestros usuarios o los de cualquier otra persona o entidad.
    3. Impedir el fraude (o para fines de gestión de riesgos).
    4. Cumplir la ley, un proceso legal o una solicitud de cooperación de una entidad administrativa, o responder a ella, sea o no obligatorio según la ley. Podríamos estar obligados, por ejemplo, a revelar su información para cumplir exigencias de autoridades policiales o de seguridad nacional, en su caso.
  4. Otras partes en relación con una transmisión de activos. Si efectuamos una venta o transferencia de activos o participamos de otro modo en una fusión o transmisión (o diligencia debida relacionada con dicha transacción), o en el improbable caso de un proceso concursal, podremos transferir su información como parte de dicha operación.
  5. Nosotros (o plataformas externas con las que trabajamos) podemos agregar su Información No Personal con la Información No Personal de otras personas y compartir la información agregada sin limitación, incluso con Editores y Anunciantes, por ejemplo, con fines analíticos o para ayudarles a obtener más información sobre sus clientes y usuarios y mejorar la personalización y cuantificación de anuncios, el contenido y las ofertas enviadas a clientes reales y potenciales.

**4\. Cookies, balizas web y tecnologías similares**

Nosotros, y las plataformas publicitarias y de contenido externas con las que trabajamos, podemos usar cookies y tecnologías similares en el sitio web de Sharethrough y cuando emplea usted nuestros servicios, por ejemplo, cuando ve o hace clic en Contenido Promocionado. En este apartado se ofrece más información sobre algunas de esas tecnologías y sobre su funcionamiento.

(a) Cookies. Las cookies son pequeños ficheros de texto que utilizan los sitios web y otros servicios en línea para almacenar información sobre los usuarios en los propios ordenadores de estos. Por ejemplo, cuando se encuentra en determinados sitios web, se pueden emplear cookies para almacenar las credenciales de inicio de sesión, de modo que no tiene que volver a introducirlas cada vez que vuelve a un sitio web o para guardar otra información y conseguir así que la navegación resulte más eficaz y constituya una experiencia más personalizada en futuras visitas. Las cookies pueden almacenar además un identificador único vinculado a su ordenador para que el contenido y los servicios web, así como las redes de publicidad, puedan reconocerle en las distintas visitas a diferentes sitios web. Puede configurar su navegador de Internet para que le avise cada vez que se envía una cookie o para que rechace todas las cookies o solo algunas por completo. No obstante, si lo hace, es probable que se vea afectada su capacidad de disfrutar plenamente de determinados sitios web.

(b) Sharethrough (y las plataformas externas con las que trabajamos) puede emplear o admitir cookies de la siguiente manera:

  1. Para recopilar información sobre sus actividades de navegación con el fin de prestar los Servicios.
  2. Para relacionar la información que recaban las cookies con información que usted nos facilita directamente (por ejemplo, a través de este Sitio web) o de fuentes disponibles comercialmente.
  3. Para colaborar con terceros que nos ayudan a proporcionar Contenido Promocionado (a través de nuestros Servicios o de Internet) o a prestar otros servicios, por ejemplo, ofrecer a los usuarios la capacidad de ver contenido o comentar acerca de él o de llevar un seguimiento de las estadísticas de uso del sitio;

También podemos utilizar cookies (y balizas web, descritas a continuación) para todos los fines que hemos señalado en el anterior apartado titulado [«Cómo utilizamos la información recabada cuando ve usted Contenido Promocionado»](https://platform-cdn.sharethrough.com/privacy-policy). Nosotros (o las plataformas externas con las que trabajamos) también podemos utilizar identificadores móviles, como los IDFA de Apple y los ID de publicidad de Android con esos mismos fines.

(c) Balizas web. Nosotros (o las plataformas externas con las que trabajamos) podemos utilizar tecnologías denominadas «balizas web», que comunican información de su navegador de Internet a un servidor web. Las balizas web pueden insertarse en páginas web, vídeos o correos electrónicos y pueden permitir que un servidor web lea ciertos tipos de información de su navegador, compruebe si ha visualizado una página web concreta o mensaje de correo electrónico y determine, entre otras cosas, la hora y la fecha en la que ha visto la baliza web, la dirección IP de su ordenador y la URL de la página web desde la que se ha visto la baliza web. Nosotros, o nuestros socios, podemos utilizar balizas web con una serie de fines, como analizar el uso de los Servicios y, junto con las cookies, para facilitar contenido que sea más pertinente para el usuario.

**5\. Prácticas en materia de privacidad respecto a los usuarios de este Sitio web**

**(a) Información que recogemos sobre el Sitio web y cómo la usamos:**

El Sitio web de Sharethrough está orientado principalmente a Editores y Anunciantes, pero estamos encantados también de acoger a otros Usuarios que desean obtener más información sobre nuestros Servicios. Cuando el usuario accede al Sitio web o a los Servicios, podemos recopilar la siguiente información:

  1. Información Personal. Si crea una cuenta con nosotros (por ejemplo, para registrarse como Editor), podemos solicitar, y usted puede facilitarnos, cierta «Información Personal», es decir, información que puede usarse para identificar directamente a una persona en función de su identidad individual y personal. Puede tratarse, entre otras cosas, del nombre, la dirección postal, la dirección de correo electrónico o el número de teléfono y otra información asociada con esta Información Personal. Recopilamos Información Personal de los usuarios cuando la facilitan conscientemente. Por ejemplo, si se registran como Anunciante o Editor del Sitio web, se comunican con nosotros y/o solicitan información. Podemos utilizar su Información Personal para administrar su cuenta y prestarle servicios, así como para enviar comunicaciones y correos electrónicos administrativos, para obtener más información sobre nuestros Usuarios y clientes, para responder a sus consultas y para enviar mensajes de marketing y sobre actualizaciones de productos.

  2. Información No Personal. Cree o no una cuenta o nos facilite o no Información Personal, cuando visite nuestro Sitio web, podemos recopilar otra Información No Personal. Esto puede incluir:

    1. El tipo de navegador y sistema operativo que ha utilizado para acceder al sitio web.
    2. Su dirección IP (que es un número asignado automáticamente a su ordenador cuando accede a Internet y que puede utilizarse para conocer su ubicación geográfica general).
    3. Qué parte de nuestro Sitio web visita, en cuál hace clic y ve y durante cuánto tiempo.
    4. Otra información que usted nos envíe.

Podemos recabar o almacenar la información anterior usando cookies, balizas web y tecnologías similares y podemos orientar o reorientar anuncios para el usuario usando cookies, identificadores de dispositivo o tecnologías similares cuando navegue por Internet o utilice su dispositivo móvil.

**(b) Acceso y control del uso que damos a su información:**

Reconocemos el derecho de acceso de las personas a sus datos personales. Si facilita Información Personal al registrarse en nuestro Sitio web, podrá acceder a ella y rectificarla en cualquier momento, visitando los ajustes de su cuenta. Aunque lamentaríamos que nos dejase, puede eliminar su cuenta en cualquier momento poniéndose en contacto con support@Sharethrough.com. Sin embargo, tenga en cuenta que aunque elimine su cuenta, podemos conservar su información para cumplir la legislación, evitar fraudes, resolver litigios, solucionar problemas, ayudar con cualquier investigación, hacer cumplir nuestras Condiciones de uso y emprender otras acciones permitidas de otro modo por la legislación. Asimismo, la eliminación de la cuenta no provocará la eliminación de la información recabada en relación con nuestros Servicios. Después de cualquier eliminación, en nuestras bases de datos, registros de acceso y otros archivos puede permanecer cierta información residual. Por otra parte, declinamos toda responsabilidad respecto a la actualización o eliminación de la información ya revelada a terceros a los que se les haya facilitado de acuerdo a lo permitido en esta Política. Además, puede cancelar la recepción de determinadas comunicaciones por correo electrónico desde el Sitio web, haciendo clic en el enlace «Cancelar la suscripción» (Unsubscribe) situado al final de cada correo electrónico. Tenga en cuenta que aunque cancele la suscripción, podemos seguir enviando comunicaciones relacionadas con el uso del Servicio por su parte. Para conocer otras opciones, consulte el siguiente apartado sobre «Usuarios internacionales».

**6\. CONDICIONES VARIAS**

**(a) Seguridad de la Información, conservación e integridad de los datos**

Adoptamos medidas de seguridad para protegerle contra el acceso no autorizado a los datos o contra una modificación, revelación o destrucción no autorizada de estos. Sin embargo, ninguna medida de seguridad es completamente infalible y, al igual que otras aplicaciones y plataformas web y móviles, no podemos garantizar que las medidas que adoptemos no sean burladas o puestas en peligro, ni que su información permanezca a salvo en todas las circunstancias.

**(b) Menores**

No recabamos ni mantenemos de manera intencionada Información Personal de personas menores de 13 años y ninguna parte de nuestro Sitio web o nuestros Servicios está diseñada para atraer a menores de 13 años. Proteger la intimidad de los menores es importante para nosotros: si tenemos conocimiento de que un usuario es menor de 13 años, adoptaremos medidas razonables para eliminar la Información Personal de dicho usuario de nuestras bases de datos.

**(c) Enlaces a otros sitios web**

Aunque podemos incluir en este Sitio web enlaces a otro servicio o sitio web o permitir que otros compartan contenido en ellos, eso no constituye un respaldo, autorización o manifestación de afiliación con dichos terceros, ni tampoco un respaldo ni reconocimiento de sus prácticas en materia de privacidad. Otros sitios web y servicios siguen normas diferentes respecto al uso o revelación de información personal. Le animamos a que lea las declaraciones o políticas de privacidad de otros sitios web que visite.

**(d) Usuarios internacionales**

El Sitio web y los Servicios se encuentran alojados en Estados Unidos y en otros lugares. Al acceder a ellos, presta usted su consentimiento para que su información sea transferida a Estados Unidos y a otros países. Las leyes de Estados Unidos y de otros países sobre el tratamiento de información pueden ser menos estrictas que las de su país.

Sharethrough cumple los principios del nuevo marco entre Estados Unidos y la UE sobre transferencia de datos (el Escudo de la Privacidad UE-EE. UU.) definidos por el Departamento de Comercio estadounidense respecto a la recopilación, uso y mantenimiento de información personal procedente de países miembros de la Unión Europea. Sharethrough posee la certificación de haberse adherido a los Principios de notificación, opción, responsabilidad por transferencia ulterior, seguridad, integridad de los datos y limitación de los fines, acceso y recurso, ejecución y responsabilidad. Si existiera algún conflicto entre las normas que se establecen en la presente política de privacidad y los Principios del Escudo de la Privacidad, tendrán prioridad estos últimos. Para obtener más información sobre el programa del Escudo de la Privacidad y para ver la página de nuestra certificación, visite https://www.privacyshield.gov/list.

Sharethrough podría ser responsable de que los datos personales de personas de la UE se transfieran a terceros adecuadamente.

Para presentar una queja, los residentes de cualquier país, por ejemplo los países que se han adherido al Escudo de la Privacidad, pueden ponerse en contacto con nosotros como se describe al final de esta Política. Sharethrough se ha comprometido además a remitir cualquier queja sin resolver en materia de privacidad, en virtud de los Principios del Escudo de la Privacidad UE-EE. UU., a BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, un proveedor de resoluciones alternativas para litigios, sin ánimo de lucro, que se encuentra en Estados Unidos y de cuyo funcionamiento se encarga el Council of Better Business Bureaus. Si no recibe puntualmente un acuse de recibo de su queja por parte de Sharethrough, o si su queja no fuera resuelta por Sharethrough de manera satisfactoria, le rogamos que visite www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/ para obtener más información o para presentar una reclamación. Por último y como último recurso, las personas de la UE que hayan presentado una queja en materia de privacidad podrán presentar, cuando esta no haya sido resuelta, una apelación ante el Panel del Escudo de la Privacidad, un mecanismo de arbitraje vinculante.

Sharethrough se encuentra supeditada a las facultades de investigación y ejecución de la normativa de la Comisión Federal de Comercio.

Las personas de algunos países diferentes a Estados Unidos (incluidas aquellas cuya información recabamos en virtud del Escudo de la Privacidad) poseen determinados derechos legales de acceso a cierta información que mantenemos sobre ellos, así como de rectificación, modificación o supresión (además de las opciones descritas en el anterior apartado «Acceso y control del uso que damos a su Información»). Para ejercer dichos derechos, puede ponerse en contacto con nosotros como se describe a continuación.

**(e) Cambios en la presente Política de privacidad**

Se pueden introducir cambios en la presente Política de privacidad cuando sea necesario, a través de la publicación de unas nuevas condiciones, que entrarán en vigor después de un plazo razonable.

**7\. REGLAMENTO GENERAL DE PROTECCIÓN DE DATOS (RGPD) DE LA UE**

El 25 de mayo de 2018 entrará en vigor en los países del EEE y en Suiza una nueva normativa conocida como el Reglamento general de protección de datos (denominado también «RGPD») de la UE. El RGPD obliga a que Sharethrough y todos aquellos que usen nuestros servicios les comuniquen a los usuarios información sobre el tratamiento de sus «Datos personales». «Datos personales» es un término empleado en Europa que se refiere por lo general a datos que identifican o pueden identificar a un dispositivo o un usuario individual como, por ejemplo, nombres, direcciones, identificadores de cookies, dispositivo móvil, datos sobre la ubicación precisa y datos biométricos.

Con el fin de cumplir el RGPD, incluimos declaraciones e información destinadas a las personas que se encuentren en los países del EEE o en Suiza (por lo que el texto a continuación no es pertinente si no es su caso).

**a. Base jurídica para el tratamiento de sus Datos personales**

El RGPD nos obliga a informarle sobre la base jurídica en la que nos amparamos para tratar sus Datos personales.  La base jurídica que nos permite tratar sus Datos personales con los fines estipulados en los apartados 3 y 4 anteriores (y en el apartado 5 en lo que concierne a nuestros datos de clientes corporativos) suele deberse a que:

  * _Ha dado su consentimiento._ Nos amparamos en su consentimiento para almacenar y acceder a información almacenada en su dispositivo. Para este denominado «consentimiento de cookies» (el cual se refiere no solo a las «cookies», sino también a los identificadores MAID (mobile advertising ID)), nos amparamos en nuestro proceso de cumplimiento y en el proceso de cumplimiento de nuestros socios de dispositivos móviles y sitios web. Ambos procesos han sido diseñados para que se recoja dicho consentimiento y sea transferido a socios, y para que solo facilitemos la recopilación de datos obtenidos de forma legal. Actuamos así para cumplir nuestras obligaciones de acuerdo con la Directiva 2002/58/CE. Es posible que optemos por obtener su consentimiento en otros casos también. De ser así, respetaremos la legislación vigente relativa a dicho consentimiento, así como a su revocación.
  * _Tenemos un interés legítimo en el procesamiento._ En algunos casos, tenemos un interés legítimo que sirve de base jurídica para el tratamiento de Datos personales con el fin de proporcionar nuestros servicios y/o los de otros responsables del tratamiento. Dicho tratamiento excede la recopilación original de identificadores MAID. Un ejemplo de un interés legítimo en el que nos amparamos es la adaptación de comunicaciones promocionales para usuarios de propiedades web y de móviles, lo que beneficia a los usuarios y además forma parte integral del ecosistema en el cual el contenido gratuito es financiado gracias a ingresos publicitarios. En ocasiones, también incluye la realización de análisis e informes sobre campañas publicitarias.
  * Asimismo, nos amparamos en nuestro interés legítimo cuando usamos los Datos personales con el fin de mantener la seguridad de nuestros Servicios como, por ejemplo, para descubrir casos de fraude, o detectar y solucionar errores.
  * _Relaciones contractuales._ En ocasiones tratamos algunos datos si lo exige una relación contractual que tengamos (por ejemplo, nuestros registros de clientes e información de contacto).
  * _Obligaciones jurídicas._ Por último, es posible que sea necesario tratar los datos para que cumplamos nuestras obligaciones jurídicas o normativas.

**b. Transferencias de Datos personales**

Sharethrough trabaja con empresas y tecnologías de todo el mundo, por lo que es posible que tengamos la necesidad de transferir sus Datos personales fuera del país en el que hayan sido obtenidos originariamente. Por ejemplo, podemos transferir sus datos a terceros con los que trabajemos y que se encuentren en jurisdicciones fuera del EEE o Suiza, y puede ocurrir que no haya legislación para la protección de datos o bien que la legislación sea menos estricta que la vigente en Europa.

Cuando transferimos Datos personales fuera del EEE o de Suiza, adoptamos las medidas necesarias para que se den las garantías oportunas que velen por la protección de sus Datos personales. Por ejemplo, tal y como se describe en el apartado 6(d), Sharethrough cuenta con la homologación del Escudo de la Privacidad, por lo que se autocertifica para proteger los Datos personales del EEE y Suiza con arreglo a los principios de privacidad de datos establecidos. Puede obtener más información sobre esta cuestión en el apartado 11.  Si desea más información sobre las garantías de que disponemos para proteger sus Datos personales y sus derechos de privacidad en estas circunstancias, póngase en contacto con nosotros a través de los medios que se detallan a continuación.

**c. Conservación de Datos personales**

Por lo general, conservamos sus Datos personales siempre que nos sean necesarios para prestar nuestros Servicios o para otros fines, como el cumplimiento de obligaciones legales, la resolución de pleitos y para exigir el cumplimiento de nuestros contratos. Solemos dejar nuestros identificadores (p. ej., los que usamos para «sincronizar» nuestros datos de clientes con los usuarios en línea) inactivos después de **[13 meses]** , siempre que los conservemos si tenemos una necesidad operativa importante o de naturaleza legal para ello como, por ejemplo, para llevar a cabo auditorías, para la conservación de registros corporativos, seguimiento del cumplimiento o por seguridad y prevención de errores.

**d. Sus derechos como interesado**

El RGPD le dota de ciertos derechos en relación con los Datos personales que los responsables del tratamiento tienen sobre usted, como derechos a acceder a sus Datos Personales, a solicitar la corrección de sus Datos personales, a solicitar que se limiten o supriman Datos personales y a oponerse al tratamiento de sus Datos personales (incluida la elaboración de perfiles para personalizar anuncios en línea).

  * _Derecho de acceso:_ Si desea ejercer su derecho de acceso a los Datos personales que tratamos como responsables del tratamiento, puede hacerlo solicitando dicho acceso dirigiéndose a la dirección de correo electrónica [support@sharethrough.com](mailto:support@sharethrough.com). Una vez que recibamos su solicitud, le proporcionaremos instrucciones detalladas que deberá seguir para obtener dicho acceso. Debido a que estamos obligados a verificar la identidad de la persona que lo solicita antes de proporcionar los Datos personales, estudiaremos de forma individual cada solicitud en la que se desee ejercer el derecho de acceso a determinados datos: para ello, tendremos en cuenta (a) la dificultad a la hora de verificar si los datos que poseemos y los datos que hemos vinculado a los mismos pertenecen real y únicamente al interesado que realiza la solicitud, así como (b) las posibles consecuencias negativas que pueda tener la divulgación de los datos personales a personas equivocadas. Ya que dicha divulgación errónea podría afectar negativamente los derechos de privacidad y las libertades del interesado, es posible que limitemos los Datos personales que revelemos.
  * Le informamos de que solo resolveremos solicitudes que se remitan por correo electrónico en relación con Datos personales de los que seamos responsables del tratamiento, tal y como se explica más adelante. En el caso en que actuemos como encargados del tratamiento para uno de nuestros clientes, le remitiremos su solicitud a dicho cliente. Le rogamos que identifique el cliente al que se refiere su solicitud (si fuera posible) con el fin de facilitar el proceso. 

_Derecho de corrección:_ Si desea ejercer su derecho a corregir sus Datos personales, puede hacerlo poniéndose en contacto con nosotros a través de los medios que se detallan a continuación.

_Derecho a objetar al tratamiento o a revocar el consentimiento:_ Si usa las señales de «cancelación» de cookies de navegadores y de «cancelación» de dispositivos móviles que se describen en el apartado 2 de la presente Política de privacidad, puede revocar su consentimiento para el tratamiento en el cual nos amparamos. De hacerlo, dejaremos de tratar sus Datos personales para la prestación de nuestros servicios en el plazo de 30 o menos días.

Recopilamos estas señales de cancelación nosotros mismos o las recibimos de las aplicaciones móviles con las que trabajamos.

  * _Derecho a supresión._ Dispone además del derecho a la supresión de los Datos personales que le afecten y de los que dispongamos en calidad de responsables del tratamiento. El proceso de cancelación anterior da cumplimiento a este derecho. Cuando un usuario realiza la cancelación a través de nuestros socios (o a través de los ajustes de un dispositivo móvil), recibimos esta señal y, a continuación, dejamos de usar los Datos personales para prestar nuestros servicios de publicidad. Además, borraremos de forma manual sus Datos personales si prefiere que lo hagamos. Póngase en contacto a través de la dirección [support@sharethrough.com](mailto:support@sharethrough.com) si desea conocer qué otros pasos debe seguir en caso de que desee ejercer este derecho a la supresión manual. No obstante, le informamos de que es posible que conservemos copias de algunos Datos personales en archivos inactivos o en copias de seguridad para satisfacer objetivos nuestros que sean necesarios y de naturaleza interna como, por ejemplo, auditorías, contabilidad y facturación, motivos jurídicos o la detección de errores. En la mayoría de los casos, borraremos dichos datos en el plazo de 36 meses si no hay un motivo imperioso para conservarlos.
  * _Derecho a presentar quejas._ Tiene el derecho a presentar una queja ante una autoridad de vigilancia. No obstante, esperamos que acuda a nosotros en primer lugar para que colaboremos con vistas a resolver cualquier queja o preocupación que tenga.

**e. Sharethrough como responsable y encargado del tratamiento**

La ley de protección de datos de la UE distingue entre organizaciones que procesan Datos personales para fines propios (los denominados «responsables del tratamiento») y las organizaciones que procesan Datos personales en nombre de otras organizaciones (los denominados «encargados del tratamiento»). Como se ha indicado anteriormente, no siempre somos los responsables del tratamiento de los datos que tenemos en nuestra posesión, sino que en ocasiones somos encargados del tratamiento para otras empresas, como nuestros clientes. En dichos casos, es posible que remitamos su petición al responsable del tratamiento correspondiente, ya que son los responsables del tratamiento los que tienen la principal responsabilidad de sus Datos personales.

**8\. Aplicación, preguntas y quejas**

Si tiene alguna pregunta o duda sobre la presente Política de privacidad o sobre nuestras prácticas en esta materia, o bien para ejercer sus derechos, envíenos un correo electrónico a privacy@sharethrough.com o una carta a:

Sharethrough, Inc.   
A la atención de: Privacy Inquiries   
170 Columbus Ave, Suite 280  
San Francisco, CA 94133, Estados Unidos

Última actualización: mayo de 2018

**Sharethrough プライバシーポリシー**

## プライバシーポリシー

Sharethrough.comへようこそ。これはSharethrough, Inc.（「Sharethrough」、「私たち」、「当社」）のウェブサイトです。当社は、ウェブサイトやモバイルのアプリケーション、つまり「アプリ」やそれに類似するプラットフォームの開発者が、当社広告主のためコンテンツ（「プロモーションコンテンツ」）を表示できるようにするプラットフォームを運営しています。当社が表示するこのようなコンテンツは「広告」等の文字によりスポンサーのついたコンテンツであることを明らかにします。お客さまがこのポリシーにたどり着いたのは、当社の広告コンテンツの横にあるアイコンをクリックされたためかもしれません。 

Sharethroughは、ウェブサイト、モバイルアプリ、およびウェブサービスがサードパーティーの興味深い関連コンテンツをユーザーに提供できるよう、無料コンテンツやメディアを支援することもあります。このために当社ではそのようなウェブサイト、アプリ、そのユーザーから受け取るデータを匿名で収集・使用することがあります。

このプライバシーポリシーでは、お客さまが広告コンテンツをご覧になるかこのウェブサイトを訪問したときに当社が収集するデータの内容と、そのデータの使用、共有、保護の目的をお知らせしています。当社はユーザーの方々のプライバシーと透明性を大切にしています。

**1.このポリシーの適用対象**

このプライバシーポリシーが適用されるのは、[www.sharethrough.com](https://sharethrough.com/) のウェブサイト（「Sharethroughのウェブサイト」）、Sharethroughのウェブサイトおよび広告コンテンツ広告プラットフォームで提供されるツールと相互交流フォーラム（「本サービス」）で、そこにはウェブサイトおよびモバイルアプリで提供される広告コンテンツが含まれます。

Sharethroughのウェブサイトと本サービスのユーザーは、一般に3つのカテゴリーに分類されます。「パブリッシャー」は広告コンテンツを表示するウェブサイトおよびアプリの運営者または発行者です。「広告主」はそのコンテンツを当社プラットフォームで表示する主体です。そして「ユーザー」はパブリッシャーのウェブサイトまたはアプリを利用する個人です。Sharethroughのウェブサイトを閲覧したり本サービスをご利用になると、お客さまはこのプライバシーポリシーに記載されているポリシーと慣行を受け入れたことになります。

このプライバシーポリシーはデータの取り扱いについて2つのことを定めています。

  * Sharethroughの本サービスおよび広告コンテンツのユーザーに対するプライバシー慣行
  * このウェブサイトのユーザーに対するプライバシー慣行（セクション5で規定）

**2\. Sharethroughサービスのコンテンツ選択およびオプトアウト選択**

当社では的を絞った関連コンテンツをお届けすることは、お客様のインターネットおよびモバイル体験を豊かなものにし、無料メディアおよびその他の人気のあるコンテンツを支援すると考えています。このプライバシーポリシーでさらに説明しているように、当社（または提携しているパートナー）では、お客さまのウェブまたはモバイルでのアクティビティ（第3節に記載する）に関する匿名で「個人情報とならない情報」を収集することがあります。「個人情報とならない情報」とは、特にブラウザーまたはデバイスと関連するものの、それ自体にはお客さまの名前、住所、電話番号、メールアドレス、その他国民識別番号（社会保障番号など）を含まない情報をいいます。当社およびパブリッシャーや広告主は、お客様にとってより関連性があって興味を引くコンテンツを提供し、同じ内容のコンテンツを何度も目にする、あるいはお客様の興味とはまったく無関係のコンテンツを見せられるなどといった迷惑な事態を避けるためにこれらの情報を使用します。

お客さまのウェブまたはモバイルでのアクティビティに関するこのような情報は、的を絞った広告をお届けするために必要なのですが、当社および提携する第三者プラットフォームが収集することを希望されない場合、そのような的を絞った広告をお届けしているオンライン広告プラットフォームの多くをオプトアウトできます。当社は広告やコンテンツをお客さまに合わせてカスタム化している他のプラットフォームと提携していることもありますが、そのような他のプラットフォームをオプトアウトしたい（または単にもっとお知りになりたい）場合は、[Digital Advertising Alliance](https://www.aboutads.com/)および[Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/)がホストしているウェブサイトをご覧いただくことができます。このようなオプトアウトのツールはクッキーをベースにしていますので、クッキーのブロックや削除、ブラウザーの変更や更新をすると、再度オプトアウトする必要があります。また、お使いのデバイスの「設定」により、収集したモバイル識別子（DFAやAndroid Ad IDなど）に基づいたモバイルベースの広告の受け取りをオプトアウトすることもできます。

また、お使いのデバイスの「設定」により、収集したモバイル識別子（DFAやAndroid Ad IDなど）に基づいたモバイルベースの広告の受け取りをオプトアウトすることもできます。 例えば、iOSで広告設定を調整するには、「設定」＞「プライバシー」＞「広告」＞「追跡型広告を制限」の順に選択します。Androidで広告設定を調整するには、「設定」＞「Google」＞「広告」＞「インタレスト ベース広告をオプトアウトする」の順に選択します。（デバイスの機種や年式によって、表現に多少の違いがある可能性があります。） 当社はこれらのオプトアウト信号を独自に収集するか、当社が協働しているモバイルアプリから受信します。

**3.このコンテンツを受け取って閲覧するエンドユーザーに対するプライバシー慣行：当社が収集するデータと、その利用および共有の方法。**

本サービスの基本となるのはSharethroughプラットフォームで、これはアプリ開発者およびウェブサイト所有者がユーザーに対して関連するサードパーティーコンテンツを提供することを支援するものです。このポリシーをご覧になっているお客さまの中には、広告主が広告コンテンツをウェブサイトやモバイルアプリで表示するときにSharethroughをどのように利用するかを既に知っていらっしゃる方もあるでしょう。広告コンテンツを閲覧またはクリックすると（ウェブまたはモバイル）、当社では当社プラットフォームで使用するため、個人情報とならない一定の情報を自動的に収集します。当社では、パブリッシャーがこの情報のすべてまたは一部をプラットフォームを通して分析目的で利用できるようにすることがあり、また当社も以下に記載するようにお客さまに合わせて広告コンテンツを（第三者プラットフォームと提携して）カスタム化するためこの情報を利用します。

**(a) お客さまが広告コンテンツを閲覧するときに当社が収集する情報**

お客さまが広告コンテンツをクリックしてご覧になると、お客様に関する特定の「個人情報とならない情報」を当社または提携している第三者プラットフォームで収集することがあります。「個人情報とならない情報」とは、（たとえば名前、住所、電話番号、メールアドレスなどとは異なり）、一般にそれ自体ではお客さまを個人レベルで特定できない情報のことです。お客さまがモバイルアプリを使い広告コンテンツをご覧になると、当社では次の情報を収集、保持、利用することがあります。

  1. Apple IDFAやAndroid Advertising IDなどのモバイル識別子。
  2. お客さまのIPアドレス（インターネットにアクセスするとお客さまのコンピューターに自動的に割り当てられる番号で、一般的な位置情報の取得に使用されることがあります）。
  3. Sharethroughのコンテンツとやり取りをするときに、お客さまのデバイスが使用しているアプリ、およびそのやり取りのタイムスタンプ。
  4. お客さまのデバイスとオペレーティングシステムに関する情報。
  5. お客さまから自発的に当社に提供される、その他の情報。

お客様がウェブサイトまたはモバイルブラウザで広告コンテンツををご覧になると、当社または当社が協働している第三者プラットフォームが以下の情報を収集、保持、利用することがあります。

  1. お客さまがウェブサイトへのアクセスに使用したブラウザーとオペレーティングシステムのタイプ。
  2. お客さまのIPアドレス（インターネットにアクセスするとお客さまのコンピューターに自動的に割り当てられる番号で、一般的な位置情報の取得に使用されることがあります）。
  3. お客さまが広告コンテンツをクリックしてご覧になる前に閲覧していたウェブサイト、タイムスタンプおよびユーザーエージェント文字列、クリックストリーム情報、ブラウザータイプ、ブラウザー言語、広告コンテンツを閲覧した日時など、広告コンテンツを閲覧したり開いたりするときにお使いのブラウザーが明らかにする情報。当社ではこの情報を、クッキー、ウェブビーコンおよび類似の技術を使用して収集・保存することがあります。このようなオンライン技術については第4節で詳しくご説明いたします。
  4. お客さまが自発的に当社に提供していただくその他の情報。

**(b) お客さまが広告コンテンツをご覧になるとき当社が収集する情報の利用方法**

当社では上記の情報を、クッキーおよびデバイス識別子の使用（これについてはセクション4でさらに詳しく説明します）を含めた次の目的で使用すること、またはその情報を使用する第三者の広告およびコンテンツプラットフォームと連携することがあります。一般的に当社では、第三者広告およびコンテンツプラットフォームがパブリッシャーの識別子をこれらのプラットフォームの識別子と「同期化」することでこれらの目的を達成することができるようにしています。これにより、これらのプラットフォームが消費者に関連性のある広告をターゲットすることが可能になります（たいていの場合、これらのプラットフォームが収集した他の情報に基づくものです：

  1. 当社（または広告主やコンテンツプロバイダーなど）が表示するコンテンツをカスタマイズすること。これにはクリックして閲覧するもの（たとえば「スポーツ関連」「クラシックロック関連」）や閲覧の時間帯、回数に基づいた関連データセグメントの構築などを含みます。
  2. モバイルやウェブベースなどのプラットフォーム間で、そのデバイスリンクに関する匿名の推測を行って、当社などでお客さまに表示するコンテンツをデバイス間で統一すること。
  3. 特定の広告が特定時間または特定層の人に多く閲覧される場合、コンテンツ閲覧の方法、時間、閲覧者を集計した分析的モデルを作成し、当社の顧客（および関連サードパーティー）と共有することにより、本サービスがどのように利用されているかをよく理解して本サービスを改善する。
  4. 特定の広告の効果の有無あるいはその理由、そのような広告とユーザーが知っている他の情報との関連方法などを広告主に理解してもらうなど、当社の顧客（および関連サードパーティー）に、ウェブサイトやモバイルでの広告キャンペーンの最適化、広告の配置または頻度のメトリクスに関する知見を提供すること。
  5. 本サービスが適切に機能しているかを確認する。
  6. 特に上記に列挙されていないその他の匿名広告の提供および報告を行う。
  7. お客さまの情報を収集するときにお客さまにお知らせするその他の目的。

**(c) お客さまが広告コンテンツをご覧になるときに当社が収集する情報の共有方法。当社では広告コンテンツに関連して収集した情報を次のように共有することがあります。**

  1. 関連会社およびパートナー。当社はお客さまの「個人情報とならない情報」を、関連会社（当社と支配もしくは被支配の関係にあるか、親会社が当社と同一である会社）、および当社が選択した本サービスの提供を支援してくれるパートナーおよびサービスプロバイダーと共有することがあります。また本サービスを提供するため、この情報をパブリッシャー、広告主、その他のサードパーティーサービスプロバイダー（データ管理プラットフォームおよび広告ネットワークなど）と共有することもあります。このような主体は、当社がお客さまの関心事項を予測できるよう、お客さまの情報を利用することができます。またこれらの主体がお客さまにオファー、販促対象物、および広告を提供することもあります。
  2. サービスプロバイダー。当社にサービスを提供する主体とあらゆる情報（このウェブサイトを使用して当社に提供されるお客さまの「個人情報」を含む）を共有することがあります。これらの主体には支払処理、顧客およびウェブサポート、ウェブ分析、データ処理、データ拡張と顧客洞察、広告、メール送信、およびその他サービスを提供する企業が含まれます。
  3. 法律で要求される場合、または本サービスを保護するために必要となるその他当事者。当社では以下の理由でお客さまの情報（「個人情報」を含む）を他の当事者に開示することがあります。
    * Sharethroughの法的権利または財産、当社の関連会社、および当社が提携しているサイトまたはサービスの保護。
    * 当社のユーザー、当社自身、またはその他の個人もしくは主体の権利、安全、およびセキュリティの保護。
    * 不正行為の防止（またはリスク管理目的）。
    * 法的に要求されるか否かにかかわらず、法律、訴訟手続きき、また行政機関からの協力依頼への準拠または応答。たとえば国のセキュリティ上、または法執行機関の要求により、必要な場合にはお客さまの情報の開示を求められることがあります。
  4. 資産の譲渡に関連するその他の当事者。当社が資産の売却または譲渡（またはそのような取引に関連するデューディリジェンス）を行う場合、合併もしくは譲渡に関与する場合、または万一倒産する場合、当社はお客さまの情報をその取引の一部として譲渡することがあります。
  5. 当社（または提携する第三者プラットフォーム）では、お客さまの「個人情報とならない情報」を他者の「個人情報とならない情報」と集計し、その情報を分析してお客さまとユーザーを深く理解し、既存のお客さまや潜在的なお客さまへの広告、コンテンツ、オファーの改善のため、パブリッシャーや広告主などと無制限に共有することがあります。

**4.クッキー、ウェブビーコン、および類似技術**

当社（および提携する第三者の広告およびコンテンツプラットフォーム）では、Sharethroughのウェブサイトにおいて、お客さまが広告コンテンツの閲覧やクリックなど、当社サービスを利用されるときにクッキーおよび類似技術を使用します。このセクションでは、このような技術とその仕組みに関する詳しい情報を提供します。

(a) クッキー。クッキーはウェブサイトやその他オンラインサービスが利用する小さなテキストファイルで、ユーザーに関する情報をユーザー自身のコンピューターに保存するものです。たとえばお客さまが特定のウェブサイトを閲覧している場合、クッキーを利用してサインイン認証を保存することができます。これによりお客さまはそのウェブサイトを利用するたびに毎回認証情報を入力する必要がなくなります。また、その他の情報を保存して、将来のウェブ閲覧をカスタム化したり効率化することができます。またクッキーがお客さまのコンピューターに付けられている一意識別子を保存することもあります。これにより、お客さまが異なるウェブサイトを閲覧してもウェブサービス、コンテンツおよび広告ネットワークで認識できるようになります。お客さまはお使いのインターネットブラウザーで、クッキーが送信されるたびに警告を発したり、すべてまたは一部のクッキーを拒否するように設定できます。ただしそれによりウェブサイトによっては十分に閲覧することができなくなることがあります。

(b) Sharethrough（および提携する第三者プラットフォーム）ではクッキーを次のように利用したりサポートすることがあります。

  1. 本サービスをお届けするため、お客さまの閲覧アクティビティに関する情報を収集する。
  2. クッキーで収集した情報と、当社がお客さまから直接取得した情報（このウェブサイトを通した情報など）または商業的に入手できるソースから取得した情報とを関連付ける。
  3. 当社の広告コンテンツ提供（本サービスまたはインターネットを通して）の支援、またはその他のサービス（ユーザーによるコンテンツ閲覧またはコメント機能、またはサイト利用統計の追跡など）を当社に提供するサードパーティーと連携する。

さらに、当社は上記セクション[「お客さまが広告コンテンツをご覧になるとき当社が収集する情報の利用方法」](https://platform-cdn.sharethrough.com/privacy-policy)に定めるすべての目的のためにクッキー（および以下に説明するウェブビーコン）を利用することがあります。当社（または提携する第三者プラットフォーム）ではApple IDFAやAndroid Advertising IDのようなモバイル識別子を同じ目的で利用することもあります。

(c) ウェブビーコン。当社（または提携する第三者プラットフォーム）ではお使いのインターネットブラウザーとウェブサーバーとで情報をやり取りするために「ウェブビーコン」という技術を利用することがあります。ウェブビーコンはウェブページ、ビデオ、メールに埋め込むことができ、これによりウェブサーバーでお使いのブラウザーから特定タイプの情報を読み取ります。お客さまが特定のウェブページやメールメッセージをご覧になっているかのチェック、お客さまがウェブビーコンをご覧になった日時、お客さまのコンピューターのIPアドレス、ウェブビーコン閲覧したウェブページのURLなどを特定することが可能になります。当社またはパートナーは、ウェブビーコンを本サービスの利用状況の分析などさまざまな目的で利用することがあり、クッキーと併用してお客さまと関連性の高いコンテンツを提供するようにしています。

**5.このウェブサイトのユーザーに対するプライバシー慣行**

**(a) 当社がウェブサイトで収集する情報と、その情報の利用方法**

Sharethroughのウェブサイトは基本的にパブリッシャーおよび広告主を対象としていますが、当社ではユーザーの方が本サービスについて知っていただくことも歓迎しています。お客さまが本ウェブサイトまたは本サービスにアクセスするとき、当社では次の情報を収集します。

  1. 「個人情報」。お客さまが当社にアカウントを作成すると（たとえばパブリッシャーとして登録）、当社ではお客さまから一定の「個人情報」、つまり個人を特定するのに必要な情報の提供をお願いすることになります。これには名前、住所、メールアドレス、電話番号、その他この「個人情報」関連する情報などが含まれます。当社はお客さまが広告主またはパブリッシャーとして本ウェブサイトに登録する、当社と連絡をとる、および／または情報を要求するなど、お客さまが了解して提供される場合にお客さまの「個人情報」を収集します。当社は、お客さまのアカウント管理、お客さまへのサービス提供、連絡・管理のためのメール送信、ユーザーおよびお客さまの十分な理解、ご質問への回答、マーケティングおよび新商品のお知らせメッセージの送信などのために、お客さまの「個人情報」を利用することがあります。
  2. 「個人情報とならない情報」。お客さまがアカウントを作成するかまたは当社に「個人情報」を提供するかにかかわらず、お客さまが本ウェブサイトを閲覧すると当社ではその他の「個人情報とならない情報」を収集することがあります。これには次のようなものが含まれます。 
    1. お客さまがウェブサイトにアクセスするのに使ったブラウザーとオペレーティングシステムのタイプ。
    2. お客さまのIPアドレス（インターネットにアクセスするとお客さまのコンピューターに自動的に割り当てられる番号で、一般的な位置情報を得るのに使われることがあります）。
    3. お客さまが本ウェブサイトで訪問、クリック、閲覧した部分、およびお客さまの滞在時間。
    4. お客さまが当社に提供するその他の情報。

当社では上記の情報をクッキー、ウェブビーコン、および類似の技術を使用して収集・保存することがあり、お客さまがインターネットを閲覧したりモバイルデバイスをご利用になるときに、このようなクッキー、デバイス識別子、または類似の技術を使ってお客さまに向けて広告を提供したり最適化することもあります。

**(b) 当社にアクセスしてお客さまの情報の利用をコントロールする**

当社では自分の個人データにアクセスする権利を認めています。お客さまが当社のウェブサイトに登録するときに「個人情報」を提供している場合、お客さまはアカウント設定にアクセスしてその情報をいつでも変更することができます。当社としては残念なことですが、support@Sharethrough.comにご連絡いただければお客さまはご自分のアカウントをいつでも削除できます。なお、お客さまがアカウントを削除しても、当社では法律への準拠、不正行為の防止、争議や問題の解決、捜査への協力、利用規約の実施、その他の法律で許容されているアクションを行うために、お客さまの情報を保持する場合があることに留意してください。アカウントを削除しても本サービスに関連して収集した情報を削除することにはなりません。削除をしても当社のデータベース、アクセスログ、その他の記録に情報が残る場合があります。さらに当社では、このポリシーで許可されたサードパーティーにすでに開示されている情報の更新・削除については責任を負いません。またお客さまは、本ウェブサイトからの特定のメールについて、各メール末尾の「配信解除」のリンクをクリックして、連絡を受信しないようにオプトアウトすることができます。なお、お客さまが配信解除やオプトアウトをしても、当社からお客さまの本サービスご利用に関するご連絡をお送りすることがありますのでご注意ください。その他のオプションについては以下の「国際ユーザー」セクションをご参照ください。

**6.その他の条件**

**(a) 情報セキュリティ、保持、データ整合性**

当社では、データへの無断アクセスや無断改変、開示、破壊を防ぐためのセキュリティ措置を講じています。しかし、どのセキュリティ対策も万全というわけではありません。他のウェブやモバイルのアプリケーションやプラットフォームと同様に、当社のセキュリティ対策がいかなる状況においても不正侵入を防ぎ、お客さまの情報の安全を確保するという保証はできません。

**(b) 子供**

当社が13歳未満の方の「個人情報」を意識的に収集・保持することはありません。また当社ウェブサイトまたは本サービスのいかなる部分も13歳未満の人々を対象とするものではありません。当社ではお子さまのプライバシー保護を重要視しています。ユーザーが13歳未満であると判明した場合、当社ではそのユーザーの「個人情報」を当社のデータベースから削除するために相当の手続をします。

**(c) その他のウェブサイトへのリンク**

当社ではこのウェブサイトから他のウェブサイトまたはサービスへリンクしたり、コンテンツの他者との共有を認めることがありますが、それは当社がそのサードパーティーを承認、許可、または提携していると表明するものではありません。また、そのプライバシー慣行を承認または確認することにもなりません。他のウェブサイトおよびサービスでは個人情報の利用と開示について異なる規則に従っています。当社では、お客さまが閲覧するその他のウェブサイトのプライバシーポリシーまたはステートメントをご覧になることを推奨します。

**(d) 国際ユーザー**

このウェブサイトおよび本サービスのホストは米国その他に所在します。お客さまがこのウェブサイトまたは本サービスにアクセスすることで、お客さまはご自分の情報の米国およびその他の国への移転に同意したことになります。情報処理に関する米国およびその他の国の法規はお客さまのお住まいの国の法規より厳格ではないかもしれません。

SharethroughではEU加盟国からの個人情報の収集、利用、保持に関しては、米国商務省が定める欧米間のプライバシーシールド枠組みの原則に従っています。Sharethroughでは、通知、選択、転送に対する説明責任、セキュリティ、データ整合性および目的制限、アクセス、リソース、執行、賠償責任の原則を順守することを保証します。このプライバシーポリシーとプライバシーシールド原則のポリシー間で競合がある場合は、プライバシーシールド原則が優先するものとします。プライバシーシールドプログラムの詳細と当社の認定ページを見るにはhttps://www.privacyshield.gov/listをご覧ください。

EU市民の個人データのサードパーティーへの適切な移転についてはSharethroughが責任を負うことがあります。

苦情の申し立てを行うには、プライバシーシールド参加国を含めいかなる国にお住まいの方もこのポリシー末尾記載のところにご連絡ください。さらにSharethroughではプライバシーに関し欧米間プライバシーシールド原則によっても解決しない苦情は、BBB EUプライバシーシールドに照会することにしています。これは米国にある非営利のオルタナティブ仲裁機関でビジネス改善協会協議会が運営しています。お客さまの苦情についてSharethroughからタイムリーに連絡がないか、その苦情にSharethroughが十分に対応していない場合、詳しい情報をwww.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/でご覧になり苦情をお申し立てください。最後にEU市民のプライバシーに関する苦情が解決していない場合は、最終手段として、拘束力のある仲裁制度であるプライバシーシールドパネルに訴えることができます。

Sharethroughは執行力を有する連邦取引委員会の監督下にあります。

米国以外の一部の国に居住する個人（プライバシーシールドに従い当社が個人情報を収集している個人を含む）には、当社が保持しているその人に関する特定の情報にアクセスし、（上記「当社にアクセスしてお客さまの情報の利用をコントロールする」のセクションに記載するオプションに加え）その修正、訂正、削除をする一定の法的権利を所有しています。このような権利を行使するには、以下に記載する当社連絡先までご連絡ください。

**(e) このプライバシーポリシーの変更**

このプライバシーポリシーは随時変更されることがあり、その変更は新しい条件を投稿し、合理的な期間を置いてから有効となります。

**7.欧州連合（EU）一般データ保護規則（GDPR**

2018年5月25日より、EU一般データ保護規則（略称：GDPR）として知られる新しいデータ保護法規が欧州経済地域（EEA）諸国とスイスで施行されます。 GDPRは、Sharethroughおよび当社のサービスを利用している組織がユーザーに「個人データ」の処理に関して特定の情報を提供することを要求しています。「個人データ」とは欧州で使用されている用語で、一般的に、唯一固有のユーザーまたはデバイスを特定する、あるいは特定しうるデータのことを指します。例えば、氏名、住所、クッキー識別子、モバイルデバイス、正確な位置情報や生体認証データなどです。

GDPRに準拠するため、当社はEEA諸国またはスイスに居住する人々に特化した以下の表明と情報を提供します（お客様の居住地がこれらの地域でない場合には以下は適用されません）。

**a. お客様の個人データを処理する法的根拠**

GDPRは、当社がお客様に関する個人データを処理するために依存している法的根拠をお知らせすることを要求しています。当社がお客様の個人データを上記のセクション3および4（さらに当社の企業顧客データに関してはセクション5）に定める目的で処理することの法的根拠は一般的に、

  * _お客様からの同意を得ていること。_ お客様のデバイスに情報を保存し、その情報にアクセスするためには、当社はお客様の同意に依存します。このいわゆる「クッキー同意」（これは「クッキー」だけでなくモバイル広告識別子にも適用されます）のために、当社は、必ずユーザーの同意を取得してパートナーに提供し、必ず当社は合法的に取得したデータの収集のみを促進するよう設計された、当社独自のコンプライアンスステップおよび当社のウェブとモバイルパートナーのコンプライアンスステップに依存します。当社はこれをeプライバシー指令が定める当社の義務を履行するために行います。当社が他のケースでユーザーの同意を得ることを選択する場合もあります。そのような場合には、当社はそのような同意とその撤回に関する適用法に従います。
  * _情報処理が当社の正当な利益であること。_ 場合によっては、当社と/または他のデーター管理者のサービスを提供するために、当社は正当な利益を個人データを処理することの法的根拠とすることがあります。そのような情報処理は、最初のモバイル広告識別子の収集の枠を超えます。当社が依存する正当な利益とは、例えば、ウェブおよびモバイルプロパティのユーザーへの販促関連の連絡をカスタマイズすることです。これはユーザーにとって有益であり、広告収入が無料で閲覧できるコンテンツの財源になるというエコシステムの不可欠な部分を形成しています。これには、広告キャンペーンの分析と報告を提供することが含まれる場合もあります。
  * 当社はまた、不正の検出やバグを検出して訂正することを確実にするなど、当社のサービスのセキュリティを維持するために個人データを利用する場合にも、法的根拠に依存します。
  * _契約上の関係。_ 当社は、当社の契約上の関係の下で必要な特定のデータを処理します（当社の顧客記録および連絡先情報など）。
  * _法的義務。_ 最後に、当社の法的義務または規則上の義務に従うためにデータを処理することが必要となることがあります。

**b. 個人データの移転**

Sharethroughは国際的な企業やテクノロジーと協働しているため、当社がお客様が個人データを最初に提供された国の外に移転する必要が生じることもあります。例えば、当社は、当社が協働する第三者で、EEA圏またはスイスの司法権外にあり、データ保護規制が全くないか、あっても欧州ほど厳格でない司法権内に所在する組織にお客様のデータを移転することがあります。

EEA圏またはスイス以外の場所に個人データを移転する場合、当社はお客様の個人データを保護するために適切な保障措置が確実に取られるように方策を講じます。例えば、セクション6（d）に説明されているように、Sharethroughは「Privacy Shield」認証を受けています。従って当社は、確立されたデータ機密性原則に基づきEEA圏およびスイスからの個人データを保護するために自己証明します。この点についてはセクション11で詳しくご説明いたします。当社がお客様の個人データを保護するために講じている予防手段、およびそのような状況でのプライバシー権利に関してさらに詳しい情報をお求めの場合、下記の連絡先までお気軽にお問い合わせください。

**c. 個人データの保持**

一般的に、当社は当社のサービスを提供するため、あるいは法的義務に従うため、争議を解決するため、そして当社の合意を遂行するためなどの他の重要な目的のために必要な期間において、お客様の個人データを保持します。当社は通常、当社独自の識別子（例：当社の顧客データをオンラインユーザーに「同期化」するために利用しているもの）を［ **13** カ月］後に無効化しています。ただし、監査、企業記録管理、会計コンプライアンスまたはセキュリティやバグ防止目的など、法的または重要な運営上の必要性がある場合、それらを保持することがあります。

**d. データ主体としてのお客様の権利**

GDPRは、データ管理者が保持するお客様に関しての個人データについて、お客様に特定の権利を提供しています。それらには、個人データにアクセスする権利、個人データの訂正を要請する権利、個人データの制限または削除を要請する権利、当社がお客様の個人データを処理すること（オンライン広告ターゲッティングのためのプロファイリングを含む）に反対する権利が含まれます。

  * アクセスする権利：当社がデータ管理者として保持している個人データにアクセスする権利の行使をご希望の場合、次のEメールアドレスを介してアクセスを要請してください：[support@sharethrough.com](mailto:support@sharethrough.com)お客様からのご要請を受信しましたら、当社はアクセスを得るための現行の段階的な指示をお客様に提供します。当社は個人データを提供する前に要請者の身元を確認することを義務付けられているため、当社はデータにアクセスする権利の行使に対する要請を臨機応変に査定します。その際、当社は (a) 当社が保有するデータおよびそれにリンクするデータが真にかつ唯一アクセスを要請しているデータ主体に属するものであるかを確認することの困難さ、そして(b) 誤った人物に個人データを開示してしまった場合の潜在的な悪影響を考慮します。そのような不適切な開示はデータ主体のプライバシー権利と自由に悪影響を及ぼす恐れがあるため、当社が開示する個人データを制限することがあります。
  * 以下に詳しく説明しておりますが、当社がデータ管理者である個人データに関する要請は、Eメールを介して提出されたもののみを対象としておりますのでご留意ください。当社が当社の顧客のデータ処理者として行動している場合、当社はお客様のご要請を該当する顧客に転送します。 このプロセスを簡素化するため、（可能であれば）お客様が要請の対象とされている顧客を特定してください。

_訂正する権利：_ 個人データを訂正する権利の行使をご希望の場合、下記のお問い合わせ情報から当社にお問い合わせください。

_個人データの処理に反対する権利または同意を撤回する権利_ このプライバシーポリシーのセクション2で説明されている、ブラウザでクッキー「オプトアウト」およびデバイスで「オプトアウト」信号を利用することで、お客様は当社が依存している個人データ処理に対する同意を撤回することができます。お客様がオプトアウトされた場合、当社は30日以内に当社のサービス提供を目的としたお客様の個人データの処理を停止いたします。

当社はこれらのオプトアウト信号を独自に収集するか、当社が協働しているモバイルアプリから受信します。

  * _削除する権利：お客様はまた、_ データ管理者として当社が保持しているお客様に関する個人データの削除を要請する権利を有しています。この権利を行使するには、上記のオプトアウト手順に従ってください。ユーザーが当社のパートナーを介して（あるいはモバイルデバイスの設定を介して）オプトアウトし、当社がこの信号を受信すると、当社は当社の広告サービスを提供するために個人データを利用することを停止します。当社はまた、お客様がご希望の場合、手作業でお客様の個人データを削除します。この権利を手作業で実行することをご希望の方は、[support@sharethrough.com](mailto:support@sharethrough.com) までご連絡ください。 ですが、監査、会計、請求書の作成、法務、バグ検知など、当社独自の内部事情や必要目的のために、当社の無効ファイルまたはバックアップファイルに特定の個人データのコピーを保存することがあるという点にご留意ください。たいていの場合、やむを得ない事情がない限り、当社はこのようなデータを36カ月以内に削除します。
  * _苦情を申し立てる権利：_ お客様は、監督機関に苦情を申し立てる権利を有しています。ですが当社は、お客様がまず当社にお問い合わせになり、お客様の苦情やご心配の対象となっている問題を共に解決することをお選びになることを望んでいます。

**e. データ管理者およびデータ処理者としてのSharethrough**

EUデータ保護法は、独自の目的で個人データを処理する組織（「データ管理者」）と、他の組織に代わって個人データを処理する組織（「データ処理者」）とを区別しています。上記のように、当社は常に当社が保持するデータの管理者である訳ではなく、ときには当社の顧客など他の企業のためのデータ処理者として活動しています。そのような場合、データ管理者がお客様の個人データに対して一義的な責任を負っているため、当社はお客様のお問い合わせを該当するデータ管理者に転送いたします。

**8\. 執行、質問、および苦情**

このプライバシーポリシーまたはプライバシー慣行についてのご質問やご心配があるとき、またはお客さまが自らの権利を行使する場合は、次の当社メールアドレス：privacy@sharethrough.com、または以下の住所に郵便でご連絡ください。

Sharethrough, Inc.  
Attention: Privacy Inquiries  
170 Columbus Ave, Suite 280  
San Francisco, CA 94133 

最終更新：2018年5月
